[
    {
        "question": "abide by",
        "options": [
            "to follow a rule, decision, or instruction",
            "to talk or behave very confidently in order to make someone who you are competing against feel nervous and less likely to succeed",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to escape from prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to follow a rule, decision, or instruction"
    },
    {
        "question": "accord with",
        "options": [
            "to sing a song with someone who is already singing",
            "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work",
            "to agree with or be the same as something else"
        ],
        "answer": "to agree with or be the same as something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "account for",
        "options": [
            "do something without help",
            "to be the reason why something exists or happens, ...",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it",
            "same as let, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be the reason why something exists or happens, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ache for",
        "options": [
            "take to another place quickly",
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "exploit a weakness",
            "to want something or someone very much"
        ],
        "answer": "to want something or someone very much"
    },
    {
        "question": "act as",
        "options": [
            "same as block in, ...",
            "applaud",
            "same as show",
            "to do the job of a particular kind of person or thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to do the job of a particular kind of person or thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "act on",
        "options": [
            "to make someone get used to something when they are young",
            "to blame someone for something, often when they are not responsible, ...",
            "to do something because you have been given information, advice, or orders",
            "behave without courage or conviction"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something because you have been given information, advice, or orders"
    },
    {
        "question": "act out",
        "options": [
            "to prepare something to eat very quickly, ...",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ...",
            "same as face"
        ],
        "answer": "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "act up",
        "options": [
            "if children act up, they behave badly, ...",
            "same as stop",
            "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed",
            "to not do something immediately because you are not confident or you do not feel certain about it"
        ],
        "answer": "if children act up, they behave badly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "act upon",
        "options": [
            "affect, ...",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "be good enough, ...",
            "used for getting the attention of a noisy group of people"
        ],
        "answer": "affect, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "add in",
        "options": [
            "to go away, or to leave",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to include something as part of something else",
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to include something as part of something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "add on",
        "options": [
            "to leave somewhere, ...",
            "to do something or move somewhere more quickly, ...",
            "to build an extra part onto a building, ...",
            "to ask someone a question, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to build an extra part onto a building, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "add on to",
        "options": [
            "to build an extra part onto a building",
            "to experience something with great enjoyment",
            "to behave in a way that is deliberately artificial, especially in order to make people laugh at traditional ideas about how men and women should behave",
            "to support someone in a game, competition etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to build an extra part onto a building"
    },
    {
        "question": "add to",
        "options": [
            "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ...",
            "reach inside something quickly",
            "to make an amount or number greater by adding another amount or number, ...",
            "used for telling someone to try to be happier, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make an amount or number greater by adding another amount or number, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "add up",
        "options": [
            "same as save",
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually",
            "to calculate the total of several numbers or amounts, ...",
            "to escape with something, especially something stolen"
        ],
        "answer": "to calculate the total of several numbers or amounts, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "add up to",
        "options": [
            "to finish a phone call",
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "go somewhere away from people to study or work",
            "to combine to produce a particular result or effect, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to combine to produce a particular result or effect, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "adhere to",
        "options": [
            "same as pull, ...",
            "to want something very much",
            "to obey a rule, law, agreement etc, ...",
            "same as bag"
        ],
        "answer": "to obey a rule, law, agreement etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "adjourn to",
        "options": [
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move",
            "to leave one place and move to another",
            "if something tips over, or if someone or something tips it over, it falls onto its side"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave one place and move to another"
    },
    {
        "question": "admit of",
        "options": [
            "to say very firmly that something must happen or must be done, ...",
            "same as tighten, ...",
            "to show that something is possible",
            "have too much work"
        ],
        "answer": "to show that something is possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "agree with",
        "options": [
            "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "to think that something is the right thing to do, ...",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to think that something is the right thing to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "aim at",
        "options": [
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy",
            "same as bowl, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to target, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to target, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "alight on",
        "options": [
            "to write something quickly and without taking much care",
            "be convincing or make a good impression",
            "to suddenly notice or think of something",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly notice or think of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "allow for",
        "options": [
            "same as spread, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls into a place, they stop there",
            "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod",
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation"
        ],
        "answer": "to consider something when making a plan or calculation"
    },
    {
        "question": "allow of",
        "options": [
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something",
            "same as close, ...",
            "to show that something is possible"
        ],
        "answer": "to show that something is possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "angle for",
        "options": [
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ...",
            "same as haul, ...",
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to try to make someone give you something without asking for it directly"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make someone give you something without asking for it directly"
    },
    {
        "question": "answer back",
        "options": [
            "to reply rudely to someone who has more authority than you",
            "exit rapidly",
            "to completely fill a container that is already partly full, ...",
            "mess up, ruin"
        ],
        "answer": "to reply rudely to someone who has more authority than you"
    },
    {
        "question": "answer for",
        "options": [
            "to feel sympathy for someone",
            "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "to make something stop or disappear just by expressing a wish",
            "to agree to be responsible for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree to be responsible for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "answer to",
        "options": [
            "to annoy someone, ...",
            "to have a particular name, ...",
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil",
            "to call someone by telephone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a particular name, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "argue down",
        "options": [
            "stay somewhere when other people leave",
            "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything",
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ...",
            "beat someone in a debate, discussion or argument, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "beat someone in a debate, discussion or argument, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "argue out",
        "options": [
            "leave a place, ...",
            "to pay money into a bank",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "make progress, often after a pause or delay"
        ],
        "answer": "argue about a problem to find a solution"
    },
    {
        "question": "arrive at",
        "options": [
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem",
            "same as sign, ...",
            "to kill someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask about",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone in an unfair way, especially by criticizing or blaming them for something, ...",
            "to be based on something",
            "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health",
            "if money is sloshing around, a lot of it is available or people are spending a lot of it"
        ],
        "answer": "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask after",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone in an extremely unfair way",
            "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ...",
            "if something gets chewed up, it becomes torn apart and destroyed, ...",
            "to ask for news about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask for news about someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask around",
        "options": [
            "to have a good result, ...",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to ask several people for information or advice",
            "inject drugs"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask several people for information or advice"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask for",
        "options": [
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "to say that you want someone to come and speak to you, ...",
            "to treat someone badly and in an unfair way, especially by giving them orders",
            "make something smart or more presentable"
        ],
        "answer": "to say that you want someone to come and speak to you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ask in",
        "options": [
            "to invite somebody into your house",
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it",
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ...",
            "pass (time)"
        ],
        "answer": "to invite somebody into your house"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask out",
        "options": [
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ...",
            "bring or force into use",
            "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "same as fool, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask over",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone to move away from a place, ...",
            "invite",
            "focus attention on, single out",
            "to develop something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "invite"
    },
    {
        "question": "ask round",
        "options": [
            "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract",
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ...",
            "invite someone",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers."
        ],
        "answer": "invite someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "associate with",
        "options": [
            "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin",
            "same as come at, ...",
            "to wash something quickly, especially the inside of a container, ...",
            "to spend time with someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "attend to",
        "options": [
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "not turn off",
            "to study something very hard, especially for an examination",
            "to deal with something or someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with something or someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "auction off",
        "options": [
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "sell something in an auction",
            "same as swell",
            "used for showing that you are surprised, impressed, or offended by something that someone has just said"
        ],
        "answer": "sell something in an auction"
    },
    {
        "question": "average out",
        "options": [
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "collide into at speed",
            "same as rain",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "awaken to",
        "options": [
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ...",
            "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger"
    },
    {
        "question": "back away",
        "options": [
            "same as tidy, ...",
            "end or close because of a time limit, ...",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to gradually become less involved in something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually become less involved in something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "back down",
        "options": [
            "same as knock, ...",
            "to stop asking for something, or to stop saying that you will do something, because a lot of people oppose you",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ...",
            "to not go to bed"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop asking for something, or to stop saying that you will do something, because a lot of people oppose you"
    },
    {
        "question": "back into",
        "options": [
            "enter a parking area in reverse gear",
            "if you hole up or are holed up somewhere, you stay there, especially because you are hiding",
            "tease, make fun of",
            "to telephone someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "enter a parking area in reverse gear"
    },
    {
        "question": "back off",
        "options": [
            "focus more closely",
            "if something, especially a secret, slips out, you say it without intending to",
            "to stop criticizing someone or telling them what to do, ...",
            "same as linger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop criticizing someone or telling them what to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "back onto",
        "options": [
            "if a feeling wears off, it gradually disappears, ...",
            "to happen, especially by chance, ...",
            "if a building, garden etc backs onto a place, that place is directly behind it",
            "same as spread, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a building, garden etc backs onto a place, that place is directly behind it"
    },
    {
        "question": "back out",
        "options": [
            "if a feeling wears off, it gradually disappears, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to heat food until it is warm in all parts",
            "to decide not to do something you agreed to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to do something you agreed to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "back out of",
        "options": [
            "to be easy to notice, ...",
            "to make someone do or experience something difficult or unpleasant, ...",
            "to decide not to do something you agreed to do",
            "to make someone feel very tired"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to do something you agreed to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "back up",
        "options": [
            "to combine to produce a particular result or effect, ...",
            "to make a car go backwards, ...",
            "to not accept an offer because you want a better one",
            "to keep one area separate from another"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a car go backwards, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bag out",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ...",
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "criticise",
            "leave, go home"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise"
    },
    {
        "question": "bag up",
        "options": [
            "same as bag",
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry",
            "to combine different things so that they form a single unit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as bag"
    },
    {
        "question": "bail out",
        "options": [
            "same as spy, ...",
            "to escape from a plane by parachute, ...",
            "same as spin, ...",
            "to quickly read everything on a list, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bail out of",
        "options": [
            "same as pick, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ...",
            "to start to employ someone, ...",
            "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bail out on",
        "options": [
            "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable",
            "to understand or describe something exactly, ...",
            "to avoid using something, or to use less of it, ...",
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "bail up",
        "options": [
            "to go or travel to different places, ...",
            "to get into a place or something such as a car, especially in large numbers or in a way that is not organized",
            "to be made at a particular time in the past",
            "rob someone at gunpoint, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "rob someone at gunpoint, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "balance out",
        "options": [
            "to search carefully among things",
            "to explain to someone in detail how something should be done, what something is about etc",
            "same as balance",
            "to say officially that someone should receive a particular punishment, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as balance"
    },
    {
        "question": "balance up",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone a lot, ...",
            "to make two different things equal in amount or value",
            "same as stir, ...",
            "to be similar to or agree with someone else\u2019s ideas, plans, feelings etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to make two different things equal in amount or value"
    },
    {
        "question": "bale out",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ...",
            "to sing with a louder voice",
            "to bail out of a plane, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to bail out of a plane, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ball up",
        "options": [
            "to have another use or job as something",
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ...",
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself"
        ],
        "answer": "roll or form into a round shape, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "balls up",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place quickly, ...",
            "to do something very badly and make a lot of mistakes",
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to stand in front of people who have been waiting longer than you, in a way that is unfair"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very badly and make a lot of mistakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "band together",
        "options": [
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something",
            "remove quickly",
            "to remove something from a surface using steam",
            "to fix a picture to a wall, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to come together as a group in order to achieve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bang about",
        "options": [
            "to work hard in order to find something",
            "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ...",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise",
            "to move around noisily in water"
        ],
        "answer": "move in a place making a lot of noise"
    },
    {
        "question": "bang around",
        "options": [
            "if a situation descends into a certain bad state, it becomes bad",
            "to increase and become more obvious",
            "to have a formal discussion with someone in order to try to reach an agreement about something",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise"
        ],
        "answer": "move in a place making a lot of noise"
    },
    {
        "question": "bang on",
        "options": [
            "same as build on",
            "to remove something that you have finished using or no longer want in order to make a place tidy",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way",
            "to make a careless mistake"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way"
    },
    {
        "question": "bang on about",
        "options": [
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ...",
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ...",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way"
    },
    {
        "question": "bang out",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ...",
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ...",
            "to take the total of a column of numbers from the bottom of one page to the top of the next, ...",
            "add an additional point to something written or spoken"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bang up",
        "options": [
            "to improve the appearance of someone or something",
            "to put someone in prison, ...",
            "same as buy, ...",
            "to try hard to develop or improve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to put someone in prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bank in",
        "options": [
            "to pay money into a bank",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to think about something carefully for a long time, before making a decision about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay money into a bank"
    },
    {
        "question": "bank on",
        "options": [
            "store up",
            "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "to not approve of an activity or action"
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bank up",
        "options": [
            "to make something into a pile, ...",
            "to go to work, ...",
            "grow again",
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something into a pile, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bargain down",
        "options": [
            "make yourself popular with someone",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "persuade someone to drop the price of something they're selling",
            "to get rid of someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "persuade someone to drop the price of something they're selling"
    },
    {
        "question": "bargain for",
        "options": [
            "to remove parts of a film, television, or radio programme that are not wanted before it is shown or broadcast",
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "expect something to happen (usually negative)",
            "to be more than something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "expect something to happen (usually negative)"
    },
    {
        "question": "bargain on",
        "options": [
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "to expect something to happen, often because something else depends on it",
            "stop paying attention, ...",
            "to decide not to do something because you are frightened or not confident"
        ],
        "answer": "to expect something to happen, often because something else depends on it"
    },
    {
        "question": "barge in",
        "options": [
            "to enter a room suddenly and noisily, usually interrupting someone in a rude way",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ...",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "a loud sound or music"
        ],
        "answer": "to enter a room suddenly and noisily, usually interrupting someone in a rude way"
    },
    {
        "question": "barge into",
        "options": [
            "move a student to a lower level",
            "to send someone to prison, ...",
            "delay or avoid doing something",
            "enter a place and interrupt people rudely"
        ],
        "answer": "enter a place and interrupt people rudely"
    },
    {
        "question": "base on",
        "options": [
            "intend, plan",
            "to admit that you were wrong, especially after expressing an opinion or argument very firmly",
            "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ...",
            "to give people a particular opinion of someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bash about",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a group of things into a series",
            "mistreat physically",
            "re-invest money you have made into a business",
            "if you are driven back by something, it forces you to stop trying to reach a person or place and move back"
        ],
        "answer": "mistreat physically"
    },
    {
        "question": "bash away at",
        "options": [
            "to stop something from falling by putting something under it or against it, ...",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to work hard on something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bash in",
        "options": [
            "to try to catch or stop someone, ...",
            "to take a vehicle away from a place by towing it, especially because it is parked illegally",
            "break, damage or injure by hitting",
            "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "break, damage or injure by hitting"
    },
    {
        "question": "bash on",
        "options": [
            "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ...",
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "criticise",
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "bash out",
        "options": [
            "to be connected to an electricity supply or to another piece of equipment, ...",
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "to produce something very quickly and without working very hard",
            "move quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something very quickly and without working very hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "bash up",
        "options": [
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "break, damage or hurt by hitting",
            "same as strike on",
            "to make something such as an edge or corner straight"
        ],
        "answer": "break, damage or hurt by hitting"
    },
    {
        "question": "bat around",
        "options": [
            "take responsibility, often without consulting other people",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way",
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle",
            "block, slow movement right down"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way"
    },
    {
        "question": "batter down",
        "options": [
            "to break a door or gate in order to get through it",
            "same as haul, ...",
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business",
            "same as throw away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to break a door or gate in order to get through it"
    },
    {
        "question": "bawl out",
        "options": [
            "to build an extra part onto a building",
            "to spread to other areas",
            "to speak angrily to someone because of something they have done wrong",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)"
        ],
        "answer": "to speak angrily to someone because of something they have done wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "be after",
        "options": [
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "try to find or get",
            "stay somewhere when other people leave",
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "try to find or get"
    },
    {
        "question": "be along",
        "options": [
            "to have everything that you need, ...",
            "arrive",
            "to be very obvious or noticeable, ...",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something"
        ],
        "answer": "arrive"
    },
    {
        "question": "be away",
        "options": [
            "be elsewhere; on holiday, etc.",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "spiil, ruin, contaminate",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be elsewhere; on holiday, etc."
    },
    {
        "question": "be cut out for",
        "options": [
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to try to prevent something from happening, ...",
            "be suitable, have the necessary qualities",
            "mistreat physically"
        ],
        "answer": "be suitable, have the necessary qualities"
    },
    {
        "question": "be cut up",
        "options": [
            "same as turn down, ...",
            "to use or do something else after other things have failed",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "be upset"
        ],
        "answer": "be upset"
    },
    {
        "question": "be down",
        "options": [
            "cause something, usually unpleasant, to happen",
            "be depressed, ...",
            "get into trouble",
            "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be depressed, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "be down on",
        "options": [
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen",
            "to knock someone over, because you are hurrying somewhere, ...",
            "have negative feelings toward someone",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "have negative feelings toward someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "be down with",
        "options": [
            "to take something without asking permission",
            "be ill",
            "to do something that will cause problems in the future, ...",
            "to do something very quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "be ill"
    },
    {
        "question": "be fed up",
        "options": [
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "same as fence, ...",
            "be bored, upset or sick of something",
            "to make a fire stop burning by putting your feet down hard on it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be bored, upset or sick of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "be in",
        "options": [
            "to make a fire stop burning by putting your feet down hard on it, ...",
            "to continue doing something as quickly as possible",
            "to spend your time behaving in a silly way",
            "be submitted, arrive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be submitted, arrive, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "be in on",
        "options": [
            "move or travel towards",
            "to look at someone in a way that shows you are sexually attracted to them",
            "reserve",
            "be involved in"
        ],
        "answer": "be involved in"
    },
    {
        "question": "be into",
        "options": [
            "same as warm, ...",
            "like",
            "to force a plane to land, ...",
            "leave somewhere quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "like"
    },
    {
        "question": "be not on",
        "options": [
            "make a quick note",
            "be unacceptable",
            "annoy",
            "to decide not to take part in something or to stop taking part in it"
        ],
        "answer": "be unacceptable"
    },
    {
        "question": "be off",
        "options": [
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "depart, leave, ...",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "encourage someone to continue"
        ],
        "answer": "depart, leave, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "be on",
        "options": [
            "to leave one place and move to another",
            "take place, ...",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to make a choice or decision from a range of possibilities"
        ],
        "answer": "take place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "be on about",
        "options": [
            "to start crying, especially in public, ...",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in a bad or unfair way",
            "mean, try to say",
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked"
        ],
        "answer": "mean, try to say"
    },
    {
        "question": "be onto",
        "options": [
            "to notice something that is not very obvious, ...",
            "to phone several people or companies in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "pursue, be aware of someone's true nature",
            "to continue for longer than planned, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pursue, be aware of someone's true nature"
    },
    {
        "question": "be out",
        "options": [
            "to give a baby the same name as someone else, especially a member of your family",
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "be absent from a place",
            "to die, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be absent from a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "be out of",
        "options": [
            "have no more left",
            "depart in a hurry",
            "remove someone secretly of discreetly",
            "to not include someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "have no more left"
    },
    {
        "question": "be out to",
        "options": [
            "attempt",
            "to search carefully among things",
            "if a path or passage opens out, it becomes wider at the end, ...",
            "to move in a circle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "attempt"
    },
    {
        "question": "be snowed under",
        "options": [
            "have too much work",
            "persuade, ...",
            "if a particular job or duty falls to someone, it is their responsibility",
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry"
        ],
        "answer": "have too much work"
    },
    {
        "question": "be taken aback",
        "options": [
            "to write your name on an official list when you leave a place, ...",
            "find an answer to a problem",
            "to recognize that something is not true and not be tricked by it, ...",
            "be shocked or surprised"
        ],
        "answer": "be shocked or surprised"
    },
    {
        "question": "be taken with",
        "options": [
            "same as stoop",
            "to attack someone physically, ...",
            "like something",
            "not go to school or work, or leave early when you shouldn't"
        ],
        "answer": "like something"
    },
    {
        "question": "be to do with",
        "options": [
            "to physically attack someone or something, ...",
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ...",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "be connected with"
        ],
        "answer": "be connected with"
    },
    {
        "question": "be up",
        "options": [
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "to go away, or to leave",
            "be out of bed, ...",
            "order something by post"
        ],
        "answer": "be out of bed, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "be up for",
        "options": [
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy",
            "be enthusiastic about an upcoming event",
            "to tell someone a secret",
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something"
        ],
        "answer": "be enthusiastic about an upcoming event"
    },
    {
        "question": "be up to",
        "options": [
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ...",
            "same as come at, ...",
            "be good enough, ...",
            "to cover an area of ground by paving it"
        ],
        "answer": "be good enough, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "beam down",
        "options": [
            "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen",
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "order something by post",
            "same as play, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
    },
    {
        "question": "beam up",
        "options": [
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ...",
            "to give something to someone officially and formally",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "in science fiction stories, to bring someone back to their spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "in science fiction stories, to bring someone back to their spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
    },
    {
        "question": "bear down",
        "options": [
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult",
            "to try to persuade someone to do something by explaining why you think it is sensible",
            "remove quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to push or press downwards, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bear down on",
        "options": [
            "to pick up things from several different places and put them together",
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "to leave with something that belongs to someone else, ...",
            "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost"
        ],
        "answer": "to push or press downwards, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bear on",
        "options": [
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to be connected with something or to influence it",
            "burn brightly",
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas"
        ],
        "answer": "to be connected with something or to influence it"
    },
    {
        "question": "bear out",
        "options": [
            "to end something in a satisfactory way, ...",
            "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth",
            "same as ladle, ...",
            "to stop hoping that you will find someone alive and stop looking for them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "bear up",
        "options": [
            "to write your name on an official list when you leave a place, ...",
            "to want something to happen very much, ...",
            "to chase someone or something, ...",
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "bear up under",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation",
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "reach inside something quickly",
            "same as save"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "bear with",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone or to find something without planning to",
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc",
            "used as a polite way of asking someone to be patient while you do or finish something"
        ],
        "answer": "used as a polite way of asking someone to be patient while you do or finish something"
    },
    {
        "question": "beat down",
        "options": [
            "to take a part of the profits from something, especially in an unfair or dishonest way",
            "if the rain beats down, it rains very hard, ...",
            "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention",
            "same as build, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if the rain beats down, it rains very hard, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "beat off",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in winning or gaining something from an opponent, ...",
            "include the affects of possible future events when assessing the value of something",
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ...",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in winning or gaining something from an opponent, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "beat on",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "same as connect, ...",
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times"
        ],
        "answer": "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times"
    },
    {
        "question": "beat out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone tell you something by hitting them, ...",
            "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone tell you something by hitting them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "beat up",
        "options": [
            "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ...",
            "make it clear you are sexually attracted to someone",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "beat up on",
        "options": [
            "same as beat up",
            "to make someone heavy and unable to move easily, ...",
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as beat up"
    },
    {
        "question": "beaver away",
        "options": [
            "to make a car go backwards, ...",
            "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it",
            "to write something quickly and without taking much care",
            "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it"
    },
    {
        "question": "beaver away at",
        "options": [
            "to look at and speak words that you wrote earlier, usually so that someone can check that what you have written is correct",
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "to phone several people or companies in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "work hard doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "work hard doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "become of",
        "options": [
            "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house",
            "to achieve a particular level or number, ...",
            "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them",
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them"
    },
    {
        "question": "bed down",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere with someone, ...",
            "to join together in a group to hurt, frighten, or fight someone",
            "fight or argue",
            "to lie down, or to put someone else into a bed or another place to sleep"
        ],
        "answer": "to lie down, or to put someone else into a bed or another place to sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "bed out",
        "options": [
            "start to have a negative feeling",
            "if information goes in, you understand it, ...",
            "to plant young plants outdoors",
            "stop paying attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to plant young plants outdoors"
    },
    {
        "question": "beef up",
        "options": [
            "to increase or improve something, or to make it more interesting",
            "to find someone or something after a long search",
            "if something such as a sound or smell issues from a place, it comes out from there",
            "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to increase or improve something, or to make it more interesting"
    },
    {
        "question": "believe in",
        "options": [
            "to do something very easily or confidently",
            "to make something more lively, exciting, or interesting",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to think that someone or something exists, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to think that someone or something exists, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "belong to",
        "options": [
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to find a successful way of dealing with something by thinking about it",
            "to be owned by someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be owned by someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "belong with",
        "options": [
            "be in the correct or appropriate location with other items",
            "if time wears on, it passes, ...",
            "to go back to an activity after an interruption, ...",
            "to try to find or catch someone, usually in order to punish or harm them"
        ],
        "answer": "be in the correct or appropriate location with other items"
    },
    {
        "question": "belt down",
        "options": [
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another",
            "to enjoy something very much"
        ],
        "answer": "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another"
    },
    {
        "question": "belt out",
        "options": [
            "to switch a computer on in the correct way",
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument",
            "to stop something from falling by putting something under it or against it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument"
    },
    {
        "question": "belt up",
        "options": [
            "to want something or someone very much",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "to send someone to prison, ...",
            "to put on a seat belt in a car, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put on a seat belt in a car, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bend down",
        "options": [
            "to develop a career or position for yourself by working hard",
            "lower the top half of your body",
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "same as sketch"
        ],
        "answer": "lower the top half of your body"
    },
    {
        "question": "bend over",
        "options": [
            "lower the top part of your body",
            "to stop working, ...",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ...",
            "to choose one person from a group for special attention"
        ],
        "answer": "lower the top part of your body"
    },
    {
        "question": "bend over backwards",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to delay dealing with something",
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "do a lot to try to help or please someone"
        ],
        "answer": "do a lot to try to help or please someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "bid up",
        "options": [
            "to officially ask a court for something, for example ask them to give you a divorce or state officially that you are bankrupt",
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place",
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it",
            "get someone into trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it"
    },
    {
        "question": "big up",
        "options": [
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ...",
            "to enjoy yourself in a social situation, often by spending a lot of money, ...",
            "same as pull, ...",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station."
        ],
        "answer": "to enjoy yourself in a social situation, often by spending a lot of money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bill as",
        "options": [
            "to advertise or describe someone or something in a particular way, especially in order to make them sound interesting or important",
            "if people sit in, they take part in a sit-in",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "muster, acquire, gather"
        ],
        "answer": "to advertise or describe someone or something in a particular way, especially in order to make them sound interesting or important"
    },
    {
        "question": "bind over",
        "options": [
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have",
            "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ...",
            "to allow someone bail when they are waiting to appear in court, ...",
            "continue, not quit"
        ],
        "answer": "to allow someone bail when they are waiting to appear in court, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bitch up",
        "options": [
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly",
            "spoil or ruin something",
            "to drink all of your drink",
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference."
        ],
        "answer": "spoil or ruin something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bite at",
        "options": [
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to try to bite something without in fact managing to bite it",
            "same as hire, ...",
            "same as get around"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to bite something without in fact managing to bite it"
    },
    {
        "question": "bite back",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the positive effect or success of something",
            "to persuade someone to do something that they do not really want to do",
            "to make something unpleasant or dangerous happen",
            "to stop yourself from saying what you think, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop yourself from saying what you think, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bite into",
        "options": [
            "persuade someone",
            "to fill something with air using a pump, ...",
            "to stop working as a way of protesting about something, ...",
            "to press hard into a surface"
        ],
        "answer": "to press hard into a surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "bite off",
        "options": [
            "to cover an area of ground with grass",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to separate something from the main part by biting, ...",
            "to move information or users of a computer system to a new place or to new equipment at the same time or in an order that causes as few problems as possible"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate something from the main part by biting, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "black out",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly become unconscious, ...",
            "break or damage, ...",
            "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ...",
            "if a particular job or duty falls to someone, it is their responsibility"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly become unconscious, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blank out",
        "options": [
            "take responsibility, often without consulting other people",
            "to persuade someone to do something that they do not really want to do",
            "to make something by joining all its parts, ...",
            "same as blank, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as blank, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blare out",
        "options": [
            "have a good time when intoxicated",
            "a loud sound or music",
            "leave a place angrily",
            "same as ladle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "a loud sound or music"
    },
    {
        "question": "blast away",
        "options": [
            "to not live at the place where you work or study, ...",
            "to shoot at someone or something a lot of times, ...",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to shoot at someone or something a lot of times, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blast off",
        "options": [
            "if a spaceship blasts off, it leaves the ground",
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are",
            "to save money for the future, often hiding it illegally"
        ],
        "answer": "if a spaceship blasts off, it leaves the ground"
    },
    {
        "question": "blaze away",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something",
            "relax, unwind",
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "relax, do nothing"
        ],
        "answer": "fire a gun repeatedly"
    },
    {
        "question": "bleed out",
        "options": [
            "to begin working on something or dealing with something, ...",
            "if you switch on something such as a light or a machine, or if it switches on, you make it start working",
            "to have a meal at home instead of in a restaurant",
            "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death"
        ],
        "answer": "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death"
    },
    {
        "question": "bleep out",
        "options": [
            "same as set against, ...",
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "to feel sympathy for someone",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
        ],
        "answer": "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
    },
    {
        "question": "blend in",
        "options": [
            "if someone or something blends in, they are similar to the other people, objects, buildings etc around them, and so they seem appropriate or you do not notice them",
            "same as check, ...",
            "to be correct, suitable, or sensible in relation to something else",
            "to want something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if someone or something blends in, they are similar to the other people, objects, buildings etc around them, and so they seem appropriate or you do not notice them"
    },
    {
        "question": "blend into",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from a surface by cutting or digging with a sharp object",
            "to seem to gradually change into something else",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to seem to gradually change into something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "bliss out",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with a lot of different people, ...",
            "to start to feel relaxed and happy, or to make someone start to feel relaxed and happy",
            "when a space vehicle splashes down, it lands in the sea after being in space",
            "to turn around quickly where you are standing"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to feel relaxed and happy, or to make someone start to feel relaxed and happy"
    },
    {
        "question": "block in",
        "options": [
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer",
            "to have an erection, ...",
            "to succeed in doing something difficult",
            "to stop someone from moving their car out of a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop someone from moving their car out of a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "block off",
        "options": [
            "if a sports game or other outside event is rained off, it does not happen because of rain",
            "to completely stop something from happening or progressing, ...",
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ...",
            "to want something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to completely stop something from happening or progressing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "block out",
        "options": [
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "to give something to a person in authority, ...",
            "to spread to other areas",
            "same as block in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as block in, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "block up",
        "options": [
            "same as block",
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past",
            "to manage to reach or touch something, ...",
            "to prevent someone from gaining or achieving something"
        ],
        "answer": "same as block"
    },
    {
        "question": "blot out",
        "options": [
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to cover something so that you can no longer see it, ...",
            "to do things that help you to make progress towards something that you want to achieve"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover something so that you can no longer see it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blot up",
        "options": [
            "to disappear, or to make something disappear, because it has been used or rubbed a lot",
            "to fill something with air using a pump, ...",
            "same as blot",
            "to suddenly become unconscious, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as blot"
    },
    {
        "question": "blow apart",
        "options": [
            "to annoy someone by frequently complaining to them about something that they do",
            "same as stir, ...",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to destroy something with an explosion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow away",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone by shooting them, ...",
            "clock in, ...",
            "to make something end quickly, especially by using force, ...",
            "remove a title, award or position"
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone by shooting them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow down",
        "options": [
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "if something blows down or is blown down, the wind makes it fall",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work",
            "to wash the whole surface of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something blows down or is blown down, the wind makes it fall"
    },
    {
        "question": "blow in",
        "options": [
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to do something that you have agreed or promised to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive unexpectedly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow off",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to",
            "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to.",
            "to fart, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fart, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow out",
        "options": [
            "to mention something when you are talking or writing",
            "to ask someone a question, ...",
            "same as blow, ...",
            "to increase and become more obvious"
        ],
        "answer": "same as blow, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow over",
        "options": [
            "if two people stay together, they continue to live together or to have a relationship with each other",
            "if a storm blows over, it ends, ...",
            "to search a place quickly for something",
            "to seem to have a small amount of an unpleasant quality"
        ],
        "answer": "if a storm blows over, it ends, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blow up",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly find something or think of something",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something",
            "to make a photograph bigger, ...",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a photograph bigger, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "blurt out",
        "options": [
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level",
            "say something quickly without thinking, especially if you shouldn't",
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them"
        ],
        "answer": "say something quickly without thinking, especially if you shouldn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "board off",
        "options": [
            "press or twist something hard into something else",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ...",
            "have sex with",
            "to hide something by putting wooden boards over or around it"
        ],
        "answer": "to hide something by putting wooden boards over or around it"
    },
    {
        "question": "board out",
        "options": [
            "to warn someone not to come near, because of a possible problem or danger",
            "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone",
            "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "board over",
        "options": [
            "to cover something with wooden boards",
            "to agree how much each person or group should pay, ...",
            "to admit something, ...",
            "to gradually get closer to someone or something that you are trying to catch"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover something with wooden boards"
    },
    {
        "question": "board up",
        "options": [
            "to burn someone\u2019s home so that they have to leave it, ...",
            "to cover a window or door with wooden boards",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "have sex with"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover a window or door with wooden boards"
    },
    {
        "question": "bob up",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone",
            "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement",
            "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement"
    },
    {
        "question": "bog down",
        "options": [
            "depart, leave, ...",
            "to suddenly put someone somewhere that they cannot escape from",
            "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ...",
            "to reduce an amount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bog in",
        "options": [
            "eat enthusiastically",
            "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times",
            "get near someone",
            "to stop existing or being noticeable, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "eat enthusiastically"
    },
    {
        "question": "bog into",
        "options": [
            "to give a punishment to someone",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "to eat your evening meal at home, or at a hotel when you are staying there, instead of at a restaurant",
            "to find something or someone that is difficult to find"
        ],
        "answer": "eat something enthusiastically"
    },
    {
        "question": "bog off!",
        "options": [
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "get lost",
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle",
            "try to reject"
        ],
        "answer": "get lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "boil away",
        "options": [
            "move or travel towards",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "if a liquid boils away, or if you boil it away, it disappears and turns to gas after reaching a very high temperature",
            "same as goof"
        ],
        "answer": "if a liquid boils away, or if you boil it away, it disappears and turns to gas after reaching a very high temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "boil down",
        "options": [
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ...",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to pay for something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "boil down to",
        "options": [
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something",
            "to spend time in a relaxed way when you have nothing else to do",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
        ],
        "answer": "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "boil over",
        "options": [
            "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ...",
            "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to be more than something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "boil up",
        "options": [
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "light a cigarette or joint",
            "if a situation or feeling boils up, people start to feel angry, ...",
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner"
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation or feeling boils up, people start to feel angry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bolster up",
        "options": [
            "give support, reinforce, strengthen",
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them",
            "same as pass",
            "to search for something among a lot of other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "give support, reinforce, strengthen"
    },
    {
        "question": "bomb out",
        "options": [
            "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime",
            "to be forced to leave a place because of being attacked by bombs",
            "to make a noise, ...",
            "pursue, be aware of someone's true nature"
        ],
        "answer": "to be forced to leave a place because of being attacked by bombs"
    },
    {
        "question": "bone up",
        "options": [
            "exploit a weakness",
            "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "cut the electricity to a computer or device to turn it off"
        ],
        "answer": "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "bone up",
        "options": [
            "go out",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to be determined to get what you want or need, and not be willing to accept anything less",
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly"
        ],
        "answer": "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "bone up on",
        "options": [
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "book in",
        "options": [
            "be as good as something",
            "to arrange for yourself or someone else to stay at a hotel, hospital etc, ...",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to grow plants or trees on an area of ground so that it is covered with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange for yourself or someone else to stay at a hotel, hospital etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "book into",
        "options": [
            "check in at a hotel, ...",
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "understand something",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "check in at a hotel, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "book on",
        "options": [
            "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "put something in a place without taking care",
            "to gradually start using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus"
    },
    {
        "question": "book out",
        "options": [
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "to walk into a room where someone is doing something private or secret",
            "to make something less severe, shocking, or offensive, ...",
            "divert money illegally, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place in a hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "book up",
        "options": [
            "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it",
            "reserve",
            "to begin returning to a place, ...",
            "to reply rudely to someone who has more authority than you"
        ],
        "answer": "reserve"
    },
    {
        "question": "boot out",
        "options": [
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in",
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in"
    },
    {
        "question": "boot up",
        "options": [
            "arrive",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ...",
            "to have a particular cause or origin",
            "to kick something or someone hard, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to kick something or someone hard, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "border on",
        "options": [
            "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ...",
            "same as border, ...",
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to call out loudly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as border, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bore into",
        "options": [
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls into a place, they stop there",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to calculate the cost, amount, size etc of something",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous"
        ],
        "answer": "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous"
    },
    {
        "question": "boss about",
        "options": [
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "use excessive authority to control people",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ...",
            "to come out of a place or thing"
        ],
        "answer": "use excessive authority to control people"
    },
    {
        "question": "boss around",
        "options": [
            "get something by chance",
            "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ...",
            "same as stop",
            "to keep telling other people what to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling other people what to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "botch up",
        "options": [
            "stop doing something annoying",
            "ruin or spoil something",
            "to include something, ...",
            "become controlled"
        ],
        "answer": "ruin or spoil something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bottle away",
        "options": [
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ...",
            "make a lot of money",
            "store up",
            "same as finish, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "store up"
    },
    {
        "question": "bottle out",
        "options": [
            "to not do something because you do not feel brave enough",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to do the opposite of what a person, set of rules etc says you should do, because you disagree with them",
            "perform or act in an excessive way to attract attention or amuse people"
        ],
        "answer": "to not do something because you do not feel brave enough"
    },
    {
        "question": "bottle up",
        "options": [
            "to stop yourself from showing negative emotions like anger and disappointment, especially over a long period, so that these feelings develop in a harmful way",
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ...",
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to send someone to prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop yourself from showing negative emotions like anger and disappointment, especially over a long period, so that these feelings develop in a harmful way"
    },
    {
        "question": "bottom out",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you",
            "to remain in your home for a period of time",
            "if something such as an economy or price bottoms out, it reaches its lowest level before starting to improve again",
            "turn around quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as an economy or price bottoms out, it reaches its lowest level before starting to improve again"
    },
    {
        "question": "bounce around",
        "options": [
            "to discuss something in order to make a decision",
            "to remove something by cutting through it with a saw or a knife",
            "to treat someone badly, especially because they have less power or importance than you",
            "be less successful"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss something in order to make a decision"
    },
    {
        "question": "bounce back",
        "options": [
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "if a market or price bounces back, it rises again after falling, ...",
            "to chase someone",
            "to meet someone unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a market or price bounces back, it rises again after falling, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bounce into",
        "options": [
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "not pay attention, ...",
            "force someone",
            "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "force someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "bounce off",
        "options": [
            "do something quickly",
            "to discuss something with someone in order to get their opinion and make a decision, ...",
            "to know about someone or something, but not know any details, ...",
            "if a situation pans out in a particular way, it develops in that way"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss something with someone in order to get their opinion and make a decision, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bow down to",
        "options": [
            "to make something begin, ...",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you",
            "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them",
            "to get connected to the internet on your computer by using a modem and telephone line"
        ],
        "answer": "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you"
    },
    {
        "question": "bow out",
        "options": [
            "become a candidate, apply for something",
            "same as share",
            "to show something to a lot of people because you want to impress them",
            "to give up a job or position, especially when you have had it for a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to give up a job or position, especially when you have had it for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "bow to",
        "options": [
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to",
            "to do something good that helps someone to feel better after you did something bad to them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "bowl out",
        "options": [
            "same as bowl, ...",
            "to move in order to make more room for someone else",
            "to form a pair, or to make two people form a pair",
            "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything"
        ],
        "answer": "same as bowl, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bowl over",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "to be covered in insects, ...",
            "to knock someone over, because you are hurrying somewhere, ...",
            "pass (time)"
        ],
        "answer": "to knock someone over, because you are hurrying somewhere, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "box in",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ...",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk"
        ],
        "answer": "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "box off",
        "options": [
            "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it",
            "to succeed after great difficulty",
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something",
            "to put on clothes, especially quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it"
    },
    {
        "question": "box up",
        "options": [
            "same as box",
            "to make something more lively, exciting, or interesting",
            "to be about something, or to be connected with something, ...",
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as box"
    },
    {
        "question": "brace up",
        "options": [
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more",
            "to join with other people in doing a job, ...",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ...",
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something"
        ],
        "answer": "feel more confident or optimistic about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "branch off",
        "options": [
            "to leave the main part of something",
            "to avoid going to school or work when you should go",
            "to agree with someone or something, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave the main part of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "branch out",
        "options": [
            "to make something happen later than it should happen, ...",
            "to start doing something new or different",
            "to stop something from happening",
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something new or different"
    },
    {
        "question": "brave out",
        "options": [
            "annoy",
            "to deal with an unpleasant situation in a confident, patient, and determined way",
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with an unpleasant situation in a confident, patient, and determined way"
    },
    {
        "question": "break away",
        "options": [
            "same as pen",
            "become very disturbed or angry",
            "be in the correct or appropriate location with other items",
            "to escape from a person, place, or situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a person, place, or situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break down",
        "options": [
            "same as spit, ...",
            "to give up a job or position, especially when you have had it for a long time",
            "to cost a particular amount",
            "to start crying, especially in public, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start crying, especially in public, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break for",
        "options": [
            "same as ring",
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way",
            "to go somewhere quickly, especially in order to escape",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere quickly, especially in order to escape"
    },
    {
        "question": "break in",
        "options": [
            "eat or drink slowly",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice",
            "to interrupt when someone is talking, ...",
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to interrupt when someone is talking, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break into",
        "options": [
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ...",
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard",
            "to want something, ...",
            "to start doing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break off",
        "options": [
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth",
            "to end a relationship or a discussion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to end a relationship or a discussion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break out",
        "options": [
            "eat enthusiastically",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to buy something expensive",
            "same as tally"
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break out in",
        "options": [
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy",
            "to make something begin, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break out of",
        "options": [
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ...",
            "to look at someone for so long that they have to look away",
            "arrive",
            "to escape from a prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break through",
        "options": [
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break up",
        "options": [
            "to stop a fight, ...",
            "to begin to like someone or something",
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them",
            "same as ladle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop a fight, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "break with",
        "options": [
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc",
            "to leave a group of people, usually because of a disagreement, ...",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ...",
            "to tell or send someone information that you have discovered, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a group of people, usually because of a disagreement, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "breathe in",
        "options": [
            "to take air into your lungs through your nose or mouth, ...",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "to force someone to leave a place by preventing them from getting enough food",
            "to begin a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take air into your lungs through your nose or mouth, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "breathe out",
        "options": [
            "target, focus on (sport)",
            "to warn someone not to come near, because of a possible problem or danger",
            "to send air out of your lungs through your nose or mouth, ...",
            "to gradually become smaller or weaker before coming to an end or disappearing completely"
        ],
        "answer": "to send air out of your lungs through your nose or mouth, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "breed out",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help",
            "remove a character trait by controlling reproduction",
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen"
        ],
        "answer": "remove a character trait by controlling reproduction"
    },
    {
        "question": "breeze along",
        "options": [
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter",
            "move easily and quickly",
            "to become covered with a layer of ice",
            "short circuit"
        ],
        "answer": "move easily and quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "breeze in",
        "options": [
            "put food onto a plate to serve",
            "enter a place quickly",
            "have too much work",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "enter a place quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "breeze into",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to tell you something",
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "to no longer be reasonable, ...",
            "enter a place quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "enter a place quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "breeze through",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private",
            "to do something very easily or confidently"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very easily or confidently"
    },
    {
        "question": "brew up",
        "options": [
            "to make a drink of tea, ...",
            "to develop something, ...",
            "to say very firmly that something must happen or must be done, ...",
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a drink of tea, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "brick in",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone unexpectedly, ...",
            "to agree how much each person or group should pay, ...",
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "to fill a space in a wall with bricks"
    },
    {
        "question": "brick up",
        "options": [
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous"
        ],
        "answer": "to fill a space in a wall with bricks"
    },
    {
        "question": "brighten up",
        "options": [
            "be unacceptable",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ...",
            "same as brighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as brighten, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "brim over",
        "options": [
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard",
            "to be easy to notice, ...",
            "to be full of a strong emotion, ...",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points"
        ],
        "answer": "to be full of a strong emotion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring about",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something until it has been completed, ...",
            "to make something happen, especially to cause changes in a situation",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something happen, especially to cause changes in a situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring along",
        "options": [
            "to masturbate",
            "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it",
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ...",
            "to take someone or something with you when you go somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone or something with you when you go somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring around",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a lot of drugs or medicine with the result that they cannot behave normally",
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "same as bring round",
            "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as bring round"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring back",
        "options": [
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ...",
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "to forget to take someone or something with you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a dead person live again, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring before",
        "options": [
            "same as stoop",
            "to cut a line of cocaine",
            "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ...",
            "to make two different things equal in amount or value"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring down",
        "options": [
            "to have an erection, ...",
            "to not leave a person or place",
            "to cause a government or politician to lose power, ...",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to cause a government or politician to lose power, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring forth",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "to produce something, or to cause a particular reaction",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something, or to cause a particular reaction"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring forward",
        "options": [
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ...",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way",
            "used for telling someone to try to be happier, ...",
            "be so loud that another sound cannot be heard"
        ],
        "answer": "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring in",
        "options": [
            "to not include someone or something, ...",
            "to do something quickly and easily",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy",
            "to introduce a new law or system, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to introduce a new law or system, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring off",
        "options": [
            "to leave one place and travel to another, ...",
            "light a cigarette or joint",
            "to do something very quickly and not very carefully",
            "to succeed in doing something difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in doing something difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring on",
        "options": [
            "to make something bad happen to someone, ...",
            "to make something quickly out of whatever you can find",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "to become quieter or weaker and finally stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something bad happen to someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring out",
        "options": [
            "to make a profit, ...",
            "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ...",
            "to try to find something",
            "employ someone for something specific"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring out in",
        "options": [
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to leave quickly, ...",
            "to buy large amounts of something or all of it that is available",
            "to make particular marks appear on someone\u2019s skin"
        ],
        "answer": "to make particular marks appear on someone\u2019s skin"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring over",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place to the place where someone else is, especially their home",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked.",
            "to apply to buy shares in a company"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone or something from one place to the place where someone else is, especially their home"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring round",
        "options": [
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you, ...",
            "to think that someone is a particular type of person",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to agree with you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring through",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to",
            "waste time",
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring together",
        "options": [
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "to consider an idea in a way that is not serious or definite, ...",
            "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ...",
            "to create a situation in which people meet and do something together, especially when they would not usually do so"
        ],
        "answer": "to create a situation in which people meet and do something together, especially when they would not usually do so"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring up",
        "options": [
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ...",
            "to start discussing a subject, ...",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to start discussing a subject, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bring up against",
        "options": [
            "to make someone have to deal with something",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "to put money into your bank account, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone have to deal with something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bristle with",
        "options": [
            "to produce something in large quantities quickly and often carelessly",
            "to have a lot of something",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "same as mark out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a lot of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "broaden out",
        "options": [
            "to be a disadvantage in a particular situation",
            "to find out information, especially something that someone does not want you to know",
            "to have one side or edge touching something, or to put something in this position",
            "same as broaden"
        ],
        "answer": "same as broaden"
    },
    {
        "question": "brush aside",
        "options": [
            "to take a part of the profits from something, especially in an unfair or dishonest way",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to show that something is possible",
            "to refuse to accept that something is important or true"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to accept that something is important or true"
    },
    {
        "question": "brush away",
        "options": [
            "be so loud that another sound cannot be heard",
            "to criticize someone who has criticized you, ...",
            "to refuse to accept or listen to something that someone says",
            "to spend time with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to accept or listen to something that someone says"
    },
    {
        "question": "brush down",
        "options": [
            "to write something on a piece of paper, ...",
            "look for something hurriedly",
            "eat enthusiastically",
            "to clean someone or something using your hands or a brush"
        ],
        "answer": "to clean someone or something using your hands or a brush"
    },
    {
        "question": "brush off",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to listen to someone, or to accept that something might be true or important",
            "to find a job easily, ...",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to listen to someone, or to accept that something might be true or important"
    },
    {
        "question": "brush up",
        "options": [
            "to practise and improve your skills or knowledge of something",
            "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people",
            "fall silent",
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to practise and improve your skills or knowledge of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "bubble over",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "end or close because of a time limit, ...",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "break something with your feet"
        ],
        "answer": "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it"
    },
    {
        "question": "bubble under",
        "options": [
            "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous",
            "to finally allow people to see something that has been hidden",
            "become controlled",
            "close a particular computer program that requires a name and password"
        ],
        "answer": "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous"
    },
    {
        "question": "bubble up",
        "options": [
            "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "if something dries out or is dried out, some or all the water comes out of it, ...",
            "to increase and become more obvious"
        ],
        "answer": "to increase and become more obvious"
    },
    {
        "question": "bubble with",
        "options": [
            "to be full of a happy or excited feeling",
            "to make a car go backwards, ...",
            "to put money into your bank account, ...",
            "be upset"
        ],
        "answer": "to be full of a happy or excited feeling"
    },
    {
        "question": "buck up",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized",
            "same as tap, ...",
            "to be more than something, ...",
            "used for telling someone to try harder, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to try harder, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bucket down",
        "options": [
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do",
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "to rain very hard"
        ],
        "answer": "to rain very hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "buckle down",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to come to a particular place without planning to",
            "same as top up, ...",
            "to start working hard and seriously"
        ],
        "answer": "to start working hard and seriously"
    },
    {
        "question": "buckle under",
        "options": [
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "accept something under pressure, against your will",
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
        ],
        "answer": "accept something under pressure, against your will"
    },
    {
        "question": "buckle up",
        "options": [
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "to do the same activity for a very long time",
            "same as buckle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as buckle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "budge up",
        "options": [
            "to move so that there is space for someone else",
            "to expect something to happen, often because something else depends on it",
            "to get a lot of pleasure or enjoyment from something",
            "to be given to someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move so that there is space for someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "buff up",
        "options": [
            "give support, reinforce, strengthen",
            "to suddenly leave your wife, husband, or partner",
            "to continue to be enough or continue to exist, ...",
            "improve, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "improve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buff up on",
        "options": [
            "sign a document joining or agreeing to something",
            "improve your knowledge quickly",
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "to end a romantic or sexual relationship with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "improve your knowledge quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "bug off",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly stop working, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone",
            "to consider all the important facts in a situation before deciding or doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone rudely to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "bug off!",
        "options": [
            "to make something accepted officially by voting",
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone rudely to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "bug out",
        "options": [
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "wipe, remove with a brush, ...",
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "to leave quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bugger about",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to cause problems for someone, ...",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions"
        ],
        "answer": "to cause problems for someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bugger off",
        "options": [
            "same as lock",
            "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you",
            "to try to find out information about someone or something",
            "to leave or go away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave or go away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bugger up",
        "options": [
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to be careful",
            "to spoil something or do something badly"
        ],
        "answer": "to spoil something or do something badly"
    },
    {
        "question": "build around",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something that takes a lot of effort or is likely to cause you problems",
            "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen",
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future",
            "to make a particular aim or idea the main part of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a particular aim or idea the main part of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "build in",
        "options": [
            "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ...",
            "to not allow your feelings to show, ...",
            "to ask or persuade someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "build into",
        "options": [
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group",
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ...",
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "build on",
        "options": [
            "to start talking about something when it is not necessary, usually something unpleasant that happened in the past and that other people want to forget",
            "to build a new room or part onto the outside of a building, ...",
            "same as tail off",
            "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to build a new room or part onto the outside of a building, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "build up",
        "options": [
            "to have something as a final result, ...",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "same as build, ...",
            "to deal with something such as a problem or a strong feeling by thinking and talking about it"
        ],
        "answer": "same as build, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "build up to",
        "options": [
            "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ...",
            "to read the measurement on a piece of equipment or graph"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do"
    },
    {
        "question": "build upon",
        "options": [
            "same as build on",
            "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen",
            "to immediately take advantage of an opportunity, ...",
            "if you force back tears, you try very hard not to cry"
        ],
        "answer": "same as build on"
    },
    {
        "question": "bulk out",
        "options": [
            "to start driving in a higher gear",
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "same as finish, ...",
            "to add something to something else to make it bigger or more satisfactory"
        ],
        "answer": "to add something to something else to make it bigger or more satisfactory"
    },
    {
        "question": "bulk up",
        "options": [
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other",
            "to become bigger and heavier",
            "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something",
            "stop doing something annoying"
        ],
        "answer": "to become bigger and heavier"
    },
    {
        "question": "bully off",
        "options": [
            "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball"
    },
    {
        "question": "bum around",
        "options": [
            "be the reason for something",
            "to be the most important aspect of a situation or problem, ...",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth",
            "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bum out",
        "options": [
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future",
            "to buy a large quantity of something",
            "to annoy someone or make them disappointed",
            "behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to annoy someone or make them disappointed"
    },
    {
        "question": "bump along",
        "options": [
            "to be very busy doing a lot of different things",
            "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom",
            "to continue at around the same level, rising and falling only slightly",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue at around the same level, rising and falling only slightly"
    },
    {
        "question": "bump into",
        "options": [
            "to be the real reason for a decision or action",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "to meet someone unexpectedly, ...",
            "think of someone or something in a particular way"
        ],
        "answer": "to meet someone unexpectedly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bump off",
        "options": [
            "to murder someone",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice",
            "to take off clothes, especially quickly, ...",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to murder someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "bump up",
        "options": [
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "to increase something, ...",
            "to keep one area separate from another",
            "pay attention after not doing so"
        ],
        "answer": "to increase something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bump up against",
        "options": [
            "to make someone angry, or to argue with them, ...",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ...",
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress"
        ],
        "answer": "to experience a problem that slows down your progress"
    },
    {
        "question": "bundle off",
        "options": [
            "collide into at speed",
            "to make someone go somewhere, especially in order to get rid of them",
            "be upset",
            "form a pair with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone go somewhere, especially in order to get rid of them"
    },
    {
        "question": "bundle out",
        "options": [
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "expel",
            "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off",
            "same as drop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "expel"
    },
    {
        "question": "bundle up",
        "options": [
            "same as bundle, ...",
            "if you have someone over, they come to your house to visit you or to stay with you",
            "to be caused by something",
            "behave without courage or conviction"
        ],
        "answer": "same as bundle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bung up",
        "options": [
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "same as bung, ...",
            "same as separate",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen"
        ],
        "answer": "same as bung, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bunk off",
        "options": [
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to spoil or damage something completely, ...",
            "fill a venue",
            "to not go to school or work when you do not have a good reason for staying away",
            "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea"
        ],
        "answer": "to not go to school or work when you do not have a good reason for staying away"
    },
    {
        "question": "buoy up",
        "options": [
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone",
            "keep afloat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "keep afloat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burn away",
        "options": [
            "to remove something, or to be removed, by burning",
            "to plan in detail how something will happen",
            "to hold something above someone or something, ...",
            "to start existing or being seen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something, or to be removed, by burning"
    },
    {
        "question": "burn down",
        "options": [
            "if a fire or flame burns down, it becomes smaller and less hot, ...",
            "to switch a computer off in the correct way",
            "to make someone leave a job or position so that you or someone else can take their place",
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a fire or flame burns down, it becomes smaller and less hot, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burn in",
        "options": [
            "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are",
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something",
            "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems"
        ],
        "answer": "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "burn off",
        "options": [
            "same as push, ...",
            "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ...",
            "to remove something by burning it, ...",
            "to prepare someone for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something by burning it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burn out",
        "options": [
            "same as fill, ...",
            "to remove something by cutting, especially a part of someone\u2019s body",
            "to burn someone\u2019s home so that they have to leave it, ...",
            "open an advertisement on the internet"
        ],
        "answer": "to burn someone\u2019s home so that they have to leave it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burn up",
        "options": [
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ...",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "same as burn off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as burn off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burst in on",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something",
            "to write something somewhere, ...",
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "to combine with something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "burst into",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly start doing something, ...",
            "become gradually more evident, ...",
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ...",
            "same as flatten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly start doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "burst out",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly say or shout something, ...",
            "if time goes by, it passes, ...",
            "if people stick together, they remain close together and support one another",
            "to arrange an agreement or deal, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly say or shout something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bust out",
        "options": [
            "to escape from prison, ...",
            "talk too much",
            "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin",
            "to make something last for a long time, usually longer than is good or necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "bust up",
        "options": [
            "same as mop, ...",
            "to oppose someone or something, especially in a brave or determined way, ...",
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ...",
            "same as bust, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as bust, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "butt in",
        "options": [
            "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do",
            "to join a conversation or activity without being asked to",
            "mistreat physically"
        ],
        "answer": "to join a conversation or activity without being asked to"
    },
    {
        "question": "butt out",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something",
            "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature",
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ...",
            "leave, go home"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "butt up",
        "options": [
            "to have one side or edge touching something, or to put something in this position",
            "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)",
            "same as sign, ...",
            "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping"
        ],
        "answer": "to have one side or edge touching something, or to put something in this position"
    },
    {
        "question": "butter up",
        "options": [
            "to be nice to someone so that they will help or support you",
            "if something boring or unpleasant grinds on, it continues happening for a long period of time",
            "to behave in a stupid way, ...",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to be nice to someone so that they will help or support you"
    },
    {
        "question": "button up",
        "options": [
            "to exist in or belong to someone or something",
            "same as button, ...",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something",
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "same as button, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buy in",
        "options": [
            "to buy a large quantity of something",
            "confront, ...",
            "to eat only a small amount of a meal, without much interest",
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to buy a large quantity of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy into",
        "options": [
            "to buy part of a business, especially in order to get control of it, ...",
            "to be provided together with something, ...",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job, ...",
            "if something such as rain or a river washes something away, it carries it away"
        ],
        "answer": "to buy part of a business, especially in order to get control of it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buy off",
        "options": [
            "to get a lot of pleasure or enjoyment from something",
            "to make someone remember something that happened in the past, ...",
            "same as buy, ...",
            "arrive, end a journey in a place, often without planning"
        ],
        "answer": "same as buy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buy out",
        "options": [
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ...",
            "to give things to different people in a group",
            "to react angrily towards someone",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buy up",
        "options": [
            "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ...",
            "to buy large amounts of something or all of it that is available",
            "to make a person or animal fatter",
            "not very attractive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to buy large amounts of something or all of it that is available"
    },
    {
        "question": "buzz around",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to move somewhere while buzzing, ...",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move somewhere while buzzing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "buzz off",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult",
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "buzz off!",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ...",
            "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad",
            "to cause problems or delays for someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "calculate on",
        "options": [
            "to reach a decision or agreement after discussing it or arguing about it for a long time",
            "to expect something to happen",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "to expect something to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "call after",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to give a baby the same name as someone else, especially a member of your family",
            "to push someone or something hard so that they fall from the position that they are in"
        ],
        "answer": "to give a baby the same name as someone else, especially a member of your family"
    },
    {
        "question": "call around",
        "options": [
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "visit",
            "break or damage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "visit"
    },
    {
        "question": "call at",
        "options": [
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "appear",
            "be in the correct or appropriate location with other items",
            "to make a place tidy after someone else has made it untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to telephone someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call away",
        "options": [
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do",
            "to depend on something",
            "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ...",
            "to ask someone to leave a place, usually by telephoning them or sending them a message"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone to leave a place, usually by telephoning them or sending them a message"
    },
    {
        "question": "call back",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out information about someone or something",
            "to go and see someone again, usually for a short time, ...",
            "to try to catch or stop someone, ...",
            "to sing with a louder voice"
        ],
        "answer": "to go and see someone again, usually for a short time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call by",
        "options": [
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly",
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time",
            "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to visit someone, usually for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "call down",
        "options": [
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "to pray for something bad to happen to someone",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pray for something bad to happen to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "call for",
        "options": [
            "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ...",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "to make something necessary or suitable, ...",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something necessary or suitable, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call forth",
        "options": [
            "same as shade",
            "to do something very badly",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to waste someone else\u2019s time or treat them in a bad way, ...",
            "to produce a particular reaction"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a particular reaction"
    },
    {
        "question": "call in",
        "options": [
            "same as call, ...",
            "same as cut, ...",
            "same as stop",
            "be enthusiastic about an upcoming event"
        ],
        "answer": "same as call, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call off",
        "options": [
            "same as separate",
            "to decide that something will not happen, ...",
            "make an empty space inside in something, reduce power or authority",
            "to have only a few things left to use or deal with, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to decide that something will not happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call on",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time, ...",
            "to improve, ...",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time",
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them"
        ],
        "answer": "to visit someone, usually for a short time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call out",
        "options": [
            "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to",
            "to buy a lot of something so that it is available when you need it",
            "to look at and speak words that you wrote earlier, usually so that someone can check that what you have written is correct",
            "to challenge someone over something they have said or done, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to challenge someone over something they have said or done, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call round",
        "options": [
            "to be dressed in a particular way, ...",
            "same as call",
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument",
            "if air or smoke puffs out, or if you puff it out, you blow it out with a short breath, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as call"
    },
    {
        "question": "call up",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to do something you agreed to do",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "add a keyword link or bookmark to a blog entry or webpage"
        ],
        "answer": "to telephone someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "call upon",
        "options": [
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "same as call on",
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as call on"
    },
    {
        "question": "calm down",
        "options": [
            "to escape with something, especially something stolen",
            "same as mail",
            "same as call, ...",
            "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "camp out",
        "options": [
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized",
            "to happen, ...",
            "same as camp, ...",
            "to search for someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as camp, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "camp up",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a way that is deliberately artificial, especially in order to make people laugh at traditional ideas about how men and women should behave",
            "let, grant a service or allow usage for a fee",
            "be upset",
            "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a way that is deliberately artificial, especially in order to make people laugh at traditional ideas about how men and women should behave"
    },
    {
        "question": "cancel out",
        "options": [
            "to stop something from having any effect",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "same as flush, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop something from having any effect"
    },
    {
        "question": "cap off",
        "options": [
            "to prevent the flavour, smell, or juice of a food from getting out",
            "finish or complete, often with some decisive action",
            "to heat food that has already been cooked, until every part of it is very hot",
            "if coloured, cut, or permed hair grows out, it grows so that it no longer has the colour or style that it had"
        ],
        "answer": "finish or complete, often with some decisive action"
    },
    {
        "question": "capitalize on",
        "options": [
            "to use an event or a situation to help you to achieve something or to get an advantage",
            "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ...",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely"
        ],
        "answer": "to use an event or a situation to help you to achieve something or to get an advantage"
    },
    {
        "question": "care for",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to treat something carefully so that it stays in good condition, ...",
            "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off",
            "to remove something, or to be removed, by burning"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat something carefully so that it stays in good condition, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carried away",
        "options": [
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ...",
            "to go to a place for only a short period of time before continuing a journey",
            "get so emotional that you lose control",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points"
        ],
        "answer": "get so emotional that you lose control"
    },
    {
        "question": "carry forward",
        "options": [
            "to start a journey, ...",
            "to annoy someone, ...",
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ...",
            "to take the total of a column of numbers from the bottom of one page to the top of the next, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take the total of a column of numbers from the bottom of one page to the top of the next, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry off",
        "options": [
            "to reply rudely to someone who has more authority than you",
            "to take air into your lungs through your nose or mouth, ...",
            "to begin something or begin to take part in something",
            "to win a prize, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to win a prize, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry on",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people",
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ...",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry on with",
        "options": [
            "if a piece of clothing rides up, it gradually moves upwards on your body",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to reduce a number to the nearest whole number, or the nearest number ending in zero",
            "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry out",
        "options": [
            "to do a particular piece of work, research etc, ...",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ...",
            "to slow down, or to become less"
        ],
        "answer": "to do a particular piece of work, research etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry over",
        "options": [
            "to do something so that a proposal is accepted or an issue is dealt with quickly",
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ...",
            "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it"
        ],
        "answer": "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "carry through",
        "options": [
            "if a liquid boils away, or if you boil it away, it disappears and turns to gas after reaching a very high temperature",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you or to be friendly to you",
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ...",
            "be out of bed, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cart off",
        "options": [
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ...",
            "to take someone somewhere, especially to a prison or hospital",
            "to give up a job or position, especially when you have had it for a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone somewhere, especially to a prison or hospital"
    },
    {
        "question": "carve out",
        "options": [
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ...",
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to develop a career or position for yourself by working hard",
            "to do a lot of activities in a short time"
        ],
        "answer": "to develop a career or position for yourself by working hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "carve up",
        "options": [
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ...",
            "to injure someone severely by hitting them",
            "to stop criticizing someone or telling them what to do, ...",
            "same as fill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cash in",
        "options": [
            "same as turn down, ...",
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter",
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ...",
            "pass quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cash in on",
        "options": [
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ...",
            "if someone is shut out of something, they are not allowed to do it or be involved in it",
            "to not be willing to do something difficult, or to not deal with something unpleasant",
            "to be used to help to pay for something"
        ],
        "answer": "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cash out",
        "options": [
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "exchange something for money, collect winnings, ...",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "exchange something for money, collect winnings, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cash up",
        "options": [
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "to spread to other areas",
            "to count and check all the money that a shop has received in a day",
            "be unacceptable"
        ],
        "answer": "to count and check all the money that a shop has received in a day"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast about for",
        "options": [
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "to leave a place, especially in a way that is not noticed by other people",
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast around for",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ...",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "to kill someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast aside",
        "options": [
            "to take a piece of clothing off",
            "same as cover, ...",
            "to not include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to get rid of someone or something because it is no longer interesting or valuable to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of someone or something because it is no longer interesting or valuable to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast off",
        "options": [
            "remove a character trait by controlling reproduction",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "to get rid of someone or something, ...",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cast on",
        "options": [
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "to start a piece of knitting by making the first row of stitches",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way",
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a piece of knitting by making the first row of stitches"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast out",
        "options": [
            "same as invite",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time, ...",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone or something to leave a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast round for",
        "options": [
            "try to find something",
            "join or enter a competition",
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ...",
            "same as mail"
        ],
        "answer": "try to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "cast up",
        "options": [
            "if the sea casts something up, the sea carries it somewhere and leaves it there",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work",
            "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to."
        ],
        "answer": "if the sea casts something up, the sea carries it somewhere and leaves it there"
    },
    {
        "question": "catch at",
        "options": [
            "to completely stop something from happening or progressing, ...",
            "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime",
            "to make a place smell very unpleasant",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to reach out and try to get hold of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "catch on",
        "options": [
            "to employ someone to do a job, ...",
            "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem",
            "to understand, ...",
            "to start a new activity, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to understand, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "catch out",
        "options": [
            "to make something stop or disappear just by expressing a wish",
            "to show that something is possible",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ...",
            "same as catch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as catch, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "catch up",
        "options": [
            "if you are struck on someone or something, you like them, ...",
            "focus more closely",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ...",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something that should have been done before, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "catch up in",
        "options": [
            "to start to employ someone, ...",
            "become involved, often against one\ufffds will",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to search very hard for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "become involved, often against one\ufffds will"
    },
    {
        "question": "catch up on",
        "options": [
            "same as come on to, ...",
            "to go and see someone again, usually for a short time, ...",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ...",
            "to go away, or to leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something that should have been done before, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "catch up with",
        "options": [
            "to speak in an angry way to someone who has done something wrong, ...",
            "to include something as part of something else",
            "to remove something from a surface by gently touching it several times with something such as a piece of cloth",
            "to begin to have an effect on someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to have an effect on someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cater for",
        "options": [
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to make something seem more impressive than it really is, ...",
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to provide people with everything they want or need"
    },
    {
        "question": "cater to",
        "options": [
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ...",
            "when something continues to happen",
            "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special"
        ],
        "answer": "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special"
    },
    {
        "question": "cave in",
        "options": [
            "if a roof or wall caves in, it falls down or inwards, ...",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to add something to someone else\u2019s conversation, ...",
            "to begin to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "if a roof or wall caves in, it falls down or inwards, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "centre around",
        "options": [
            "harass, bully (in a group)",
            "to be defeated by someone in a competition, ...",
            "if something centres around a place, or if you centre something around it, it happens mainly there, ...",
            "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything"
        ],
        "answer": "if something centres around a place, or if you centre something around it, it happens mainly there, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chalk out",
        "options": [
            "to cut a line of cocaine",
            "to explain to someone in detail how something should be done, what something is about etc",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "remove clothing to a certain level"
        ],
        "answer": "to cut a line of cocaine"
    },
    {
        "question": "chalk up",
        "options": [
            "to make a vehicle stop by waving your arm or hand at the driver",
            "to achieve a particular level or number, ...",
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it"
        ],
        "answer": "to achieve a particular level or number, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chalk up to",
        "options": [
            "to not use the usual way of doing something",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ...",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "explain the reason for a problem"
        ],
        "answer": "explain the reason for a problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "chance on",
        "options": [
            "to gradually become weaker or to disappear",
            "if you put something down to a particular reason, you think it has happened for that reason, ...",
            "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest"
        ],
        "answer": "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to"
    },
    {
        "question": "chance upon",
        "options": [
            "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to",
            "to spend time in a relaxed way when you have nothing else to do",
            "to do something quickly and easily",
            "to make something possible"
        ],
        "answer": "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to"
    },
    {
        "question": "change around",
        "options": [
            "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist",
            "to send a copy of a message or letter to someone",
            "to move things so that they are in different places or positions",
            "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move things so that they are in different places or positions"
    },
    {
        "question": "change back",
        "options": [
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ...",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "sleep on something other than a bed",
            "to send someone to a court of law because they have been accused of a crime"
        ],
        "answer": "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "change down",
        "options": [
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it",
            "to start driving in a lower gear",
            "to play a tune very loudly, especially on the piano",
            "same as build on"
        ],
        "answer": "to start driving in a lower gear"
    },
    {
        "question": "change into",
        "options": [
            "to work hard in order to find something",
            "move easily and quickly",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to stop being in one state, condition, or form and start being in another, or to make something do this, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop being in one state, condition, or form and start being in another, or to make something do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "change over",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else",
            "light a cigarette or joint",
            "to pretend that you have not noticed something or do not know about it, because you do not approve of it",
            "to relax"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "change up",
        "options": [
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to start driving in a higher gear",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ...",
            "same as hang"
        ],
        "answer": "to start driving in a higher gear"
    },
    {
        "question": "charge up",
        "options": [
            "same as charge",
            "add an additional point to something written or spoken",
            "same as spy, ...",
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it"
        ],
        "answer": "same as charge"
    },
    {
        "question": "charge with",
        "options": [
            "same as set against, ...",
            "accuse somebody of a crime",
            "to sell something quickly and for a low price, usually because you need money",
            "vomit"
        ],
        "answer": "accuse somebody of a crime"
    },
    {
        "question": "chase away",
        "options": [
            "to have a particular cause or origin",
            "to clean the inside of something thoroughly",
            "to get rid of something unpleasant",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of something unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "chase down",
        "options": [
            "to try hard to catch someone or to get something that you need",
            "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized",
            "same as beat up",
            "same as block"
        ],
        "answer": "to try hard to catch someone or to get something that you need"
    },
    {
        "question": "chase off",
        "options": [
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ...",
            "to cough loudly, ...",
            "force a person to leave or go away"
        ],
        "answer": "force a person to leave or go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "chase up",
        "options": [
            "to find out what is being done about something, ...",
            "to admit that you have done something bad or embarrassing",
            "to press a cigarette hard against a surface to make it stop burning",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
        ],
        "answer": "to find out what is being done about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chat away",
        "options": [
            "to avoid mentioning something, ...",
            "if two people who ended their sexual or romantic relationship get back together, they start having a relationship with each other again",
            "to manage to remember something that you learned or knew long ago, ...",
            "same as chat"
        ],
        "answer": "same as chat"
    },
    {
        "question": "chat up",
        "options": [
            "same as spit, ...",
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them",
            "if the rain beats down, it rains very hard, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "cheat on",
        "options": [
            "to say that someone is responsible for something bad",
            "to cheat by not obeying the rules on something, ...",
            "to spend a lot of money on something",
            "withdraw from company"
        ],
        "answer": "to cheat by not obeying the rules on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cheat out of",
        "options": [
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ...",
            "intend, plan",
            "get money from someone under false pretences",
            "to improve, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "get money from someone under false pretences"
    },
    {
        "question": "check against",
        "options": [
            "to find out whether information is accurate or useful by comparing it with other information",
            "scold, tell off, nag",
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ...",
            "to gradually start using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to find out whether information is accurate or useful by comparing it with other information"
    },
    {
        "question": "check by",
        "options": [
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "visit a place to check something",
            "to waste time in silly or useless activities, ...",
            "spend time doing very little or being unproductive"
        ],
        "answer": "visit a place to check something"
    },
    {
        "question": "check in",
        "options": [
            "to quickly produce something such as a meal using whatever is available",
            "same as check, ...",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to become partners, or to make people become partners"
        ],
        "answer": "same as check, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "check into",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out more information about a particular subject, ...",
            "increase",
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil",
            "to manage to say something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out more information about a particular subject, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "check off",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel strange",
            "to tick off something",
            "to make something more lively, exciting, or interesting",
            "eat something"
        ],
        "answer": "to tick off something"
    },
    {
        "question": "check on",
        "options": [
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it",
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "check out",
        "options": [
            "to officially agree to something",
            "same as drop",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "to phone from one part of a building to another"
        ],
        "answer": "to borrow a book from a library, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "check out of",
        "options": [
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "if animals feed off something, they eat it, ...",
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to borrow a book from a library, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "check over",
        "options": [
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "to have only a few things left to use or deal with, ...",
            "same as check, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as check, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "check up",
        "options": [
            "same as put, ...",
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "include someone or something in a group, category, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to make certain about something by checking it"
    },
    {
        "question": "check up on",
        "options": [
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it",
            "to say goodbye to someone by waving as they leave",
            "to find out information about someone, especially secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "to find out information about someone, especially secretly"
    },
    {
        "question": "cheer on",
        "options": [
            "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise",
            "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "cheer up",
        "options": [
            "to reduce an amount of money by using it",
            "to start to deal with a new subject in a discussion, ...",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "used for telling someone to try to be happier, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to try to be happier, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chew off",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to heat food until it is warm in all parts",
            "remove by biting",
            "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "remove by biting"
    },
    {
        "question": "chew on",
        "options": [
            "to return something that is not satisfactory",
            "to think about something carefully for a long time, before making a decision about it",
            "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ...",
            "to give something to a person in authority, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to think about something carefully for a long time, before making a decision about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "chew out",
        "options": [
            "to move so that you are behind someone or something, ...",
            "to speak angrily to someone because they have done something wrong",
            "to pay no attention to something, ...",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility"
        ],
        "answer": "to speak angrily to someone because they have done something wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "chew over",
        "options": [
            "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation",
            "find an answer to a problem",
            "to think about something carefully or discuss it carefully with other people before making a decision about it",
            "to build an extra part onto a building"
        ],
        "answer": "to think about something carefully or discuss it carefully with other people before making a decision about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "chew up",
        "options": [
            "to measure a particular length, width, height etc, often at a point where something is to be cut",
            "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people",
            "if you fix someone with your eyes, you look directly in their eyes so that they feel they cannot turn away",
            "if something gets chewed up, it becomes torn apart and destroyed, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something gets chewed up, it becomes torn apart and destroyed, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chicken out",
        "options": [
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself",
            "to want something very much",
            "to clock off, ...",
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened"
        ],
        "answer": "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened"
    },
    {
        "question": "chill out",
        "options": [
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to",
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place",
            "same as chill"
        ],
        "answer": "same as chill"
    },
    {
        "question": "chime in",
        "options": [
            "to enclose someone or something and prevent them from moving or leaving, ...",
            "to join a conversation by saying something",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ...",
            "same as flip"
        ],
        "answer": "to join a conversation by saying something"
    },
    {
        "question": "chime with",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to have an ordinary job or life because you do not want to be part of society, ...",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ...",
            "to give all your attention to something",
            "to be similar to or agree with someone else\u2019s ideas, plans, feelings etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to be similar to or agree with someone else\u2019s ideas, plans, feelings etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "chip away",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something even though it is difficult or unpleasant",
            "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ...",
            "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it",
            "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chip away at",
        "options": [
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ...",
            "to fall asleep, ...",
            "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chip in",
        "options": [
            "to add more details about something in order to make it easier to understand or imagine",
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ...",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "to add something to someone else\u2019s conversation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to add something to someone else\u2019s conversation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chip off",
        "options": [
            "put something in a place without taking care",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it"
    },
    {
        "question": "choke back",
        "options": [
            "to stop yourself from showing a feeling or emotion",
            "to build a new room or part onto the outside of a building, ...",
            "clear a table in a restaurant",
            "to do something very quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop yourself from showing a feeling or emotion"
    },
    {
        "question": "choke down",
        "options": [
            "invite",
            "talk fast or incomprehensibly",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting",
            "same as choke, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as choke, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "choke off",
        "options": [
            "same as choke",
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "same as camp, ...",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as choke"
    },
    {
        "question": "choke out",
        "options": [
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil",
            "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem",
            "clog or overwhelm",
            "be as good as something"
        ],
        "answer": "clog or overwhelm"
    },
    {
        "question": "choke up",
        "options": [
            "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them",
            "be good enough, ...",
            "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ...",
            "same as choke, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as choke, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "choose up",
        "options": [
            "same as spread, ...",
            "to be responsible for something, ...",
            "form groups or teams",
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "form groups or teams"
    },
    {
        "question": "chop down",
        "options": [
            "same as warm, ...",
            "if two or more things go together, they frequently exist together, ...",
            "to make a tree or tall plant fall down by cutting through it, ...",
            "to lead someone around a place for the first time, so that they can see all parts of it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a tree or tall plant fall down by cutting through it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chop off",
        "options": [
            "to remove something by cutting, especially a part of someone\u2019s body",
            "same as press, ...",
            "to try to find something by looking everywhere, even in places that you would prefer not to look in",
            "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something by cutting, especially a part of someone\u2019s body"
    },
    {
        "question": "chop up",
        "options": [
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ...",
            "same as chop",
            "visit someone for a short time."
        ],
        "answer": "same as chop"
    },
    {
        "question": "chow down",
        "options": [
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "if something dawns on you, you realize it for the first time",
            "to eat food, especially a lot of food, quickly or in an enthusiastic way"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat food, especially a lot of food, quickly or in an enthusiastic way"
    },
    {
        "question": "chow down on",
        "options": [
            "eat something",
            "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "eat something"
    },
    {
        "question": "chuck away",
        "options": [
            "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)",
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "same as heave"
        ],
        "answer": "same as chuck, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chuck in",
        "options": [
            "if something dries out or is dried out, some or all the water comes out of it, ...",
            "to agree to be responsible for something, ...",
            "to reach the time when something should happen",
            "to leave or give up something"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave or give up something"
    },
    {
        "question": "chuck out",
        "options": [
            "if a storm blows over, it ends, ...",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "consume"
        ],
        "answer": "same as chuck, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "chuck up",
        "options": [
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "to be used to help to pay for something",
            "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen",
            "to vomit food from your stomach out of your mouth"
        ],
        "answer": "to vomit food from your stomach out of your mouth"
    },
    {
        "question": "churn out",
        "options": [
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly",
            "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ...",
            "to produce something in large quantities quickly and often carelessly",
            "to be similar to something from the past, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something in large quantities quickly and often carelessly"
    },
    {
        "question": "churn up",
        "options": [
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "harass, bully (in a group)",
            "same as churn, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as churn, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clag up",
        "options": [
            "make something sticky",
            "to make a person or animal fatter",
            "if you dine out on an event or experience, people invite you to meals so that you can tell them about it",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered"
        ],
        "answer": "make something sticky"
    },
    {
        "question": "claim back",
        "options": [
            "same as get on, ...",
            "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it",
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "clam up",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly stop talking or explaining something, because you are embarrassed, unhappy, or want to keep a secret",
            "to make a car go backwards, ...",
            "to be opposed to something, ...",
            "to become ill with a particular illness"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly stop talking or explaining something, because you are embarrassed, unhappy, or want to keep a secret"
    },
    {
        "question": "clamp down",
        "options": [
            "to think of a new idea or plan, especially one that is silly or unusual",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "if air or smoke puffs out, or if you puff it out, you blow it out with a short breath, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal"
    },
    {
        "question": "clamp down on",
        "options": [
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to refuse to accept or listen to something that someone says",
            "to succeed in winning or gaining something from an opponent, ...",
            "to produce things in large numbers without caring much about their quality"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal"
    },
    {
        "question": "clap in",
        "options": [
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening",
            "to suddenly put someone somewhere that they cannot escape from",
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly put someone somewhere that they cannot escape from"
    },
    {
        "question": "clap out",
        "options": [
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry",
            "same as linger, ...",
            "to spend time relaxing or doing nothing when you should be doing something",
            "to decide not to do something because you are too tired"
        ],
        "answer": "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry"
    },
    {
        "question": "claw back",
        "options": [
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way",
            "to get something again that you had lost such as power, especially gradually and with difficulty, ...",
            "to progress at a very slow steady rate",
            "same as balance"
        ],
        "answer": "to get something again that you had lost such as power, especially gradually and with difficulty, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clean down",
        "options": [
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ...",
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "to remove the dirt from something, especially from an upright surface",
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove the dirt from something, especially from an upright surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "clean off",
        "options": [
            "to hold something so that someone else can reach it or see it, ...",
            "to make a noise, ...",
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "same as cool, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "remove dirt or something dirty"
    },
    {
        "question": "clean out",
        "options": [
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer",
            "to remove things from a group, ...",
            "treat someone badly, ...",
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clean up",
        "options": [
            "to make a lot of money, ...",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "argue with someone about a specific subject",
            "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a lot of money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clean up after",
        "options": [
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to start to win or increase quickly and easily",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy"
    },
    {
        "question": "clear away",
        "options": [
            "to remove something that you have finished using or no longer want in order to make a place tidy",
            "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly",
            "same as chill",
            "if one thing shades into another thing, it is difficult to know where one ends and the other begins"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something that you have finished using or no longer want in order to make a place tidy"
    },
    {
        "question": "clear off",
        "options": [
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination",
            "to force a group of soldiers to stay in one place, ...",
            "used for getting the attention of a noisy group of people",
            "to leave a place quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clear out",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place quickly and often permanently, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "to work hard in order to find something",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place quickly and often permanently, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clear up",
        "options": [
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "use correction fluid to cover a mistake in a written text",
            "to do what you have promised or decided, ...",
            "break a piece off something"
        ],
        "answer": "to solve a problem or a mystery, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clear up after",
        "options": [
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "to start crying, especially in public, ...",
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "to make a place tidy after someone else has made it untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a place tidy after someone else has made it untidy"
    },
    {
        "question": "cleave to",
        "options": [
            "to stick firmly to something, ...",
            "same as tuck in",
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ...",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth"
        ],
        "answer": "to stick firmly to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "click through",
        "options": [
            "make a decision by throwing a coin and seeing which side lands face up",
            "to happen, ...",
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "open an advertisement on the internet"
    },
    {
        "question": "climb down",
        "options": [
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked",
            "to admit that you were wrong, especially after expressing an opinion or argument very firmly",
            "same as broaden",
            "same as lighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to admit that you were wrong, especially after expressing an opinion or argument very firmly"
    },
    {
        "question": "cling on",
        "options": [
            "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more",
            "to try to avoid dealing with a difficult or unpleasant situation, ...",
            "to press hard into something, ...",
            "hold tight"
        ],
        "answer": "hold tight"
    },
    {
        "question": "cling on to",
        "options": [
            "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something",
            "try to keep something",
            "to start being brave and dealing with a difficult situation",
            "same as show, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "try to keep something"
    },
    {
        "question": "cling to",
        "options": [
            "to chase someone or something, ...",
            "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ...",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "try to maintain beliefs, hopes, etc."
        ],
        "answer": "try to maintain beliefs, hopes, etc."
    },
    {
        "question": "clock in",
        "options": [
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you have arrived at work",
            "make a hand signal to tell someone to keep moving",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to stay at home"
        ],
        "answer": "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you have arrived at work"
    },
    {
        "question": "clock in at",
        "options": [
            "to persuade someone to agree with you, ...",
            "same as tidy, ...",
            "to take a particular amount of time, or to last for a particular amount of time",
            "a phrase that was used a greeting"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a particular amount of time, or to last for a particular amount of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "clock off",
        "options": [
            "to start a new activity, ...",
            "to be very happy about something, ...",
            "to admit something, ...",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work"
        ],
        "answer": "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work"
    },
    {
        "question": "clock up",
        "options": [
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you",
            "to reach a particular number or amount",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to criticize or punish someone severely"
        ],
        "answer": "to reach a particular number or amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "clog up",
        "options": [
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "same as gobble",
            "to be an aspect of a situation, ...",
            "block, slow movement right down"
        ],
        "answer": "block, slow movement right down"
    },
    {
        "question": "close down",
        "options": [
            "same as close, ...",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ...",
            "have negative feelings toward someone",
            "leave a place in a hurry"
        ],
        "answer": "same as close, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "close in",
        "options": [
            "vomit",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "same as mark out, ...",
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "close in on",
        "options": [
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ...",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "same as slow, ...",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data"
        ],
        "answer": "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "close in upon",
        "options": [
            "get near someone",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties",
            "to try to find out information about someone or something",
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "get near someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "close off",
        "options": [
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc",
            "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom",
            "used for warning someone to be careful, especially because they are likely to have an accident",
            "to get rid of an unpleasant or uncomfortable feeling by sleeping, especially after eating or drinking too much"
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "close on",
        "options": [
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "ignore, exclude, ...",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry",
            "not turn off"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "close out",
        "options": [
            "consider, regard",
            "ignore, exclude, ...",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ...",
            "focus more closely"
        ],
        "answer": "ignore, exclude, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "close up",
        "options": [
            "to expect something to happen",
            "to do the same activity for a very long time",
            "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ...",
            "same as close, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as close, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cloud over",
        "options": [
            "to expect something to happen",
            "same as cloud, ...",
            "pursue, be aware of someone's true nature",
            "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people"
        ],
        "answer": "same as cloud, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "clown about",
        "options": [
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to raise a flag to the top of a pole, ...",
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "approach someone discreetly"
        ],
        "answer": "behave stupidly or waste time"
    },
    {
        "question": "clown around",
        "options": [
            "move quickly",
            "to do something without being very serious about it, ...",
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to take the place of someone temporarily"
        ],
        "answer": "behave stupidly or waste time"
    },
    {
        "question": "club together",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else",
            "eat or drink slowly",
            "get the energy or courage to do something",
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something"
        ],
        "answer": "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something"
    },
    {
        "question": "clump together",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to search through a collection of things in order to find something",
            "to form a solid mass, ...",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
        ],
        "answer": "to form a solid mass, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "coast along",
        "options": [
            "do something without making much effort or trying to improve",
            "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ...",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station.",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private"
        ],
        "answer": "do something without making much effort or trying to improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "cobble together",
        "options": [
            "praise someone in an excessive way to get their favour or something from them",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
    },
    {
        "question": "cock up",
        "options": [
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to be based on something",
            "to spoil something by doing it wrongly",
            "to stop asking for something, or to stop saying that you will do something, because a lot of people oppose you"
        ],
        "answer": "to spoil something by doing it wrongly"
    },
    {
        "question": "collect up",
        "options": [
            "to get things from different places or people after people have finished with them",
            "to put something around something else",
            "used for asking someone to repeat what they have just said, ...",
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document"
        ],
        "answer": "to get things from different places or people after people have finished with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "colour (color) up",
        "options": [
            "blush",
            "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ...",
            "to live at the place where you work or study",
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "blush"
    },
    {
        "question": "colour up",
        "options": [
            "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ...",
            "to move somewhere while buzzing, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something",
            "if you colour up, your face becomes red"
        ],
        "answer": "if you colour up, your face becomes red"
    },
    {
        "question": "comb out",
        "options": [
            "to use a comb to make your hair smooth or straight",
            "if a vehicle moves off, it starts to move",
            "to stop paying attention",
            "same as tangle"
        ],
        "answer": "to use a comb to make your hair smooth or straight"
    },
    {
        "question": "comb through",
        "options": [
            "to search carefully among things",
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious",
            "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous",
            "to not accept an offer because you want a better one"
        ],
        "answer": "to search carefully among things"
    },
    {
        "question": "come about",
        "options": [
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair",
            "to happen, especially by chance, ...",
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want",
            "to begin a case against someone in a court of law"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, especially by chance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come across",
        "options": [
            "be upset",
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ...",
            "to arrange for something to happen or for someone to do something, knowing that it may have to be changed later",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come across with",
        "options": [
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ...",
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something",
            "to provide something that is needed or wanted"
        ],
        "answer": "to provide something that is needed or wanted"
    },
    {
        "question": "come after",
        "options": [
            "remove quickly",
            "to try to find or catch someone, usually in order to punish or harm them",
            "to murder someone",
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find or catch someone, usually in order to punish or harm them"
    },
    {
        "question": "come along",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere with someone, ...",
            "to not do something because you do not feel brave enough",
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it",
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come apart",
        "options": [
            "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ...",
            "to fail completely, or to come to an end, ...",
            "same as rise",
            "go somewhere away from people to study or work"
        ],
        "answer": "to fail completely, or to come to an end, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come around",
        "options": [
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to always enjoy something, ...",
            "to continue to be enough or continue to exist, ...",
            "same as come"
        ],
        "answer": "same as come"
    },
    {
        "question": "come around to",
        "options": [
            "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked.",
            "to suddenly leave your wife, husband, or partner",
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ...",
            "to be lucky"
        ],
        "answer": "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked."
    },
    {
        "question": "come at",
        "options": [
            "be funny, or try to",
            "to invite someone to your house, for example for a meal",
            "same as lead to",
            "to examine or deal with something such as a problem in a particular way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to examine or deal with something such as a problem in a particular way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come away",
        "options": [
            "same as piss",
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ...",
            "to move away from someone or something, ...",
            "to start discussing a subject, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move away from someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come back",
        "options": [
            "pay attention after not doing so",
            "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ...",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to return to a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to return to a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come back to",
        "options": [
            "to become mentally ill, ...",
            "rob someone at gunpoint, ...",
            "to deal again with something that you were dealing with earlier",
            "to be as good as what was expected or promised"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal again with something that you were dealing with earlier"
    },
    {
        "question": "come before",
        "options": [
            "to be more important than someone or something else, ...",
            "to say that someone or something is an example of something, usually something good",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "argue with someone about a specific subject"
        ],
        "answer": "to be more important than someone or something else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come between",
        "options": [
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ...",
            "to write to an organization asking for something, ...",
            "a phrase that was used a greeting",
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come by",
        "options": [
            "to make a place tidy after someone else has made it untidy",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move",
            "to use a hose to clean something",
            "to get something, especially something that is hard to get"
        ],
        "answer": "to get something, especially something that is hard to get"
    },
    {
        "question": "come down",
        "options": [
            "to agree to ask for or pay a lower price, ...",
            "to start a journey, ...",
            "if a market or price bounces back, it rises again after falling, ...",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree to ask for or pay a lower price, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come down on",
        "options": [
            "to do something without being very serious about it, ...",
            "to criticize or punish someone severely",
            "be bored, upset or sick of something",
            "to make a car go backwards, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize or punish someone severely"
    },
    {
        "question": "come down to",
        "options": [
            "same as save",
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you",
            "return somewhere",
            "to be the most important aspect of a situation or problem, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be the most important aspect of a situation or problem, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come down upon",
        "options": [
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "to make something simpler and easier to understand in a way that reduces its quality",
            "to be based on or planned around a particular idea or event",
            "criticise, reprimand severely"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise, reprimand severely"
    },
    {
        "question": "come down with",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone a question, ...",
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "same as cough, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious"
    },
    {
        "question": "come for",
        "options": [
            "to increase and become more obvious",
            "same as come at, ...",
            "to not go to bed",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people"
        ],
        "answer": "same as come at, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come forth",
        "options": [
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult",
            "appear",
            "to waste time when you should be working"
        ],
        "answer": "appear"
    },
    {
        "question": "come forth with",
        "options": [
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "provide information",
            "to shout something",
            "to divide something among people so that each one gets a small amount"
        ],
        "answer": "provide information"
    },
    {
        "question": "come forward",
        "options": [
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "need or want something",
            "if someone\u2019s voice or words trail away or trail off, they gradually become silent",
            "to offer help or information"
        ],
        "answer": "to offer help or information"
    },
    {
        "question": "come from",
        "options": [
            "be ill",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ...",
            "to do a particular piece of work, research etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be the result of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come in",
        "options": [
            "if a situation descends into a certain bad state, it becomes bad",
            "to go to work, ...",
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ...",
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to work, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come in at",
        "options": [
            "to do something after you have intended to do it for some time",
            "to leave somewhere, ...",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "to cost a particular amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to cost a particular amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "come in for",
        "options": [
            "same as bowl, ...",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist"
        ],
        "answer": "to receive something such as criticism"
    },
    {
        "question": "come into",
        "options": [
            "to be an aspect of a situation, ...",
            "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "to make something explode, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be an aspect of a situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come into use",
        "options": [
            "start being used",
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "to reduce an amount, ...",
            "same as file"
        ],
        "answer": "start being used"
    },
    {
        "question": "come of",
        "options": [
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ...",
            "to increase the speed of a vehicle by increasing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "to realize or understand something",
            "to be the result of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be the result of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "come off",
        "options": [
            "to allow someone bail when they are waiting to appear in court, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to use or do something else after other things have failed",
            "to clean the dirt or dust from a carpet or floor with a vacuum cleaner"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come off it",
        "options": [
            "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ...",
            "to put things together without any order, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "if you fling clothes on, you put them on quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come on",
        "options": [
            "to escape from prison, ...",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry",
            "to improve, ...",
            "exploit, use to your advantage"
        ],
        "answer": "to improve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come on to",
        "options": [
            "to start to deal with a new subject in a discussion, ...",
            "same as sift",
            "if a plant dies back, the part above the ground dies but the roots stay alive",
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to deal with a new subject in a discussion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come out",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of something",
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something",
            "to be easy to notice, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be easy to notice, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come out in",
        "options": [
            "same as hang, ...",
            "entertain someone in your home",
            "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine",
            "express or display emotions openly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine"
    },
    {
        "question": "come out of",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the price of something, ...",
            "to continue to support someone who is in a difficult situation, ...",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing"
        ],
        "answer": "to be the result of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come out with",
        "options": [
            "to emphasize something",
            "to inform someone about something, ...",
            "introduce a new product; launch, ...",
            "to be built, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "introduce a new product; launch, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come over",
        "options": [
            "to do something bad or unpleasant to someone",
            "same as tease, ...",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "same as head"
        ],
        "answer": "same as come across, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come over to",
        "options": [
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to change your position or opinion and start supporting someone you were arguing or fighting with"
        ],
        "answer": "to change your position or opinion and start supporting someone you were arguing or fighting with"
    },
    {
        "question": "come round",
        "options": [
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things",
            "to be dressed in a particular way, ...",
            "if a regular event comes round, it happens again, ...",
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "if a regular event comes round, it happens again, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come through",
        "options": [
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ...",
            "to combine different things so that they form a single unit, ...",
            "change topic or subject",
            "to do something that you have agreed or promised to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something that you have agreed or promised to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come through with",
        "options": [
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "keep quiet, say nothing",
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ...",
            "provide something needed"
        ],
        "answer": "provide something needed"
    },
    {
        "question": "come to",
        "options": [
            "to make someone leave a job or position so that you or someone else can take their place",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)",
            "same as come on to, ...",
            "to leave a place, usually suddenly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as come on to, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come together",
        "options": [
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ...",
            "same as heap",
            "to begin working on something or dealing with something, ...",
            "to gradually become less involved in something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come under",
        "options": [
            "to finish drinking something",
            "to attempt to get or achieve something difficult or something that you want very much",
            "to belong to a particular group or class, ...",
            "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to"
        ],
        "answer": "to belong to a particular group or class, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come up",
        "options": [
            "to stay in bed in the morning for longer than usual",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions",
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be about to happen soon, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come up against",
        "options": [
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is less expensive",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "take responsibility, often without consulting other people"
        ],
        "answer": "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "come up for",
        "options": [
            "to gradually reduce the amount or importance of something",
            "to reach the time when something should happen",
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them",
            "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reach the time when something should happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "come up to",
        "options": [
            "to become completely understood",
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to push or press downwards, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come up with",
        "options": [
            "retire, quit",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ...",
            "same as set against, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come upon",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ...",
            "leave a place angrily",
            "to attract very large audiences, ...",
            "to make something less severe, shocking, or offensive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "come with",
        "options": [
            "leave",
            "to start to play or sing a piece of music, ...",
            "to be provided together with something, ...",
            "to visit a place for a short time on your way to another place"
        ],
        "answer": "to be provided together with something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "complain of",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something for success",
            "to turn the pages of a book, magazine, newspaper etc very quickly looking at some of the pages for a very short time, ...",
            "to decide not to take part in something or to stop taking part in it",
            "to say that something bad has happened, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say that something bad has happened, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cone off",
        "options": [
            "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm",
            "to put traffic cones across a road in order to prevent traffic from going along the road",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "same as lift"
        ],
        "answer": "to put traffic cones across a road in order to prevent traffic from going along the road"
    },
    {
        "question": "conjure up",
        "options": [
            "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc.",
            "leave something you don't like",
            "to make something appear using magic powers, ...",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something appear using magic powers, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "conk out",
        "options": [
            "sleep somewhere for the night",
            "to suddenly stop working, ...",
            "to depend on someone, ...",
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly stop working, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "connect up",
        "options": [
            "to get ready to play a game such as tennis by hitting the ball over the net",
            "to tie the ends of something together, ...",
            "same as connect, ...",
            "to include someone in your plans"
        ],
        "answer": "same as connect, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "contend with",
        "options": [
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times",
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "contract in",
        "options": [
            "to think carefully about something over a period of time",
            "to increase something such as a rate or level, especially the rate at which goods are produced",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "contract out",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ...",
            "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "to put on clothes, especially quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "contract out of",
        "options": [
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "same as goof",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "talk too much"
        ],
        "answer": "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cook up",
        "options": [
            "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose",
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly",
            "to invent a story, excuse, or plan",
            "not gain or have something advantageous"
        ],
        "answer": "to invent a story, excuse, or plan"
    },
    {
        "question": "cool down",
        "options": [
            "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist",
            "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to discover something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as cool, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cool off",
        "options": [
            "to make a photograph bigger, ...",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to become calm again, ...",
            "waste time"
        ],
        "answer": "to become calm again, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "coop up",
        "options": [
            "if a person or animal is cooped up in a place, they have to stay there without being able to move around much",
            "used for telling children to go away",
            "to give something to someone although you would prefer to keep it",
            "to deal with something or someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a person or animal is cooped up in a place, they have to stay there without being able to move around much"
    },
    {
        "question": "cop it",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something",
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "get into trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "get into trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "cop off",
        "options": [
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "make someone feel worried or uneasy",
            "make a quick note",
            "to meet someone and start a sexual relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to meet someone and start a sexual relationship with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "cop out",
        "options": [
            "to try on clothes to see if they fit, ...",
            "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult",
            "to get ready for an activity by putting on a uniform or special clothes",
            "persuade someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "copy down",
        "options": [
            "to examine or read something very carefully and in a lot of detail",
            "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ...",
            "to make someone or something more active and lively",
            "to write exactly what someone has written or said"
        ],
        "answer": "to write exactly what someone has written or said"
    },
    {
        "question": "copy in",
        "options": [
            "to count things one by one, ...",
            "to add something to something else to make it bigger or more satisfactory",
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure",
            "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person"
    },
    {
        "question": "copy out",
        "options": [
            "to write something again exactly as it has been written",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ...",
            "same as chop",
            "to not choose someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to write something again exactly as it has been written"
    },
    {
        "question": "copy to",
        "options": [
            "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime",
            "to send a copy of a message or letter to someone",
            "to gradually reduce the strength, value, or importance of something",
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to send a copy of a message or letter to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "cost up",
        "options": [
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need",
            "have a part in a project, activity, etc",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "calculate how expensive some work is going to be"
        ],
        "answer": "calculate how expensive some work is going to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "cotton on",
        "options": [
            "to begin to realize or understand something",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "if you sign for a sports club, you join it by signing a contract, ...",
            "to copy someone or something\u2019s style"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to realize or understand something"
    },
    {
        "question": "cough up",
        "options": [
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something",
            "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something",
            "same as cough, ...",
            "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection"
        ],
        "answer": "same as cough, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "could do with",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone violently, ...",
            "need or want something",
            "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them",
            "to arrange for yourself or someone else to stay at a hotel, hospital etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "need or want something"
    },
    {
        "question": "count against",
        "options": [
            "fight or argue",
            "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to",
            "to have a formal discussion with someone in order to try to reach an agreement about something",
            "to be a disadvantage in a particular situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to be a disadvantage in a particular situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "count among",
        "options": [
            "include someone or something in a group, category, etc",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "to continue to talk about something unpleasant that someone else no longer wants to talk or think about"
        ],
        "answer": "include someone or something in a group, category, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "count down",
        "options": [
            "to look or behave like an older relative",
            "same as get",
            "to lead someone around a place in order to show them how interesting or attractive it is",
            "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens"
        ],
        "answer": "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens"
    },
    {
        "question": "count for",
        "options": [
            "to have something as a very important part or purpose, ...",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen",
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ...",
            "be recognised as important, worthwhile or valuable"
        ],
        "answer": "be recognised as important, worthwhile or valuable"
    },
    {
        "question": "count in",
        "options": [
            "to include someone in your plans",
            "to officially agree to something",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug",
            "same as lap, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to include someone in your plans"
    },
    {
        "question": "count off",
        "options": [
            "marry someone of a different ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "to focus on being an effective manager for the people you are responsible for in an organization, more than on satisfying the people who are above you",
            "say numbers aloud in a sequence",
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc"
        ],
        "answer": "say numbers aloud in a sequence"
    },
    {
        "question": "count on",
        "options": [
            "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ...",
            "to clearly need something a lot",
            "take responsibility, often without consulting other people",
            "to lose weight, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "count out",
        "options": [
            "collapse, break, ...",
            "to use all of something and not have any left, ...",
            "to count things one by one, ...",
            "to phone someone again, or to phone someone who phoned you earlier when you were away or were too busy to speak to them"
        ],
        "answer": "to count things one by one, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "count towards",
        "options": [
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly",
            "to be important, or to have influence, ...",
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like"
        ],
        "answer": "to be important, or to have influence, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "count up",
        "options": [
            "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening",
            "clock in, ...",
            "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling",
            "to count all the things or people in a group"
        ],
        "answer": "to count all the things or people in a group"
    },
    {
        "question": "count upon",
        "options": [
            "same as flare",
            "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ...",
            "to not include someone or something, ...",
            "to take control of a smaller company or country, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "count with",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something or someone",
            "force a person to leave or go away",
            "if time drags by, it seems to pass very slowly",
            "to attract very large audiences, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on something or someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "cover for",
        "options": [
            "to avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to do someone\u2019s work while they are away or ill, ...",
            "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ...",
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times"
        ],
        "answer": "to do someone\u2019s work while they are away or ill, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cover up",
        "options": [
            "same as cover, ...",
            "to find and arrest people, ...",
            "same as pen",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as cover, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cozy up",
        "options": [
            "to gradually start to talk or write about a particular subject in a conversation or piece of writing, especially because it is embarrassing",
            "to stop for a moment in order to consider something",
            "look in different places for something",
            "make yourself comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "make yourself comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "cozy up to",
        "options": [
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "make yourself popular with someone",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "make a quick note"
        ],
        "answer": "make yourself popular with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "crack down",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly"
    },
    {
        "question": "crack down on",
        "options": [
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ...",
            "to give things to different people in a group, ...",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen",
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly"
        ],
        "answer": "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly"
    },
    {
        "question": "crack on",
        "options": [
            "to force someone into an unpleasant state or situation, ...",
            "to have something as the final part, ...",
            "to continue doing something as quickly as possible",
            "to send someone somewhere, usually when they do not want to go"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something as quickly as possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "crack onto",
        "options": [
            "to try to start a conversation with someone because you are sexually attracted to them",
            "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to start a conversation with someone because you are sexually attracted to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "crack up",
        "options": [
            "if a vehicle draws up, it arrives at a place and stops, ...",
            "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ...",
            "behave in a silly way",
            "to become mentally ill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become mentally ill, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cram in",
        "options": [
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to start laughing, or to make someone laugh a lot",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to do a lot of activities in a short time"
        ],
        "answer": "to do a lot of activities in a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "crank out",
        "options": [
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened",
            "to do something in a very short period of time, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to produce things in large numbers without caring much about their quality"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce things in large numbers without caring much about their quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "crank up",
        "options": [
            "to increase the level or degree of something",
            "to steal something, ...",
            "if a storm blows over, it ends, ...",
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase the level or degree of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "crap on",
        "options": [
            "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult",
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "to stay at home",
            "to talk continuously in an annoying or boring way"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk continuously in an annoying or boring way"
    },
    {
        "question": "crash around",
        "options": [
            "to turn the pages of a book, magazine, newspaper etc very quickly looking at some of the pages for a very short time, ...",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to not use the usual way of doing something",
            "to make certain about something by checking it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "crash out",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly start sleeping, usually when you are very tired, ...",
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "sell something in an auction",
            "to dress or behave in public in a particular way, especially when this makes you look or seem silly"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly start sleeping, usually when you are very tired, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "crawl with",
        "options": [
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to be covered in insects, ...",
            "to add something to someone else\u2019s conversation, ...",
            "to cough loudly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be covered in insects, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cream off",
        "options": [
            "to take a lot of money or profit, especially an unfair amount, in a business deal, ...",
            "to be caused by something",
            "think about something",
            "to try to find something by looking everywhere, even in places that you would prefer not to look in"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a lot of money or profit, especially an unfair amount, in a business deal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "crease up",
        "options": [
            "end or close because of a time limit, ...",
            "to make someone think something, ...",
            "same as get along, ...",
            "to start laughing, or to make someone laugh a lot"
        ],
        "answer": "to start laughing, or to make someone laugh a lot"
    },
    {
        "question": "credit to",
        "options": [
            "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to discuss something with someone in order to get their opinion and make a decision, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "credit with",
        "options": [
            "to say or believe that someone has a particular quality, ...",
            "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement",
            "do something without making much effort or trying to improve",
            "to have happened previously, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say or believe that someone has a particular quality, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "creep by",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ...",
            "if time creeps by, it passes very slowly",
            "to use an event or a situation to help you to achieve something or to get an advantage"
        ],
        "answer": "if time creeps by, it passes very slowly"
    },
    {
        "question": "creep in",
        "options": [
            "break something with your feet",
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to try to deal with or solve a difficult problem"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually start to affect or change something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "creep into",
        "options": [
            "same as finish, ...",
            "to interrupt someone who is speaking, ...",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "retire, quit"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually start to affect or change something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "creep out",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ...",
            "to make a path through something by cutting, ...",
            "make someone feel worried or uneasy",
            "criticise"
        ],
        "answer": "make someone feel worried or uneasy"
    },
    {
        "question": "creep out on",
        "options": [
            "to not be willing to do something difficult, or to not deal with something unpleasant",
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "remove a character trait by controlling reproduction",
            "to do the same activity for a very long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to do the same activity for a very long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "creep over",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "start to have a negative feeling",
            "to receive news about someone, ...",
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress"
        ],
        "answer": "start to have a negative feeling"
    },
    {
        "question": "creep up",
        "options": [
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to stop a process from working smoothly, ...",
            "to gradually become larger in number or amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually become larger in number or amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "creep up on",
        "options": [
            "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "to think about what is likely to happen, or to plan what you are going to do in the future",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "crop up",
        "options": [
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ...",
            "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time",
            "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ...",
            "to not consider or include something in your plans and so not be prepared for it"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cross off",
        "options": [
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to move or happen faster, ...",
            "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it",
            "get the energy or courage to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it"
    },
    {
        "question": "cross out",
        "options": [
            "to stand in front of people who have been waiting longer than you, in a way that is unfair",
            "to agree with someone or something, ...",
            "to draw an X or a line through writing because it is wrong or because you have decided to write something else",
            "to put a person or animal in a place that they cannot leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to draw an X or a line through writing because it is wrong or because you have decided to write something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "cross over",
        "options": [
            "to win something easily, ...",
            "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ...",
            "force someone to leave",
            "to show the truth or importance of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cross up",
        "options": [
            "to deal with something easily and successfully, ...",
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc",
            "confuse, deceive",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "confuse, deceive"
    },
    {
        "question": "crowd in on",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "if a situation pans out in a particular way, it develops in that way",
            "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people",
            "if a group of people crowd in on someone, they move close to them and then surround them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a group of people crowd in on someone, they move close to them and then surround them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "crowd out",
        "options": [
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "cruise through",
        "options": [
            "join a teleconference",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "to leave a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized",
            "to try to find something"
        ],
        "answer": "pass or succeed easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "crumb down",
        "options": [
            "be upset",
            "clear a table in a restaurant",
            "get someone into trouble",
            "to make something such as an edge or corner straight"
        ],
        "answer": "clear a table in a restaurant"
    },
    {
        "question": "cry off",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "to waste time or money on things that are not necessary or important",
            "to start to win or increase quickly and easily",
            "to search for someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "cry out",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place by preventing them from getting enough food",
            "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "find a new enthusiasm for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cry out for",
        "options": [
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "to clearly need something a lot",
            "to continue doing something as quickly as possible",
            "calculate how expensive some work is going to be"
        ],
        "answer": "to clearly need something a lot"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuddle up",
        "options": [
            "to sit or lie with your body against someone else\u2019s because you want to feel warm, protected, or loved",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm",
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "to give something to each member of a group, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to sit or lie with your body against someone else\u2019s because you want to feel warm, protected, or loved"
    },
    {
        "question": "curl up",
        "options": [
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "same as curl, ...",
            "to cause problems for someone, ...",
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like"
        ],
        "answer": "same as curl, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cuss out",
        "options": [
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "to persuade someone to lower the price of something, ...",
            "same as throw away, ...",
            "to send many copies of a letter, advertisement etc by post at one time"
        ],
        "answer": "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "cut across",
        "options": [
            "to be completely certain of something",
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to physically attack someone",
            "to direct your thoughts or attention to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as cut, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut away",
        "options": [
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something",
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use",
            "same as lock away, ...",
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them"
    },
    {
        "question": "cut back",
        "options": [
            "same as cut down, ...",
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "to break because of being old or badly made, ...",
            "to gradually become weaker or to disappear"
        ],
        "answer": "same as cut down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut back on",
        "options": [
            "to make something better than it was before, or to do something better than you did before",
            "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')",
            "to make something flat, ...",
            "same as cut down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as cut down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut down",
        "options": [
            "to make something stop or disappear just by expressing a wish",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ...",
            "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with",
            "to raise a flag to the top of a pole, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut down on",
        "options": [
            "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it",
            "to join a conversation or activity without being asked to",
            "to have something as a very important part or purpose, ...",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut in",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone and start a sexual relationship with them",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to interrupt someone who is speaking, ...",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to interrupt someone who is speaking, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut into",
        "options": [
            "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people",
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ...",
            "to try to make people support you or buy something from you",
            "to find out information, especially something that someone does not want you to know"
        ],
        "answer": "to interrupt an activity or process, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut it out",
        "options": [
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ...",
            "to say that something bad has happened, ...",
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ...",
            "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour"
        ],
        "answer": "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour"
    },
    {
        "question": "cut off",
        "options": [
            "to remove all or most of your clothes, ...",
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as cut, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut out",
        "options": [
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "return somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "same as cut, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut out on",
        "options": [
            "let down, snub",
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to take a young plant that is growing in a container and put it in the ground to grow",
            "to succeed in persuading someone to agree to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "let down, snub"
    },
    {
        "question": "cut over",
        "options": [
            "depart furtively",
            "to move information or users of a computer system to a new place or to new equipment at the same time or in an order that causes as few problems as possible",
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation",
            "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to move information or users of a computer system to a new place or to new equipment at the same time or in an order that causes as few problems as possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "cut through",
        "options": [
            "a way of expressing disbelief, or telling someone that they're wrong or have an incorrect opinion",
            "to make a path through something by cutting, ...",
            "to avoid going to a place",
            "to score a goal when your team is losing in a football match, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a path through something by cutting, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "cut up",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere",
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ...",
            "to behave in a noisy silly way, ...",
            "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a noisy silly way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dab off",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from a surface by gently touching it several times with something such as a piece of cloth",
            "focus more closely",
            "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are",
            "to ask someone about someone else, especially about how they are or what they are doing"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something from a surface by gently touching it several times with something such as a piece of cloth"
    },
    {
        "question": "dally with",
        "options": [
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want",
            "to try to prevent something from happening, ...",
            "to have a short sexual relationship with someone, ...",
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it"
        ],
        "answer": "to have a short sexual relationship with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "damp down",
        "options": [
            "to make a person or animal fatter",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something",
            "make a fire burn less, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "make a fire burn less, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "damp off",
        "options": [
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ...",
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "to give a summary of something, ...",
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided"
        ],
        "answer": "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites"
    },
    {
        "question": "dash down",
        "options": [
            "write something quickly",
            "same as set against, ...",
            "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "write something quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "dash off",
        "options": [
            "muster, acquire, gather",
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "to leave quickly or suddenly because you are in a hurry, ...",
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave quickly or suddenly because you are in a hurry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "date back to",
        "options": [
            "same as buy, ...",
            "to not use the usual way of doing something",
            "to be made or begun at a particular time in the past",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off the surface of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be made or begun at a particular time in the past"
    },
    {
        "question": "date from",
        "options": [
            "to be made at a particular time in the past",
            "to point a weapon at someone, ...",
            "same as haul, ...",
            "to clearly need something a lot"
        ],
        "answer": "to be made at a particular time in the past"
    },
    {
        "question": "dawn on",
        "options": [
            "if something dawns on you, you realize it for the first time",
            "to promise to stop doing or using something",
            "to do gentle exercises that make your muscles stretch, especially in order to prepare for taking part in a sport",
            "to sit or lie with your body against someone else\u2019s because you want to feel warm, protected, or loved"
        ],
        "answer": "if something dawns on you, you realize it for the first time"
    },
    {
        "question": "deal in",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ...",
            "to buy and sell something, ...",
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to buy and sell something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "deal out",
        "options": [
            "to start a piece of knitting by making the first row of stitches",
            "if you hole up or are holed up somewhere, you stay there, especially because you are hiding",
            "same as deal, ...",
            "same as spread, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as deal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "deal with",
        "options": [
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "to start to sleep, especially during the day and without intending to",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do",
            "to be about a subject, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be about a subject, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "decide against",
        "options": [
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "to not choose someone or something",
            "to earn a particular amount of money, ...",
            "to wave at the driver of a car so that they stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to not choose someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "decide on",
        "options": [
            "if something sweeps you along, you become very involved in it because you are so excited about it",
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "to put a person or animal in a place that they cannot leave",
            "to choose someone or something from a number of possible choices"
        ],
        "answer": "to choose someone or something from a number of possible choices"
    },
    {
        "question": "decide upon",
        "options": [
            "choose, select",
            "to understand, ...",
            "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection",
            "to deal successfully with a problem or situation that is especially difficult, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "choose, select"
    },
    {
        "question": "deck out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone become very excited, ...",
            "to decorate a person or object with something, usually for a special occasion",
            "to spend time doing things in a relaxed way, ...",
            "to switch off a light, machine etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to decorate a person or object with something, usually for a special occasion"
    },
    {
        "question": "declare against",
        "options": [
            "to lead someone around a place for the first time, so that they can see all parts of it",
            "to relax, or to become less serious, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ...",
            "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "declare for",
        "options": [
            "to cover a hole or surface with plaster",
            "to say publicly that you support someone or something",
            "same as spit, ...",
            "help someone to start a piece or work or activity"
        ],
        "answer": "to say publicly that you support someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "defer to",
        "options": [
            "leave somebody angrily",
            "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them"
    },
    {
        "question": "delight in",
        "options": [
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ...",
            "to get a lot of pleasure or enjoyment from something",
            "to keep one area separate from another"
        ],
        "answer": "to get a lot of pleasure or enjoyment from something"
    },
    {
        "question": "deliver up",
        "options": [
            "to give something to someone officially and formally",
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ...",
            "to explain your opinion clearly and defend it in a determined way, ...",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something to someone officially and formally"
    },
    {
        "question": "depart from",
        "options": [
            "to be easy to see or notice because of being different, ...",
            "to be about a subject, ...",
            "if something dries off, or if you dry it off, all the water dries or is wiped from its surface",
            "to not use the usual way of doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to not use the usual way of doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "derogate from",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ...",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ...",
            "approach someone without their knowing",
            "same as pucker"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "descend from",
        "options": [
            "to break a door or gate in order to get through it",
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ...",
            "pay a debt over time",
            "to suddenly let something bad or unpleasant have its full effect on someone or something in an uncontrolled way"
        ],
        "answer": "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "descend into",
        "options": [
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "if a situation descends into a certain bad state, it becomes bad",
            "same as tape"
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation descends into a certain bad state, it becomes bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "descend on",
        "options": [
            "used about things that suddenly arrive or appear, ...",
            "to do someone\u2019s work while they are away or ill, ...",
            "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad",
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
        ],
        "answer": "used about things that suddenly arrive or appear, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "descend to",
        "options": [
            "to work with other people in order to help someone in a difficult situation",
            "to pull something gently and quickly several times",
            "to start behaving in a bad way",
            "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to start behaving in a bad way"
    },
    {
        "question": "devolve to",
        "options": [
            "same as spin, ...",
            "to visit a place for a short time on your way to another place",
            "to produce something such as heat, light, or a smell",
            "to become someone\u2019s property when someone else dies"
        ],
        "answer": "to become someone\u2019s property when someone else dies"
    },
    {
        "question": "dial down",
        "options": [
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ...",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice",
            "same as lay, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dial in",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "join a teleconference",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "exploit or harm, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "join a teleconference"
    },
    {
        "question": "dial into",
        "options": [
            "join a teleconference",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ...",
            "do something quickly",
            "same as empty"
        ],
        "answer": "join a teleconference"
    },
    {
        "question": "dial up",
        "options": [
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "to get connected to the internet on your computer by using a modem and telephone line",
            "to be easy to notice, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get connected to the internet on your computer by using a modem and telephone line"
    },
    {
        "question": "die away",
        "options": [
            "to become quieter or weaker and finally stop",
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ...",
            "depart furtively"
        ],
        "answer": "to become quieter or weaker and finally stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "die back",
        "options": [
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat",
            "if a plant dies back, the part above the ground dies but the roots stay alive",
            "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ...",
            "to receive news about someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a plant dies back, the part above the ground dies but the roots stay alive"
    },
    {
        "question": "die down",
        "options": [
            "to begin an attack in boxing with a particular hand or hit, ...",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "save money in a bank account, investment, etc",
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active"
    },
    {
        "question": "die for",
        "options": [
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "relax, do nothing",
            "to kill yourself, ...",
            "to challenge someone over something they have said or done, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to kill yourself, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "die off",
        "options": [
            "to do the opposite of what a person, set of rules etc says you should do, because you disagree with them",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist"
        ],
        "answer": "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist"
    },
    {
        "question": "die out",
        "options": [
            "to agree with an idea",
            "same as tape",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely",
            "to do the same activity for a very long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely"
    },
    {
        "question": "dig around",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something inside a place or container by searching in every part of it, ...",
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "if something centres around a place, or if you centre something around it, it happens mainly there, ...",
            "to choose someone or something after considering the situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something inside a place or container by searching in every part of it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dig in",
        "options": [
            "to start to sleep",
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat",
            "to not do something because you do not feel brave enough",
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to mix something into the ground by digging, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dig into",
        "options": [
            "to start working hard and seriously",
            "to spend time doing nothing useful or important",
            "to press hard into something, ...",
            "force someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to press hard into something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dig out",
        "options": [
            "to accelerate rapidly in a vehicle, ...",
            "to masturbate",
            "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ...",
            "to say officially that someone should receive a particular punishment, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to accelerate rapidly in a vehicle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dig over",
        "options": [
            "to dig ground in order to prepare it for new plants",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ...",
            "to choose one person from a group for special attention",
            "go somewhere quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to dig ground in order to prepare it for new plants"
    },
    {
        "question": "dig up",
        "options": [
            "clock in, ...",
            "to dig holes in an area of land, ...",
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound",
            "to decide not to have an ordinary job or life because you do not want to be part of society, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to dig holes in an area of land, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dine in",
        "options": [
            "to eat your evening meal at home, or at a hotel when you are staying there, instead of at a restaurant",
            "introduce a new product; launch, ...",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to make something more interesting and exciting"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat your evening meal at home, or at a hotel when you are staying there, instead of at a restaurant"
    },
    {
        "question": "dine on",
        "options": [
            "to eat a particular type of food, especially an expensive one",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to wash the whole surface of something, ...",
            "same as block"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat a particular type of food, especially an expensive one"
    },
    {
        "question": "dine out",
        "options": [
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car",
            "focus attention on, single out",
            "to eat dinner in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "to notice something that is not very obvious, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to eat dinner in a restaurant instead of at home"
    },
    {
        "question": "dine out on",
        "options": [
            "to joke about something in order to show that you think it is not important or serious",
            "to arrive or appear somewhere",
            "if you dine out on an event or experience, people invite you to meals so that you can tell them about it",
            "phone back"
        ],
        "answer": "if you dine out on an event or experience, people invite you to meals so that you can tell them about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "dip in",
        "options": [
            "put something in a liquid for a short time",
            "to compare one thing with another, ...",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something"
        ],
        "answer": "put something in a liquid for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "dip into",
        "options": [
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ...",
            "pretend to think about or think about in a casual way",
            "to put your hand into a container in order to get something, ...",
            "to have happened previously, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put your hand into a container in order to get something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dip out",
        "options": [
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to give something to several people, ...",
            "remove quickly",
            "to fail a test or a course at school, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fail a test or a course at school, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "disagree with",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ...",
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group",
            "continue doing something you don't want to",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls over, they stop by the side of the road, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dish out",
        "options": [
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "to serve food, ...",
            "to handle or use something in a stupid or careless way",
            "to suddenly stop working, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to serve food, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dish up",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, machine etc",
            "to become quieter or weaker and finally stop",
            "to put food into dishes so that it is ready to be eaten",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put food into dishes so that it is ready to be eaten"
    },
    {
        "question": "dispense with",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in something, ...",
            "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them",
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "to not do something that you promised to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them"
    },
    {
        "question": "dissolve into",
        "options": [
            "if you dissolve into something such as tears or laughter, you begin to cry or laugh in an uncontrolled way",
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ...",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "to stand somewhere and do nothing, often when you should be doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "if you dissolve into something such as tears or laughter, you begin to cry or laugh in an uncontrolled way"
    },
    {
        "question": "dive in",
        "options": [
            "same as close, ...",
            "to start eating in a very enthusiastic way, ...",
            "to give someone something that is not what they want or need, ...",
            "if you have finished with something, you have stopped using it and no longer need it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start eating in a very enthusiastic way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dive into",
        "options": [
            "to have enough money to pay for the things that you really need in order to live, but no more",
            "reach inside something quickly",
            "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance",
            "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "reach inside something quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "divide into",
        "options": [
            "to be connected with someone or something, ...",
            "to consider something in a particular way, ...",
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number",
            "to be very happy about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number"
    },
    {
        "question": "divide off",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to have an ordinary job or life because you do not want to be part of society, ...",
            "become very disturbed or angry",
            "to keep one area separate from another",
            "same as toss"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep one area separate from another"
    },
    {
        "question": "divide up",
        "options": [
            "same as divide",
            "to remove one part of something",
            "to fail a test or a course at school, ...",
            "repeatedly criticise someone verbally"
        ],
        "answer": "same as divide"
    },
    {
        "question": "divvy out",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "to not allow yourself to be treated badly, especially by someone in authority",
            "have a good time when intoxicated",
            "divide, share"
        ],
        "answer": "divide, share"
    },
    {
        "question": "divvy up",
        "options": [
            "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way",
            "to ask for news about someone",
            "to divide or share something"
        ],
        "answer": "to divide or share something"
    },
    {
        "question": "do away with",
        "options": [
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc",
            "to press hard into a surface",
            "to finally allow people to see something that has been hidden"
        ],
        "answer": "to murder someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "do in",
        "options": [
            "to escape with something that you have stolen",
            "get near someone",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "to murder someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to murder someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "do out of",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone from getting or having something that they should have, especially in a way that is unfair or dishonest",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug",
            "to attack someone or something, ...",
            "to produce something very quickly and without working very hard"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop someone from getting or having something that they should have, especially in a way that is unfair or dishonest"
    },
    {
        "question": "do over",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ...",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "do up",
        "options": [
            "to talk to someone who has done something wrong in an effort to persuade them to improve their behaviour",
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "to fasten something, ...",
            "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night"
        ],
        "answer": "to fasten something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "do with",
        "options": [
            "to recognize that something is not true and not be tricked by it, ...",
            "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ...",
            "to be connected with someone or something, ...",
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to be connected with someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "do without",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of something unpleasant",
            "to give knowledge or teach skills to your children or to younger people",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ...",
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dob in",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to tell someone in authority about something bad that another person has done",
            "return quickly",
            "to cover a window or door with wooden boards"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone in authority about something bad that another person has done"
    },
    {
        "question": "dole out",
        "options": [
            "progress, ...",
            "same as spy, ...",
            "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it",
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group"
    },
    {
        "question": "doss about",
        "options": [
            "spend time doing very little or being unproductive",
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ...",
            "to understand or describe something exactly, ...",
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner"
        ],
        "answer": "spend time doing very little or being unproductive"
    },
    {
        "question": "doss around",
        "options": [
            "spend time doing very little or being unproductive",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to start to get better after being ill or in a bad situation"
        ],
        "answer": "spend time doing very little or being unproductive"
    },
    {
        "question": "doss down",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something until it has been completed, ...",
            "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose",
            "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home",
            "to have another use or job as something"
        ],
        "answer": "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home"
    },
    {
        "question": "double as",
        "options": [
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ...",
            "to have another use or job as something",
            "to arrange an agreement or deal, ...",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have another use or job as something"
    },
    {
        "question": "double back",
        "options": [
            "to build an extra part onto a building, ...",
            "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from",
            "same as eat away, ...",
            "to suddenly have an idea, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from"
    },
    {
        "question": "double down",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "to believe that something is true when it is not, ...",
            "to be an important aspect of a situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky"
    },
    {
        "question": "double down on",
        "options": [
            "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type",
            "same as flip",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours"
        ],
        "answer": "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky"
    },
    {
        "question": "double for",
        "options": [
            "approach someone discreetly",
            "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film",
            "to stay at home",
            "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them"
        ],
        "answer": "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film"
    },
    {
        "question": "double over",
        "options": [
            "same as double, ...",
            "to want something, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to consider a problem or decision carefully"
        ],
        "answer": "same as double, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "double up",
        "options": [
            "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules",
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom"
    },
    {
        "question": "double up as",
        "options": [
            "same as double",
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "to send air out of your lungs through your nose or mouth, ...",
            "to encourage someone to do something that they should not do"
        ],
        "answer": "same as double"
    },
    {
        "question": "doze off",
        "options": [
            "if you sign for a sports club, you join it by signing a contract, ...",
            "to start to sleep, especially during the day and without intending to",
            "work hard doing something",
            "if you sign away property or a right to something, you agree that it no longer belongs to you by writing your name on a document"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to sleep, especially during the day and without intending to"
    },
    {
        "question": "draft in",
        "options": [
            "to bring someone into a team or group of people in order to help them do something",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "to murder someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to bring someone into a team or group of people in order to help them do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "drag by",
        "options": [
            "to tick off something",
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier",
            "if time drags by, it seems to pass very slowly",
            "same as lighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if time drags by, it seems to pass very slowly"
    },
    {
        "question": "drag down",
        "options": [
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ...",
            "visit different places for pleasure"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drag in",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something",
            "visit different places for pleasure",
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drag into",
        "options": [
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ...",
            "to plan in detail how something will happen",
            "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drag on",
        "options": [
            "to return something that is not satisfactory",
            "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is",
            "to continue for longer than you want or think is necessary",
            "to keep telling other people what to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue for longer than you want or think is necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "drag out",
        "options": [
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen",
            "to pay a particular amount of money for something",
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something continue for longer than necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "drag out of",
        "options": [
            "to force or persuade someone to tell you something when they do not want to",
            "to be able to understand something or to solve a problem, ...",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force or persuade someone to tell you something when they do not want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "drag up",
        "options": [
            "join a teleconference",
            "to make particular marks appear on someone\u2019s skin",
            "short circuit",
            "to start talking about something when it is not necessary, usually something unpleasant that happened in the past and that other people want to forget"
        ],
        "answer": "to start talking about something when it is not necessary, usually something unpleasant that happened in the past and that other people want to forget"
    },
    {
        "question": "draw away",
        "options": [
            "not turn off",
            "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ...",
            "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ...",
            "to move away from a person or place"
        ],
        "answer": "to move away from a person or place"
    },
    {
        "question": "draw back",
        "options": [
            "enter a place and interrupt people rudely",
            "same as seal",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to move away from someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move away from someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw down",
        "options": [
            "to reduce an amount of money by using it",
            "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping",
            "to remove something from a list or record, ...",
            "to drink all of your drink"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce an amount of money by using it"
    },
    {
        "question": "draw even",
        "options": [
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "equalize one\ufffds competitive position",
            "same as blank, ...",
            "to become successful or happy in a particular situation, especially one that other people would not enjoy"
        ],
        "answer": "equalize one\ufffds competitive position"
    },
    {
        "question": "draw in",
        "options": [
            "fairly old, ...",
            "same as light, ...",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to answer a question or remark quickly and in an angry way"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive in a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw into",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force",
            "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive in a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw off",
        "options": [
            "same as rain",
            "get lost",
            "to take some of the liquid out of something",
            "get so emotional that you lose control"
        ],
        "answer": "to take some of the liquid out of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "draw on",
        "options": [
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "to breathe in smoke from a cigarette, ...",
            "to tell someone something, ...",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug"
        ],
        "answer": "to breathe in smoke from a cigarette, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw out",
        "options": [
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems",
            "if an injury heals up, the skin or bone grows back together and becomes healthy again",
            "to take out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take out, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw up",
        "options": [
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it",
            "be good enough, ...",
            "if a vehicle draws up, it arrives at a place and stops, ...",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility"
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle draws up, it arrives at a place and stops, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "draw upon",
        "options": [
            "same as roll, ...",
            "same as draw on",
            "to get an advantage by making use of something",
            "to inform someone about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as draw on"
    },
    {
        "question": "dream away",
        "options": [
            "to make something flat, ...",
            "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist",
            "same as tidy, ...",
            "to spend your time thinking pleasant thoughts but not really achieving anything"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend your time thinking pleasant thoughts but not really achieving anything"
    },
    {
        "question": "dream of",
        "options": [
            "become very disturbed or angry",
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to do something immediately, and often with enthusiasm, as soon as you have the chance to do it",
            "not think or consider"
        ],
        "answer": "not think or consider"
    },
    {
        "question": "dream up",
        "options": [
            "to do something that you have agreed or promised to do, ...",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ...",
            "to think of a new idea or plan, especially one that is silly or unusual"
        ],
        "answer": "to think of a new idea or plan, especially one that is silly or unusual"
    },
    {
        "question": "dredge up",
        "options": [
            "to tie the ends of something together, ...",
            "to celebrate the end of a year, ...",
            "to manage to remember something that you learned or knew long ago, ...",
            "to make something flat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to manage to remember something that you learned or knew long ago, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dress down",
        "options": [
            "to speak in an angry way to someone who has done something wrong, ...",
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question",
            "to search for someone or something, ...",
            "to start a journey by ship, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to speak in an angry way to someone who has done something wrong, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dress up",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to increase in size, ...",
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "to make something seem more impressive than it really is, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something seem more impressive than it really is, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drift apart",
        "options": [
            "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling",
            "if an injury heals over, new skin forms over it and it becomes healthy again",
            "if two or more people drift apart, their relationship gradually ends",
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "if two or more people drift apart, their relationship gradually ends"
    },
    {
        "question": "drift off",
        "options": [
            "to examine a place by walking around it, ...",
            "to start to sleep",
            "to try hard to catch someone or to get something that you need",
            "to achieve a particular level or number, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "drill down",
        "options": [
            "same as flare",
            "to organize data (=computer information) according to different levels of detail, each level more detailed than the previous one",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ...",
            "to do something, especially something that you should not do"
        ],
        "answer": "to organize data (=computer information) according to different levels of detail, each level more detailed than the previous one"
    },
    {
        "question": "drill down through",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something for a period of time, ...",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly"
        ],
        "answer": "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data"
    },
    {
        "question": "drill into",
        "options": [
            "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times",
            "to earn a particular amount of money, ...",
            "same as melt, ...",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times"
    },
    {
        "question": "drink down",
        "options": [
            "to consider an idea or plan, but not very seriously, ...",
            "same as tangle",
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly",
            "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to drink all of something, especially quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "drink in",
        "options": [
            "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to give someone the same amount of money that you borrowed from them, ...",
            "to experience something with great enjoyment"
        ],
        "answer": "to experience something with great enjoyment"
    },
    {
        "question": "drink to",
        "options": [
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to make something happen, especially to cause changes in a situation",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drink up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone or something more active and lively",
            "to drink all of your drink",
            "depart furtively",
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to drink all of your drink"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive at",
        "options": [
            "same as flatten, ...",
            "what someone is really trying to say",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it"
        ],
        "answer": "what someone is really trying to say"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive away",
        "options": [
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone",
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling",
            "when something continues to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive back",
        "options": [
            "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked.",
            "to give something to someone officially and formally",
            "if you are driven back by something, it forces you to stop trying to reach a person or place and move back",
            "enter a place quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "if you are driven back by something, it forces you to stop trying to reach a person or place and move back"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive by",
        "options": [
            "to stop working as a way of protesting about something, ...",
            "do something out of a car",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to tell information or facts that you should keep secret, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "do something out of a car"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive down",
        "options": [
            "to produce something in large quantities, especially when this is boring or difficult",
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level",
            "to deal successfully with a problem or situation that is especially difficult, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive off",
        "options": [
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drive out",
        "options": [
            "force someone",
            "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort",
            "same as show, ...",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone or something to leave a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "drive up",
        "options": [
            "to leave or give up something",
            "to spend your time behaving in a silly way",
            "to sleep outside",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drone on",
        "options": [
            "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ...",
            "to copy a way of doing something or a system, ...",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a very boring way",
            "same as call"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk about something for a long time in a very boring way"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop around",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone or something",
            "deliver, ...",
            "to dig something out of the ground, especially with your hands",
            "be submitted, arrive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "deliver, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drop away",
        "options": [
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
        ],
        "answer": "same as drop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drop back",
        "options": [
            "to copy someone or something\u2019s style",
            "same as watch, ...",
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots",
            "same as drop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as drop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drop behind",
        "options": [
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "become controlled",
            "same as drop back"
        ],
        "answer": "same as drop back"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop by",
        "options": [
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "to make a short visit somewhere",
            "be depressed, ...",
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a short visit somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop in",
        "options": [
            "same as touch",
            "to make it difficult to hear what someone says by shouting while they are speaking",
            "to make a short visit somewhere",
            "to not approve of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a short visit somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop off",
        "options": [
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "to attempt to get or achieve something difficult or something that you want very much",
            "same as double"
        ],
        "answer": "same as drop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drop out",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to have an ordinary job or life because you do not want to be part of society, ...",
            "same as fiddle, ...",
            "to move things so that they are in different places or positions",
            "to get back something that you have lost"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to have an ordinary job or life because you do not want to be part of society, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "drop over",
        "options": [
            "to take someone somewhere, especially to a prison or hospital",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to make something happen more quickly or easily",
            "to force someone to leave a place or an organization"
        ],
        "answer": "visit for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop round",
        "options": [
            "have sex with",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls up, they stop, ...",
            "same as drop",
            "a loud sound or music"
        ],
        "answer": "same as drop"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop someone in it",
        "options": [
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to escape with something, especially something stolen",
            "get someone into trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "get someone into trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "drop through",
        "options": [
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "to quickly jump or dive into water, ...",
            "to start discussing a subject, ...",
            "come to nothing, produce no results"
        ],
        "answer": "come to nothing, produce no results"
    },
    {
        "question": "drown in",
        "options": [
            "if you force back tears, you try very hard not to cry",
            "cover excessively",
            "to return to a place, ...",
            "to suddenly notice or think of something"
        ],
        "answer": "cover excessively"
    },
    {
        "question": "drown out",
        "options": [
            "be so loud that another sound cannot be heard",
            "same as charge",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to continue for longer than you want or think is necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "be so loud that another sound cannot be heard"
    },
    {
        "question": "drug up",
        "options": [
            "leave a place angrily",
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "if a liquid boils away, or if you boil it away, it disappears and turns to gas after reaching a very high temperature",
            "to give someone a lot of drugs or medicine with the result that they cannot behave normally"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone a lot of drugs or medicine with the result that they cannot behave normally"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum into",
        "options": [
            "persuade, ...",
            "to make someone learn or understand something by repeating it many times",
            "to separate an object into pieces, ...",
            "to make someone go somewhere, especially in order to get rid of them"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone learn or understand something by repeating it many times"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum out",
        "options": [
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them",
            "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad",
            "to leave quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum up",
        "options": [
            "to try to make people support you or buy something from you",
            "try to maintain beliefs, hopes, etc.",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make people support you or buy something from you"
    },
    {
        "question": "dry off",
        "options": [
            "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ...",
            "to press hard into a surface",
            "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ...",
            "if something dries off, or if you dry it off, all the water dries or is wiped from its surface"
        ],
        "answer": "if something dries off, or if you dry it off, all the water dries or is wiped from its surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "dry out",
        "options": [
            "same as get over",
            "if something dries out or is dried out, some or all the water comes out of it, ...",
            "fall, ...",
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something dries out or is dried out, some or all the water comes out of it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dry up",
        "options": [
            "if a vehicle draws up, it arrives at a place and stops, ...",
            "to become connected to something such as a computer network or phone system, ...",
            "same as set against, ...",
            "same as dry, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as dry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dub in",
        "options": [
            "to leave quickly, ...",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ...",
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it"
    },
    {
        "question": "dub out",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to remove part of the original sound from a recording, especially a film",
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to leave a job or position, especially an important one, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove part of the original sound from a recording, especially a film"
    },
    {
        "question": "dub over",
        "options": [
            "same as light, ...",
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen",
            "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist"
        ],
        "answer": "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language"
    },
    {
        "question": "duck out",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place, especially in a way that is not noticed by other people",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems",
            "to send someone somewhere, usually when they do not want to go",
            "to understand, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, especially in a way that is not noticed by other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "duck out of",
        "options": [
            "to form a long line of traffic that is not moving",
            "if a roof or wall caves in, it falls down or inwards, ...",
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something",
            "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "duff up",
        "options": [
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "same as burn off, ...",
            "to prevent an amount or number from passing a limit, ...",
            "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times"
        ],
        "answer": "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times"
    },
    {
        "question": "dumb down",
        "options": [
            "to take a lot of money or profit, especially an unfair amount, in a business deal, ...",
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to make something simpler and easier to understand in a way that reduces its quality",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something simpler and easier to understand in a way that reduces its quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "dump on",
        "options": [
            "cover excessively",
            "to treat someone in an unfair way, especially by criticizing or blaming them for something, ...",
            "to begin doing something, especially in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone in an unfair way, especially by criticizing or blaming them for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dust down",
        "options": [
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to discuss something until you find a solution or reach an agreement",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off the surface of something, ...",
            "to secretly give the police or someone in authority information about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to wipe dust or dirt off the surface of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dust off",
        "options": [
            "to go to sleep",
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "to remain at a place longer than you had intended to",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "dwell on",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "to come out of a place or thing",
            "to prevent someone from making progress, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "dwell upon",
        "options": [
            "to avoid dealing directly with a problem, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly",
            "to start laughing, or to make someone laugh a lot"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "earth up",
        "options": [
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "progress",
            "to put soil around a plant in order to protect it or to help it to grow",
            "to walk into a room where someone is doing something private or secret"
        ],
        "answer": "to put soil around a plant in order to protect it or to help it to grow"
    },
    {
        "question": "ease off",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "to go more slowly, especially when you are driving or running fast, ...",
            "same as pine"
        ],
        "answer": "to go more slowly, especially when you are driving or running fast, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ease out",
        "options": [
            "to gradually become thinner and weaker over a period of time, usually because of an illness",
            "something that makes you feel very disappointed or upset, especially when you have been trying hard to achieve something",
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly"
    },
    {
        "question": "ease up",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "stop paying attention, ...",
            "to put soil around a plant in order to protect it or to help it to grow",
            "same as ease off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as ease off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "eat away",
        "options": [
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to start discussing a subject, ...",
            "make a lot of money",
            "to gradually destroy something"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually destroy something"
    },
    {
        "question": "eat away at",
        "options": [
            "to start to sleep",
            "same as put, ...",
            "to refuse to obey instructions, ...",
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried"
    },
    {
        "question": "eat in",
        "options": [
            "to have a meal at home instead of in a restaurant",
            "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you",
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a meal at home instead of in a restaurant"
    },
    {
        "question": "eat into",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere away from people to study or work",
            "same as eat away, ...",
            "to drink all of your drink",
            "to pay money into a bank"
        ],
        "answer": "same as eat away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "eat out",
        "options": [
            "same as pass",
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show",
            "to eat a lot of a particular food with enjoyment",
            "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home"
        ],
        "answer": "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home"
    },
    {
        "question": "eat up",
        "options": [
            "same as watch, ...",
            "to separate an object into pieces, ...",
            "same as post",
            "to eat all of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to eat all of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ebb away",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to let someone come into a place",
            "to admit that you were wrong, especially after expressing an opinion or argument very firmly",
            "same as pen, ...",
            "disappear gradually"
        ],
        "answer": "disappear gradually"
    },
    {
        "question": "edge out",
        "options": [
            "to increase in size, ...",
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to be an aspect of a situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "edge up",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone from getting or having something that they should have, especially in a way that is unfair or dishonest",
            "approach slowly",
            "work with someone or a group to achieve something",
            "sleep on something other than a bed"
        ],
        "answer": "approach slowly"
    },
    {
        "question": "edit out",
        "options": [
            "to remove parts of a film, television, or radio programme that are not wanted before it is shown or broadcast",
            "to make a car go backwards, ...",
            "to seem to have a small amount of an unpleasant quality",
            "to buy a lot of something so that it is available when you need it"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove parts of a film, television, or radio programme that are not wanted before it is shown or broadcast"
    },
    {
        "question": "egg on",
        "options": [
            "to encourage someone to do something that they should not do",
            "break, damage or hurt by hitting",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "same as swell"
        ],
        "answer": "to encourage someone to do something that they should not do"
    },
    {
        "question": "eke out",
        "options": [
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ...",
            "to be caused by something",
            "accept something less satisfactory because there's no alternative",
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future"
        ],
        "answer": "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "elbow out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone leave a job or position so that you or someone else can take their place",
            "not think or consider",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ...",
            "to babysit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone leave a job or position so that you or someone else can take their place"
    },
    {
        "question": "embark on",
        "options": [
            "same as bust, ...",
            "to start a journey by ship, ...",
            "to make a vehicle stop by waving your arm or hand at the driver",
            "to keep criticizing someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a journey by ship, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "embark upon",
        "options": [
            "to do something after you have intended to do it for some time",
            "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ...",
            "sit down heavily",
            "to start a journey by ship, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start a journey by ship, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "empty out",
        "options": [
            "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife",
            "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy",
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "same as empty"
        ],
        "answer": "same as empty"
    },
    {
        "question": "end in",
        "options": [
            "to surround someone or something, ...",
            "to reduce the number of possibilities or choices",
            "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it",
            "to have something as a final result, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have something as a final result, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "end up",
        "options": [
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "same as light, ...",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it",
            "to physically attack someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it"
    },
    {
        "question": "end up with",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "to develop a career or position for yourself by working hard",
            "get as a result of something"
        ],
        "answer": "get as a result of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "end with",
        "options": [
            "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ...",
            "to pull something gently and quickly several times",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to have something as the final part, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have something as the final part, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "endow with",
        "options": [
            "same as block",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "express or display emotions openly, ...",
            "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "engage in",
        "options": [
            "to disappear, or to make something disappear, because it has been used or rubbed a lot",
            "divide, share",
            "to be about something, or to be connected with something, ...",
            "to start having a conversation with someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start having a conversation with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "engage with",
        "options": [
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ...",
            "persevere, not give up",
            "same as throw away, ...",
            "same as beat up"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "enlarge on",
        "options": [
            "to relax",
            "to stop the flow of something, usually water or electricity, ...",
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ...",
            "to give more information about something that you have already mentioned"
        ],
        "answer": "to give more information about something that you have already mentioned"
    },
    {
        "question": "enter for",
        "options": [
            "to shoot someone and kill them or injure them badly, especially someone who is not guilty of anything, or who is not carrying a gun",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "join or enter a competition",
            "to make two things fit or match each other, or to fit or match in this way"
        ],
        "answer": "join or enter a competition"
    },
    {
        "question": "enter into",
        "options": [
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "same as jam",
            "to be an important aspect of a situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be an important aspect of a situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "enter on",
        "options": [
            "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ...",
            "same as tape",
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to begin something or begin to take part in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin something or begin to take part in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "even out",
        "options": [
            "to walk or go somewhere in a relaxed and confident way, ...",
            "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ...",
            "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth",
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "even up",
        "options": [
            "to get an advantage by making use of something",
            "if you wash dirt off something, or if dirt washes off, you remove it by washing",
            "employ someone for something specific",
            "to make something fairer or more equal"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something fairer or more equal"
    },
    {
        "question": "explain away",
        "options": [
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it",
            "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening",
            "to make a place smell very unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "eye up",
        "options": [
            "to look at someone in a way that shows you are sexually attracted to them",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "to start to employ someone, ...",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to look at someone in a way that shows you are sexually attracted to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "face about",
        "options": [
            "become nervous, tense or unable to relax",
            "to turn and face in the opposite direction",
            "when a feeling can be seen despite attempts to conceal it",
            "to think someone or something is wrong"
        ],
        "answer": "to turn and face in the opposite direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "face down",
        "options": [
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "to appear strong and confident when someone is threatening or criticizing you",
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong"
        ],
        "answer": "to appear strong and confident when someone is threatening or criticizing you"
    },
    {
        "question": "face off",
        "options": [
            "to organize data (=computer information) according to different levels of detail, each level more detailed than the previous one",
            "to begin a game of ice hockey, ...",
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "make a cannabis joint"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a game of ice hockey, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "face up to",
        "options": [
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something of lower quality than they wanted",
            "same as face",
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them"
        ],
        "answer": "same as face"
    },
    {
        "question": "factor in",
        "options": [
            "treat someone badly, ...",
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount",
            "try to find something"
        ],
        "answer": "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something"
    },
    {
        "question": "factor into",
        "options": [
            "to speak in support of a person or an idea, belief, or plan, especially when no one else will",
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you"
        ],
        "answer": "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something"
    },
    {
        "question": "factor out",
        "options": [
            "to not include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "do something out of a car"
        ],
        "answer": "to not include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fade away",
        "options": [
            "to deal with an unpleasant situation in a confident, patient, and determined way",
            "same as fade, ...",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ...",
            "to take out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as fade, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fade in",
        "options": [
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "if a sound or picture fades in, or if you fade it in, it gradually becomes louder or clearer",
            "to force a plane to land, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a sound or picture fades in, or if you fade it in, it gradually becomes louder or clearer"
    },
    {
        "question": "fade out",
        "options": [
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "to consider or express something in a different way, ...",
            "if a sound or picture fades out, or if you fade it out, it gradually disappears",
            "same as build on"
        ],
        "answer": "if a sound or picture fades out, or if you fade it out, it gradually disappears"
    },
    {
        "question": "faff about",
        "options": [
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball",
            "to waste time doing things that are not important or necessary",
            "to begin something or begin to take part in something",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it"
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time doing things that are not important or necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "faff around",
        "options": [
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier",
            "behave indecisively",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "behave indecisively"
    },
    {
        "question": "fake out",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out information about something",
            "to trick someone by pretending something or by behaving dishonestly",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "understand something, often after a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to trick someone by pretending something or by behaving dishonestly"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall about",
        "options": [
            "same as ease off, ...",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "fail to keep an appointment",
            "to telephone someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall apart",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to tell someone something that they do not expect",
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ...",
            "to break because of being old or badly made, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to break because of being old or badly made, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall away",
        "options": [
            "same as heave",
            "re-invest money you have made into a business",
            "to continue doing something although it is difficult or although other people have stopped doing it",
            "to become smaller or lower in amount, level, value etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become smaller or lower in amount, level, value etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall back",
        "options": [
            "if a sound or picture fades in, or if you fade it in, it gradually becomes louder or clearer",
            "to move so that you are behind someone or something, ...",
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to switch off a light, machine etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to move so that you are behind someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall back on",
        "options": [
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to become involved in something, ...",
            "to use or do something else after other things have failed",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use or do something else after other things have failed"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall behind",
        "options": [
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ...",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to kill someone by shooting them, ...",
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall down",
        "options": [
            "to take a young plant that is growing in a container and put it in the ground to grow",
            "to ask for news about someone",
            "same as fall, ...",
            "to force or persuade someone to tell you something when they do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fall, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall for",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "to completely fill a container that is already partly full, ...",
            "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ...",
            "to be closed by means of a zip, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall in",
        "options": [
            "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ...",
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "visit a place to check something",
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall in with",
        "options": [
            "to become friends with someone, ...",
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "to have one side or edge touching something, or to put something in this position",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food"
        ],
        "answer": "to become friends with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall into",
        "options": [
            "persuade or deceive someone into doing something",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to start doing something by chance, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something by chance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall off",
        "options": [
            "same as pull, ...",
            "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people",
            "if the amount, level, or value of something falls off, it gets smaller",
            "same as hitch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if the amount, level, or value of something falls off, it gets smaller"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall on",
        "options": [
            "if something falls on someone, it is their responsibility to do it, ...",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "to have a meal at home instead of in a restaurant"
        ],
        "answer": "if something falls on someone, it is their responsibility to do it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall out",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "if something such as your hair or a tooth falls out, it comes out, ...",
            "to buy something expensive",
            "have no more left"
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as your hair or a tooth falls out, it comes out, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall over",
        "options": [
            "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ...",
            "to finish drinking something",
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "depart in a hurry"
        ],
        "answer": "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fall through",
        "options": [
            "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen",
            "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')",
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "if the amount, level, or value of something falls off, it gets smaller"
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall to",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone or something, ...",
            "to move a small young plant into a larger pot or container so that it can grow bigger",
            "if a particular job or duty falls to someone, it is their responsibility",
            "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a particular job or duty falls to someone, it is their responsibility"
    },
    {
        "question": "fall under",
        "options": [
            "become controlled",
            "same as charge",
            "same as cut, ...",
            "same as choke, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "become controlled"
    },
    {
        "question": "fan out",
        "options": [
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "to change something in order to make it seem more interesting, exciting, or important",
            "to spread objects or parts out, often in the shape of a semi-circle, ...",
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spread objects or parts out, often in the shape of a semi-circle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "farm out",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to be looked after by someone else, ...",
            "to not do something immediately because you are not confident or you do not feel certain about it",
            "same as flatten, ...",
            "to reach a particular number or amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone to be looked after by someone else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fart about",
        "options": [
            "open a particular computer program that requires a name and password",
            "same as invite",
            "to buy part of a business, especially in order to get control of it, ...",
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things"
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things"
    },
    {
        "question": "fart around",
        "options": [
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ...",
            "to make something fairer or more equal",
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is"
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things"
    },
    {
        "question": "fasten down",
        "options": [
            "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ...",
            "to be very happy about something, ...",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move",
            "to stop doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "tie something so that it doesn't move"
    },
    {
        "question": "fasten on",
        "options": [
            "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something",
            "to be a disadvantage in a particular situation",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fasten onto",
        "options": [
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "provide information",
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "to leave or give up something"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fasten up",
        "options": [
            "reserve",
            "same as fasten",
            "to spend a period of time in sleeping, ...",
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fasten"
    },
    {
        "question": "fathom out",
        "options": [
            "equalize one\ufffds competitive position",
            "to dig holes in an area of land, ...",
            "understand something",
            "to tell someone something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "understand something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fatten up",
        "options": [
            "to waste time or money on things that are not necessary or important",
            "to make a person or animal fatter",
            "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it",
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a person or animal fatter"
    },
    {
        "question": "favour with",
        "options": [
            "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way",
            "to experience something with great enjoyment",
            "like someone from the first time you meet them",
            "to give someone something such as a look, smile, or answer to a question"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone something such as a look, smile, or answer to a question"
    },
    {
        "question": "fawn on",
        "options": [
            "praise someone in an excessive way to get their favour or something from them",
            "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ...",
            "to enjoy a particular thing or activity, ...",
            "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "praise someone in an excessive way to get their favour or something from them"
    },
    {
        "question": "fawn over",
        "options": [
            "to start to do something in a different way, ...",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "to be extremely nice to someone more important than you because you want them to like you or give you something",
            "to remind someone of something in the past, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be extremely nice to someone more important than you because you want them to like you or give you something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fear for",
        "options": [
            "to help someone to get rid of feelings of sadness, worry, or anger by kissing them to show that you are sympathetic",
            "to feel worried about someone or something because you think something bad may happen to them or has happened to them",
            "to start to sleep",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "to feel worried about someone or something because you think something bad may happen to them or has happened to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "feast on",
        "options": [
            "to eat a lot of a particular food with enjoyment",
            "expel",
            "to arrange something in a long line, ...",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat a lot of a particular food with enjoyment"
    },
    {
        "question": "feed off",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone a lot, ...",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended",
            "if animals feed off something, they eat it, ...",
            "to be very obvious or noticeable, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if animals feed off something, they eat it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "feed on",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ...",
            "to cut a line of cocaine",
            "to change to a new system or way of behaving, ...",
            "same as feed off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as feed off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "feed up",
        "options": [
            "to become thinner by losing weight, ...",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another",
            "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin",
            "to secretly give the police or someone in authority information about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin"
    },
    {
        "question": "feel for",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to feel sympathy for someone",
            "to do something bad or unpleasant to someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to feel sympathy for someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "feel out",
        "options": [
            "affect, ...",
            "to make it difficult to hear what someone says by shouting while they are speaking",
            "to try to discover in a careful or indirect way what a situation is like or what someone\u2019s attitude is",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to discover in a careful or indirect way what a situation is like or what someone\u2019s attitude is"
    },
    {
        "question": "feel up",
        "options": [
            "to make a choice or decision from a range of possibilities",
            "to touch someone sexually without them wanting you to",
            "same as bung, ...",
            "continue with something difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "to touch someone sexually without them wanting you to"
    },
    {
        "question": "feel up to",
        "options": [
            "to move things so that they are in different places or positions",
            "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them",
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fence in",
        "options": [
            "to give someone the same amount of money that you borrowed from them, ...",
            "same as fence, ...",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fence, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fence off",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time with someone, especially someone who other people do not approve of",
            "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence",
            "to consider the good and bad aspects of something in order to reach a decision about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence"
    },
    {
        "question": "fend for",
        "options": [
            "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "fend off",
        "options": [
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost",
            "to defend yourself against an attack, ...",
            "to make a dead person live again, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to defend yourself against an attack, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ferret out",
        "options": [
            "to discover information by searching for it in a determined way",
            "to grow taller very quickly, ...",
            "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ...",
            "to officially ask for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to discover information by searching for it in a determined way"
    },
    {
        "question": "fess up",
        "options": [
            "form a pair with someone",
            "to continue sleeping for a long time, ...",
            "to admit that something is true or that you have done something wrong",
            "to do what you have promised or decided, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to admit that something is true or that you have done something wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "fess up to",
        "options": [
            "to spend time with someone, ...",
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "same as blow, ...",
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "confess, admit reluctantly to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fetch up",
        "options": [
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "inject drugs",
            "to arrive at a place by accident or without intending to go there",
            "to leave a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive at a place by accident or without intending to go there"
    },
    {
        "question": "fiddle about",
        "options": [
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "same as fiddle, ...",
            "to introduce a new law or system, ...",
            "return quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fiddle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fiddle around",
        "options": [
            "to say officially that someone should receive a particular punishment, ...",
            "same as fiddle, ...",
            "to spend your time behaving in a silly way",
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as fiddle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fiddle away",
        "options": [
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "waste time",
            "to keep telling other people what to do",
            "to still exist from the past, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "waste time"
    },
    {
        "question": "fight back",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it",
            "to hit or kick someone who is attacking you, ...",
            "to pay no attention to something, ...",
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit or kick someone who is attacking you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fight down",
        "options": [
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in a bad or unfair way",
            "to be lucky",
            "to try hard not to feel or express an emotion that you are starting to feel"
        ],
        "answer": "to try hard not to feel or express an emotion that you are starting to feel"
    },
    {
        "question": "fight it out",
        "options": [
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "same as close, ...",
            "to be shocked by something",
            "to continue sleeping after the time that you usually wake up"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided"
    },
    {
        "question": "fight off",
        "options": [
            "to try to hit someone or something with your hand or a weapon, ...",
            "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ...",
            "to have a formal discussion with someone in order to try to reach an agreement about something",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fight out",
        "options": [
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ...",
            "to reduce the positive effect or success of something",
            "have sex",
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided"
    },
    {
        "question": "figure on",
        "options": [
            "to think that something will happen and plan for it",
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "to produce a particular reaction",
            "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else"
        ],
        "answer": "to think that something will happen and plan for it"
    },
    {
        "question": "figure out",
        "options": [
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it",
            "to relax, or to become less serious, ...",
            "to be able to understand something or to solve a problem, ...",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be able to understand something or to solve a problem, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "file away",
        "options": [
            "to finish drinking something",
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to pay money into a bank",
            "to give all your attention to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to put a document away in a file"
    },
    {
        "question": "file down",
        "options": [
            "same as file",
            "to turn the pages of a book, magazine, newspaper etc very quickly looking at some of the pages for a very short time, ...",
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to gradually change to a quieter or less active state, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as file"
    },
    {
        "question": "file for",
        "options": [
            "to pay attention so that you will see something when it arrives or happens",
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "to officially ask a court for something, for example ask them to give you a divorce or state officially that you are bankrupt",
            "to heat a metal until it becomes liquid, especially in order to make something new from it"
        ],
        "answer": "to officially ask a court for something, for example ask them to give you a divorce or state officially that you are bankrupt"
    },
    {
        "question": "fill in",
        "options": [
            "same as fill, ...",
            "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ...",
            "to handle or use something in a stupid or careless way",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fill, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fill in for",
        "options": [
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to",
            "same as fill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as fill, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fill in on",
        "options": [
            "give someone information",
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "same as double",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
        ],
        "answer": "give someone information"
    },
    {
        "question": "fill out",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "same as put aside",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting",
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fill up",
        "options": [
            "same as put aside",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ...",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ...",
            "same as fill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as fill, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "film over",
        "options": [
            "exploit, use to your advantage",
            "to decide not to do something because you are too tired",
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it",
            "to become covered in a thin layer of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to become covered in a thin layer of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "filter in",
        "options": [
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to not allow your feelings to show, ...",
            "move into a lane of traffic without making other cars stop",
            "to include something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "move into a lane of traffic without making other cars stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "filter out",
        "options": [
            "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod",
            "to be opposed to something, ...",
            "to remove things from a group, ...",
            "to stay at home"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove things from a group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "find for",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone who has criticized you, ...",
            "if a piece of cloth or clothing rucks up, or if you ruck it up, it forms untidy folds",
            "if a court finds for someone, it makes a decision in their favour",
            "to buy something expensive"
        ],
        "answer": "if a court finds for someone, it makes a decision in their favour"
    },
    {
        "question": "find out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone",
            "to use a hose to clean something",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to discover a fact or piece of information, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to discover a fact or piece of information, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "finish off",
        "options": [
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "to win a prize, ...",
            "to plan in detail how something will happen",
            "same as finish, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as finish, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "finish up",
        "options": [
            "to say that something bad has happened, ...",
            "same as finish, ...",
            "become gradually more evident, ...",
            "to spend time with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "same as finish, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "finish up with",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something",
            "to spread to other areas",
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "have or do something at the end or as the last of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "finish with",
        "options": [
            "same as check, ...",
            "if you have finished with something, you have stopped using it and no longer need it, ...",
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ...",
            "entertain someone in your home"
        ],
        "answer": "if you have finished with something, you have stopped using it and no longer need it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fink on",
        "options": [
            "give away secrets about someone",
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them",
            "get more people into a space than normal or comfortable",
            "to gradually become larger in number or amount"
        ],
        "answer": "give away secrets about someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "fink out",
        "options": [
            "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc",
            "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)",
            "go into the pits (car racing)",
            "same as box"
        ],
        "answer": "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "fire away",
        "options": [
            "to clock off, ...",
            "not turn off",
            "to make a noise, ...",
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question"
        ],
        "answer": "used for giving someone permission to ask a question"
    },
    {
        "question": "fire back at",
        "options": [
            "to answer a question or remark quickly and in an angry way",
            "waste time",
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "break the surface of soil"
        ],
        "answer": "to answer a question or remark quickly and in an angry way"
    },
    {
        "question": "fire off",
        "options": [
            "to live or work with someone in a friendly way",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems",
            "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ...",
            "same as mark, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fire up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel very enthusiastic",
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "improve a document",
            "to tell someone that they must stop doing something and that if they do not something bad will happen to them"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel very enthusiastic"
    },
    {
        "question": "firm up",
        "options": [
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ...",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ...",
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ...",
            "to build a new room or part onto the outside of a building, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fish for",
        "options": [
            "same as foul, ...",
            "to catch fish in a particular area of water, ...",
            "to spend a period of time relaxing or sleeping after doing something tiring",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen"
        ],
        "answer": "to catch fish in a particular area of water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fish out",
        "options": [
            "to continue for longer than planned, ...",
            "to get ready for an activity by putting on a uniform or special clothes",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something",
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pull someone or something out of the water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fit in",
        "options": [
            "same as get around",
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "to build an extra part onto a building, ...",
            "to have space for someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have space for someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fit in with",
        "options": [
            "to be correct, suitable, or sensible in relation to something else",
            "use power, contacts, etc, to force someone out",
            "same as toss",
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules"
        ],
        "answer": "to be correct, suitable, or sensible in relation to something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "fit into",
        "options": [
            "to be suitable or right for something, ...",
            "to become involved in something by accident",
            "to fix a picture to a wall, ...",
            "to pull very strongly at something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be suitable or right for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fit out",
        "options": [
            "to join together in a group to hurt, frighten, or fight someone",
            "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ...",
            "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands",
            "to not do something because you do not feel brave enough"
        ],
        "answer": "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fit out with",
        "options": [
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word",
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business",
            "to delay dealing with something",
            "provide someone with necessary equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "provide someone with necessary equipment"
    },
    {
        "question": "fit together",
        "options": [
            "if a machine or computer shuts down, or if someone shuts it down, it stops operating, ...",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to hit someone more than once. This word is used especially about men who hit their wives or girlfriends.",
            "if you fit things together, you join them in the right way to make something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you fit things together, you join them in the right way to make something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fit up",
        "options": [
            "to show the truth or importance of something",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group",
            "to make it seem that someone is guilty of a crime when they are not, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make it seem that someone is guilty of a crime when they are not, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fix on",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to choose someone or something after considering the situation, ...",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to choose someone or something after considering the situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fix up",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone something, ...",
            "to arrange for something to happen, ...",
            "to delay dealing with something",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange for something to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fix with",
        "options": [
            "visit a lot of different places for pleasure",
            "to interrupt when someone is talking, ...",
            "if you fix someone with your eyes, you look directly in their eyes so that they feel they cannot turn away",
            "to react angrily towards someone"
        ],
        "answer": "if you fix someone with your eyes, you look directly in their eyes so that they feel they cannot turn away"
    },
    {
        "question": "fizzle out",
        "options": [
            "to make plans about things that will or may happen in the future, so that you will be prepared for them",
            "end in an unsuccessful way",
            "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ...",
            "to be the reason why something exists or happens, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "end in an unsuccessful way"
    },
    {
        "question": "flag down",
        "options": [
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way",
            "to increase the speed of a vehicle by increasing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to wave at the driver of a car so that they stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to wave at the driver of a car so that they stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "flag up",
        "options": [
            "if children act up, they behave badly, ...",
            "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked.",
            "go somewhere quickly",
            "to mention something so that people know about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to mention something so that people know about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "flake out",
        "options": [
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to follow a rule, decision, or instruction",
            "to go to sleep very quickly because you are very tired",
            "order something by post"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to sleep very quickly because you are very tired"
    },
    {
        "question": "flame out",
        "options": [
            "tease, make fun of",
            "fail",
            "to become sober after being drunk, ...",
            "same as mount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fail"
    },
    {
        "question": "flame up",
        "options": [
            "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping",
            "burn brightly",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "be funny, or try to"
        ],
        "answer": "burn brightly"
    },
    {
        "question": "flare off",
        "options": [
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to begin to realize or understand something",
            "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere"
    },
    {
        "question": "flare out",
        "options": [
            "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ...",
            "to try to bite something without in fact managing to bite it",
            "same as ring",
            "same as flare"
        ],
        "answer": "same as flare"
    },
    {
        "question": "flare up",
        "options": [
            "if something blows down or is blown down, the wind makes it fall",
            "to encourage someone to do something that they should not do",
            "same as flare, ...",
            "to reach a particular number or amount"
        ],
        "answer": "same as flare, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "flash around",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to continue to live or do something without having a clear idea of what you want to achieve",
            "to show something to a lot of people because you want to impress them"
        ],
        "answer": "to show something to a lot of people because you want to impress them"
    },
    {
        "question": "flash back to",
        "options": [
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ...",
            "be unacceptable",
            "to have a particular cause or origin",
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past"
    },
    {
        "question": "flash on",
        "options": [
            "end in an unsuccessful way",
            "fairly old, ...",
            "to realize or remember something",
            "to receive information about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to realize or remember something"
    },
    {
        "question": "flatten out",
        "options": [
            "to spread objects or parts out, often in the shape of a semi-circle, ...",
            "same as flatten, ...",
            "to make a careless mistake",
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "same as flatten, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "flesh out",
        "options": [
            "same as rain",
            "depart rapidly",
            "to add more details about something in order to make it easier to understand or imagine",
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems"
        ],
        "answer": "to add more details about something in order to make it easier to understand or imagine"
    },
    {
        "question": "flick over",
        "options": [
            "to become someone\u2019s property when someone else dies",
            "change tv channels quickly",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "change tv channels quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "flick through",
        "options": [
            "to interrupt someone who is speaking, ...",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "to join a conversation or activity without being asked to",
            "to turn the pages of a book, magazine, newspaper etc very quickly looking at some of the pages for a very short time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to turn the pages of a book, magazine, newspaper etc very quickly looking at some of the pages for a very short time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fling off",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "to remove something by cutting it",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "fling on",
        "options": [
            "if you fling clothes on, you put them on quickly",
            "to reduce something, ...",
            "to leave quickly or suddenly because you are in a hurry, ...",
            "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you fling clothes on, you put them on quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip for",
        "options": [
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to immediately like someone or something very much",
            "consider, regard",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something"
        ],
        "answer": "to immediately like someone or something very much"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip off",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to a court of law because they have been accused of a crime",
            "to avoid going to school or work when you should go",
            "to tie your hair tightly so that it does not touch your face",
            "to switch off a light, machine etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to switch off a light, machine etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip on",
        "options": [
            "to not allow your feelings to show, ...",
            "arrive, end a journey in a place, often without planning",
            "to switch on a light, machine etc",
            "to be full of a strong emotion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to switch on a light, machine etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip out",
        "options": [
            "to improve, ...",
            "same as flip",
            "to reduce the number of people or things, or the size of something",
            "same as fill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as flip"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip over",
        "options": [
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ...",
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ...",
            "same as flip"
        ],
        "answer": "same as flip"
    },
    {
        "question": "flip through",
        "options": [
            "same as fill, ...",
            "same as flare, ...",
            "to tick off something",
            "to quickly look through a magazine or book, or to quickly look at several different television programmes"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly look through a magazine or book, or to quickly look at several different television programmes"
    },
    {
        "question": "flirt with",
        "options": [
            "to bail out of a plane, ...",
            "to focus on being an effective manager for the people you are responsible for in an organization, more than on satisfying the people who are above you",
            "to consider an idea or plan, but not very seriously, ...",
            "to make something explode, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to consider an idea or plan, but not very seriously, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "float around",
        "options": [
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ...",
            "short circuit"
        ],
        "answer": "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "flog off",
        "options": [
            "to seem to gradually change into something else",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ...",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "sell something cheaply to get rid of it"
        ],
        "answer": "sell something cheaply to get rid of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "flood back",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, machine etc",
            "criticise or insult",
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly"
    },
    {
        "question": "flood out",
        "options": [
            "if people are flooded out, their home becomes filled with water and they are forced to leave",
            "make something smart or more presentable",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident",
            "to understand or describe something exactly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if people are flooded out, their home becomes filled with water and they are forced to leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "floor it",
        "options": [
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "same as press, ...",
            "to not allow someone to enter a particular place, ...",
            "drive a vehicle as fast as possible"
        ],
        "answer": "drive a vehicle as fast as possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "flounce off",
        "options": [
            "to start to realize something",
            "same as light, ...",
            "leave a place or walk away from someone angrily",
            "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place or walk away from someone angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "flounce out",
        "options": [
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "avoid",
            "to not do something that you promised to do, ...",
            "leave a place angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "flow from",
        "options": [
            "to find a husband or wife for someone",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary",
            "to take no action when something bad is happening",
            "to be a natural result of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be a natural result of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fluff out",
        "options": [
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to move a small young plant into a larger pot or container so that it can grow bigger"
        ],
        "answer": "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air"
    },
    {
        "question": "fluff up",
        "options": [
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air",
            "to keep attacking someone or something, ...",
            "to seem to gradually change into something else",
            "to have a particular cause or origin"
        ],
        "answer": "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air"
    },
    {
        "question": "flunk out",
        "options": [
            "to have a tooth removed from your mouth or an organ removed from your body, ...",
            "same as fasten",
            "to stick firmly to something, ...",
            "to have to leave a school because your work is not satisfactory"
        ],
        "answer": "to have to leave a school because your work is not satisfactory"
    },
    {
        "question": "flush out",
        "options": [
            "if a sports game or other outside event is rained off, it does not happen because of rain",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "same as flush, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as flush, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fly about",
        "options": [
            "to attract very large audiences, ...",
            "to take someone away to a place they do not want to go",
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to succeed in doing something difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "circulate (rumours, etc)"
    },
    {
        "question": "fly around",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ...",
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "collapse, break, ...",
            "to do something without first thinking carefully about it"
        ],
        "answer": "circulate (rumours, etc)"
    },
    {
        "question": "fly at",
        "options": [
            "to make a problem seem less serious",
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "to waste time doing things that are not important or necessary",
            "to attack someone violently"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone violently"
    },
    {
        "question": "fly by",
        "options": [
            "face (of a building)",
            "to separate something into different parts or areas",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth"
        ],
        "answer": "to travel by plane, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fly into",
        "options": [
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "to attack someone violently"
        ],
        "answer": "to travel by plane, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fob off",
        "options": [
            "when something continues to happen",
            "to give someone something that is not what they want or need, ...",
            "to consider an idea or plan, but not very seriously, ...",
            "to copy a way of doing something or a system, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone something that is not what they want or need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fob off on",
        "options": [
            "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "to remain in one piece and not break apart, or to make something do this, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want"
    },
    {
        "question": "fob off onto",
        "options": [
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "same as swell",
            "look in a place to try to find something",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station."
        ],
        "answer": "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want"
    },
    {
        "question": "fob off with",
        "options": [
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to keep criticizing someone or something",
            "continue or go ahead with a project, process, plan, etc",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something of lower quality than they wanted"
        ],
        "answer": "make or persuade someone to accept something of lower quality than they wanted"
    },
    {
        "question": "focus on",
        "options": [
            "same as pass",
            "concentrate",
            "to take someone or something from one place to the place where someone else is, especially their home",
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show"
        ],
        "answer": "concentrate"
    },
    {
        "question": "fold in",
        "options": [
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ...",
            "to use a spoon or knife to add something slowly and gently to a mixture, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to use a spoon or knife to add something slowly and gently to a mixture, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fold up",
        "options": [
            "to write to an organization asking for something, ...",
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "same as fold, ...",
            "try to keep something"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fold, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "follow around",
        "options": [
            "to kill a lot of people quickly and violently, especially by shooting them",
            "same as cough, ...",
            "to follow someone wherever they go, especially in a way that annoys them",
            "to do something quickly and easily"
        ],
        "answer": "to follow someone wherever they go, especially in a way that annoys them"
    },
    {
        "question": "follow on",
        "options": [
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "to become completely understood",
            "same as ring",
            "avoid"
        ],
        "answer": "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "follow on from",
        "options": [
            "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are",
            "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose",
            "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it",
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "follow through",
        "options": [
            "have food delivered",
            "to stop doing something that is annoying someone, ...",
            "to interrupt someone while they are talking, ...",
            "to continue doing something until it has been completed, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something until it has been completed, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "follow up",
        "options": [
            "to develop something, ...",
            "same as laze",
            "to do what someone tells you to do",
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fool about",
        "options": [
            "same as get around",
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to add more information"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way for fun, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fool around",
        "options": [
            "to sing a song with someone who is already singing",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it",
            "to look at someone in a way that shows you are sexually attracted to them",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way for fun, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fool around with",
        "options": [
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to handle or use something in a stupid or careless way",
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress"
        ],
        "answer": "to handle or use something in a stupid or careless way"
    },
    {
        "question": "fool with",
        "options": [
            "leave, depart",
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "same as fool, ...",
            "to refuse to let someone come into a place"
        ],
        "answer": "same as fool, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "force back",
        "options": [
            "to become ill with a particular illness",
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something",
            "if you force back tears, you try very hard not to cry",
            "to stop something from happening, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you force back tears, you try very hard not to cry"
    },
    {
        "question": "force down",
        "options": [
            "to arrive at home or at work, ...",
            "to force a plane to land, ...",
            "to start being brave and dealing with a difficult situation",
            "behave stupidly or waste time"
        ],
        "answer": "to force a plane to land, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "force on",
        "options": [
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time",
            "same as fiddle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone accept something that they do not want"
    },
    {
        "question": "force out of",
        "options": [
            "to do a lot of activities in a short time",
            "to force someone to tell you something",
            "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to",
            "an old phrase meaning \u2018to have sex with someone\u2019, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to tell you something"
    },
    {
        "question": "force through",
        "options": [
            "same as hit on",
            "to do something so that a proposal is accepted or an issue is dealt with quickly",
            "to physically attack someone or something, ...",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something so that a proposal is accepted or an issue is dealt with quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "force up",
        "options": [
            "to put money into your bank account",
            "to make something increase",
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "to waste time, energy, or money"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something increase"
    },
    {
        "question": "force upon",
        "options": [
            "think of someone or something in a particular way",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone accept something that they do not want"
    },
    {
        "question": "forge ahead",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly stop moving or working properly",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to make strong steady progress, ...",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to make strong steady progress, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fork out",
        "options": [
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ...",
            "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to",
            "same as blank, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "form up",
        "options": [
            "if a group of people forms up, they move together in order to create a group that is correctly or tidily arranged",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ...",
            "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person",
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a group of people forms up, they move together in order to create a group that is correctly or tidily arranged"
    },
    {
        "question": "foul up",
        "options": [
            "to dig ground in order to prepare it for new plants",
            "to tie the ends of something together, ...",
            "same as foul, ...",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
        ],
        "answer": "same as foul, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "freak out",
        "options": [
            "become very disturbed or angry",
            "to buy a large quantity of something",
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "hold a grudge"
        ],
        "answer": "become very disturbed or angry"
    },
    {
        "question": "free up",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "same as free",
            "to stand up straight, ...",
            "keep quiet, say nothing"
        ],
        "answer": "same as free"
    },
    {
        "question": "freeze out",
        "options": [
            "to breathe in smoke from a cigarette, ...",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "to make something such as rope become straighter by removing it from an object shaped like a wheel that it was put around"
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent someone from taking part in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "freeze over",
        "options": [
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place",
            "to have some of a particular quality",
            "to become covered with a layer of ice",
            "to produce a series of quick loud noises or words"
        ],
        "answer": "to become covered with a layer of ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "freeze up",
        "options": [
            "to eat a particular kind of food, ...",
            "to be unable to think of anything to say, especially because you are nervous, ...",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "make very secure"
        ],
        "answer": "to be unable to think of anything to say, especially because you are nervous, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "freshen up",
        "options": [
            "to be owned by someone, ...",
            "muster, acquire, gather",
            "to become calm again, ...",
            "same as freshen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as freshen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "frighten away",
        "options": [
            "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ...",
            "to reach a decision or agreement after discussing it or arguing about it for a long time",
            "to think about something that happened in the past",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "frighten off",
        "options": [
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound",
            "same as gobble, ...",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fritter away",
        "options": [
            "if time goes by, it passes, ...",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "have negative feelings toward someone",
            "to waste time or money on things that are not necessary or important"
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time or money on things that are not necessary or important"
    },
    {
        "question": "front for",
        "options": [
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "to be a person or company that hides an illegal or secret activity for another person or organization",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "pass (time)"
        ],
        "answer": "to be a person or company that hides an illegal or secret activity for another person or organization"
    },
    {
        "question": "front off",
        "options": [
            "confront someone and let them know you are prepared to fight",
            "move to another side or place",
            "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time",
            "to say unkind things about someone when they are not there, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "confront someone and let them know you are prepared to fight"
    },
    {
        "question": "front onto",
        "options": [
            "to immediately like someone or something very much",
            "stop paying attention, ...",
            "face (of a building)",
            "to make something quickly out of whatever you can find"
        ],
        "answer": "face (of a building)"
    },
    {
        "question": "front out",
        "options": [
            "same as invite",
            "express or display emotions openly, ...",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "to begin a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "face up to someone, withstand criticism"
    },
    {
        "question": "front up",
        "options": [
            "to arrive or appear somewhere",
            "to succeed in persuading someone to agree to something, ...",
            "to suddenly attack someone violently, ...",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive or appear somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "frost over",
        "options": [
            "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone",
            "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost"
    },
    {
        "question": "frown on",
        "options": [
            "to avoid mentioning something, ...",
            "behave in a silly way",
            "to not approve of something",
            "to suddenly become unconscious, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not approve of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuck around",
        "options": [
            "give someone information, advice",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to waste someone else\u2019s time or treat them in a bad way, ...",
            "to examine or deal with something such as a problem in a particular way, ...",
            "to begin to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "an extremely offensive expression that means to waste someone else\u2019s time or treat them in a bad way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fuck off",
        "options": [
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ...",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to make someone very angry, ...",
            "to decide not to do something because you are too tired",
            "same as close, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "an extremely offensive expression that means to make someone very angry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fuck over",
        "options": [
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in a bad or unfair way",
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in a bad or unfair way"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuck up",
        "options": [
            "charge more for something",
            "to leave or go away, ...",
            "to enter a place illegally and steal things from it, ...",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to spoil or damage something completely, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "an extremely offensive expression that means to spoil or damage something completely, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "fuck with",
        "options": [
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in an unfair way or trick them, in a way that shows you do not respect them",
            "have a good relationship from the first time you meet a person",
            "take to another place quickly",
            "to continue sleeping after the time that you usually wake up"
        ],
        "answer": "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in an unfair way or trick them, in a way that shows you do not respect them"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuel up",
        "options": [
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle",
            "try to compensate for doing something wrong",
            "same as flare",
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention"
        ],
        "answer": "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuss at",
        "options": [
            "same as toss",
            "to reduce the number of possibilities or choices",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to annoy someone by frequently complaining to them about something that they do"
        ],
        "answer": "to annoy someone by frequently complaining to them about something that they do"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuss over",
        "options": [
            "to divide or share something",
            "to give a person or animal a lot of attention to show that you love them",
            "argue with someone about a specific subject",
            "forward a film or tape to a certain point"
        ],
        "answer": "to give a person or animal a lot of attention to show that you love them"
    },
    {
        "question": "gad about",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone by hitting them",
            "to be full of a happy or excited feeling",
            "to add more information",
            "visit a lot of different places for pleasure"
        ],
        "answer": "visit a lot of different places for pleasure"
    },
    {
        "question": "gad around",
        "options": [
            "have food delivered",
            "visit different places for pleasure",
            "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them",
            "do something out of a car"
        ],
        "answer": "visit different places for pleasure"
    },
    {
        "question": "gag for",
        "options": [
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner",
            "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth",
            "want something a lot",
            "to give knowledge or teach skills to your children or to younger people"
        ],
        "answer": "want something a lot"
    },
    {
        "question": "gain on",
        "options": [
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ...",
            "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house",
            "to gradually get closer to someone or something that you are trying to catch",
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually get closer to someone or something that you are trying to catch"
    },
    {
        "question": "gallop through",
        "options": [
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to finish a phone call",
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to ask someone for help, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "gamble away",
        "options": [
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to",
            "to lose all of an amount of money by gambling",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to build an extra part onto a building, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to lose all of an amount of money by gambling"
    },
    {
        "question": "gang up",
        "options": [
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "same as get around",
            "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ...",
            "form a group against something or someone"
        ],
        "answer": "form a group against something or someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "gang up against",
        "options": [
            "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing",
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ...",
            "harass, bully (in a group)",
            "have a good relationship from the first time you meet a person"
        ],
        "answer": "harass, bully (in a group)"
    },
    {
        "question": "gang up on",
        "options": [
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to join together in a group to hurt, frighten, or fight someone",
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to join together in a group to hurt, frighten, or fight someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "gasp out",
        "options": [
            "to say something while you are breathing with difficulty, for example because you need more air, or are in pain",
            "to try to hit someone or something with your hand or a weapon, ...",
            "same as open, ...",
            "if two people live together, they are not married but live in the same house and have a sexual relationship"
        ],
        "answer": "to say something while you are breathing with difficulty, for example because you need more air, or are in pain"
    },
    {
        "question": "gather in",
        "options": [
            "to stop paying attention",
            "same as drop back",
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "used about things that suddenly arrive or appear, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to collect crops from the field when they are ready"
    },
    {
        "question": "gather up",
        "options": [
            "same as fool, ...",
            "to pick up things from several different places and put them together",
            "stop paying attention, ...",
            "to show the truth or importance of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to pick up things from several different places and put them together"
    },
    {
        "question": "gear to",
        "options": [
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "to gradually start using something",
            "to attack, harm, or criticize someone who has attacked, harmed, or criticized you, ...",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)"
        ],
        "answer": "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)"
    },
    {
        "question": "gear towards",
        "options": [
            "to walk or go somewhere in a relaxed and confident way, ...",
            "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc",
            "to examine or deal with something such as a problem in a particular way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "gear up",
        "options": [
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to aim at something and move quickly and directly to it, ...",
            "if two people square up, one pays what they owe so that both people are equal, ...",
            "to move in a circle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event"
    },
    {
        "question": "gee up",
        "options": [
            "encourage people to show more enthusiasm or make more effort, ...",
            "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ...",
            "try to compensate for doing something wrong",
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "encourage people to show more enthusiasm or make more effort, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "geek out",
        "options": [
            "to gradually destroy something",
            "talk at length about computing",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to make something such as an edge or corner straight"
        ],
        "answer": "talk at length about computing"
    },
    {
        "question": "get about",
        "options": [
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "same as get around, ...",
            "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ...",
            "fire a gun repeatedly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get around, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get above",
        "options": [
            "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ...",
            "provide someone with what they require, ...",
            "behave as if you are better or more important than others",
            "to pay money into a bank"
        ],
        "answer": "behave as if you are better or more important than others"
    },
    {
        "question": "get across",
        "options": [
            "to arrive at work or school, ...",
            "to start behaving in a bad way",
            "to start crying, especially in public, ...",
            "to make people understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make people understand something"
    },
    {
        "question": "get across to",
        "options": [
            "treat someone badly, ...",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation",
            "be convincing or make a good impression",
            "to talk about something in detail, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be convincing or make a good impression"
    },
    {
        "question": "get after",
        "options": [
            "to chase someone or something, ...",
            "say something quickly without thinking, especially if you shouldn't",
            "to arrive at work or school, ...",
            "same as double, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to chase someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get ahead",
        "options": [
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to go in the direction of someone or something",
            "to build an extra part onto a building",
            "to have sex with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "get ahead of",
        "options": [
            "move in front of",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to leave a place quickly and often permanently, ...",
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "move in front of"
    },
    {
        "question": "get along",
        "options": [
            "to make a careless mistake",
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ...",
            "to leave a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get along in",
        "options": [
            "to be built, ...",
            "to arrive at a place by accident or without intending to go there",
            "to mix one substance completely into another one, usually using your hands, ...",
            "progress"
        ],
        "answer": "progress"
    },
    {
        "question": "get along with",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to find out information, especially something that someone does not want you to know",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "not think or consider"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get around",
        "options": [
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "to go or travel to different places, ...",
            "if you fix someone with your eyes, you look directly in their eyes so that they feel they cannot turn away",
            "to formally state that something is true, especially in a court of law"
        ],
        "answer": "to go or travel to different places, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get around to",
        "options": [
            "to make something happen later than it should happen, ...",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to do something after you have intended to do it for some time",
            "go out"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something after you have intended to do it for some time"
    },
    {
        "question": "get at",
        "options": [
            "to prepare something to eat very quickly, ...",
            "to lead someone to the door by which they leave a place",
            "to manage to reach or touch something, ...",
            "a way of encouraging someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to manage to reach or touch something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get away",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "ignore, exclude, ...",
            "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a person or place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get away from",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to move away from a person or place, ...",
            "to be able to understand something or to solve a problem, ...",
            "marry someone of the same ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to move away from a person or place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get away with",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone by shooting them, ...",
            "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level",
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ...",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force"
        ],
        "answer": "to manage to do something without any bad results, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get away!",
        "options": [
            "to copy someone or something\u2019s style",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "to make a noise, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to escape from a person or place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get back",
        "options": [
            "to return to a place, ...",
            "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it",
            "to represent the feelings or opinions of another person or group of people",
            "same as sketch"
        ],
        "answer": "to return to a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get back at",
        "options": [
            "become a candidate, apply for something",
            "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you",
            "pass (time)",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you"
    },
    {
        "question": "get back into",
        "options": [
            "persuade, ...",
            "to make something explode, ...",
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "find a new enthusiasm for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "find a new enthusiasm for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get back to",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to stop talking or to make less noise",
            "to phone, write, or speak to someone at a later time because you were busy or could not answer their question earlier",
            "to tell someone something that they do not expect",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone, write, or speak to someone at a later time because you were busy or could not answer their question earlier"
    },
    {
        "question": "get back together",
        "options": [
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "if two people who ended their sexual or romantic relationship get back together, they start having a relationship with each other again",
            "to reduce the speed of a vehicle by reducing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "same as spy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if two people who ended their sexual or romantic relationship get back together, they start having a relationship with each other again"
    },
    {
        "question": "get back with",
        "options": [
            "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ...",
            "same as muddle",
            "to use a hose to clean something",
            "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before"
    },
    {
        "question": "get behind",
        "options": [
            "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do",
            "to support an idea, project etc, or help someone in what they are trying to do, ...",
            "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something",
            "to be sent by post, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to support an idea, project etc, or help someone in what they are trying to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get behind with",
        "options": [
            "to stop something by taking determined action, ...",
            "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ...",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "be late paying instalments for something."
        ],
        "answer": "be late paying instalments for something."
    },
    {
        "question": "get by",
        "options": [
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ...",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way",
            "to clock off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "get by on",
        "options": [
            "to use something as a way of preventing people from discovering information about you",
            "to gradually reduce the strength, value, or importance of something",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to catch fish in a particular area of water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "get by with",
        "options": [
            "same as ring",
            "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "get down",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel very unhappy or upset, ...",
            "to write something somewhere, ...",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "use correction fluid to cover a mistake in a written text"
        ],
        "answer": "to write something somewhere, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get down on",
        "options": [
            "to keep criticizing someone or something",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "to give a baby the same name as someone else, especially a member of your family"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep criticizing someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "get down to",
        "options": [
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ...",
            "to have only a few things left to use or deal with, ...",
            "to not approve of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have only a few things left to use or deal with, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get in",
        "options": [
            "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ...",
            "waste (money, time, resources, etc)",
            "to give someone something that they owned or had before, ...",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get in on",
        "options": [
            "be submitted, arrive, ...",
            "to stop a process from working smoothly, ...",
            "to add something to something else to make it bigger or more satisfactory",
            "to become involved in something that other people are doing that is fun or interesting, or that makes money"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in something that other people are doing that is fun or interesting, or that makes money"
    },
    {
        "question": "get in with",
        "options": [
            "go to someone",
            "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ...",
            "same as ladle, ...",
            "to go or travel to different places, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get into",
        "options": [
            "do something out of a car",
            "to make people come together to form a group",
            "to arrive at work or school, ...",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive at work or school, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get it",
        "options": [
            "be punished or scolded",
            "cause something, usually unpleasant, to happen",
            "go somewhere discreetly",
            "to treat someone in an extremely unfair way"
        ],
        "answer": "be punished or scolded"
    },
    {
        "question": "get it off",
        "options": [
            "have sex",
            "to mix one substance completely into another one, usually using your hands, ...",
            "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening",
            "to make an event or activity more lively and enjoyable"
        ],
        "answer": "have sex"
    },
    {
        "question": "get it off with",
        "options": [
            "drive a vehicle as fast as possible",
            "to be similar to something from the past, ...",
            "have sex with",
            "pass or succeed easily"
        ],
        "answer": "have sex with"
    },
    {
        "question": "get it on",
        "options": [
            "fairly old, ...",
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "to make someone go away or leave a place, especially by chasing them, ...",
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fairly old, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get it on with",
        "options": [
            "have sex with",
            "same as land, ...",
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "to put someone in a room and lock the door so they cannot leave, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "have sex with"
    },
    {
        "question": "get it together",
        "options": [
            "to remain in your home for a period of time",
            "clear a table in a restaurant",
            "to be easy to see or notice because of being different, ...",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get it up",
        "options": [
            "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ...",
            "to make someone give a formal promise in a law court or at an official ceremony",
            "store up",
            "to have an erection, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have an erection, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get off",
        "options": [
            "to become covered with ice",
            "to fall asleep, ...",
            "if you put something down to a particular reason, you think it has happened for that reason, ...",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something"
        ],
        "answer": "to fall asleep, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get off it",
        "options": [
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "to try to become a member of a team or to get a part in a play or film by showing someone how well you can play or perform",
            "to secretly give the police or someone in authority information about someone",
            "a way of expressing disbelief, or telling someone that they're wrong or have an incorrect opinion"
        ],
        "answer": "a way of expressing disbelief, or telling someone that they're wrong or have an incorrect opinion"
    },
    {
        "question": "get off on",
        "options": [
            "to become mentally ill, ...",
            "same as block in, ...",
            "used for telling someone to be quiet, ...",
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way"
        ],
        "answer": "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way"
    },
    {
        "question": "get off with",
        "options": [
            "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc",
            "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "to dress or behave in public in a particular way, especially when this makes you look or seem silly"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a new sexual relationship with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "get off!",
        "options": [
            "to fall asleep, ...",
            "associate with, ...",
            "to pay for someone else\u2019s share of something",
            "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed"
        ],
        "answer": "to fall asleep, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get on",
        "options": [
            "fairly old, ...",
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth",
            "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fairly old, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get on at",
        "options": [
            "same as tune, ...",
            "pass without stopping",
            "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else",
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like"
    },
    {
        "question": "get on for",
        "options": [
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something",
            "be near a time",
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place"
        ],
        "answer": "be near a time"
    },
    {
        "question": "get on to",
        "options": [
            "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ...",
            "same as get on, ...",
            "give someone information, advice",
            "have a good time by spending a lot of money"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get on, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get on with",
        "options": [
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry",
            "same as get along, ...",
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules",
            "to start doing something new or different"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get along, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get onto",
        "options": [
            "same as put about",
            "have sex with",
            "to become involved in a fight or an argument with someone",
            "same as get on, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as get on, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get out",
        "options": [
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to manage to say something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to manage to say something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get out of",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to leave, ...",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something",
            "same as goof",
            "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to leave, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get out!",
        "options": [
            "to put a saddle on a horse",
            "to put traffic cones across a road in order to prevent traffic from going along the road",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to manage to say something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to manage to say something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get over",
        "options": [
            "to start to feel relaxed and happy, or to make someone start to feel relaxed and happy",
            "same as get across, ...",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get across, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get over with",
        "options": [
            "to search very hard for something, ...",
            "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something",
            "same as get over"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get over"
    },
    {
        "question": "get past",
        "options": [
            "to get something again that you had lost such as power, especially gradually and with difficulty, ...",
            "yield, surrender, retreat, ...",
            "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening"
    },
    {
        "question": "get round",
        "options": [
            "same as get around",
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to pay for something"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get around"
    },
    {
        "question": "get round (around) to",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone with enough force to make them fall down, ...",
            "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy",
            "finally manage to do something",
            "if a piece of clothing rides up, it gradually moves upwards on your body"
        ],
        "answer": "finally manage to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "get round (or around)",
        "options": [
            "to have existed since or for a particular time, ...",
            "if someone sitting down scoots over, they move to a different position, for example to make space for someone else to sit down",
            "same as save",
            "persuade someone"
        ],
        "answer": "persuade someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "get round to",
        "options": [
            "to try to catch or stop someone, ...",
            "to give something to each member of a group, ...",
            "same as pine",
            "same as get"
        ],
        "answer": "same as get"
    },
    {
        "question": "get through",
        "options": [
            "to use or finish something, ...",
            "same as gulp",
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly",
            "same as roll, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use or finish something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get through to",
        "options": [
            "to officially ask for something, ...",
            "spoil or ruin something",
            "to make someone understand what you are trying to say, ...",
            "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone understand what you are trying to say, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get to",
        "options": [
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ...",
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "to mention something when you are talking or writing",
            "if children act up, they behave badly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get together",
        "options": [
            "confront, ...",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ...",
            "expel",
            "go somewhere quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get up",
        "options": [
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly",
            "to write your name on an official list when you leave a place, ...",
            "to have an erection, ...",
            "to move so that there is space for someone else"
        ],
        "answer": "to have an erection, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "get up to",
        "options": [
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to do something, especially something that you should not do",
            "criticise or insult",
            "to stop paying attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something, especially something that you should not do"
    },
    {
        "question": "ghost away",
        "options": [
            "to make a problem seem less serious",
            "to meet someone or to find something without planning to",
            "be submitted, arrive, ...",
            "remove someone secretly of discreetly"
        ],
        "answer": "remove someone secretly of discreetly"
    },
    {
        "question": "gin up",
        "options": [
            "provide someone with necessary equipment",
            "same as pass, ...",
            "boost, increase or exaggerate",
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself"
        ],
        "answer": "boost, increase or exaggerate"
    },
    {
        "question": "ginger up",
        "options": [
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "become friends",
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something more interesting and exciting"
    },
    {
        "question": "give away",
        "options": [
            "same as slacken",
            "put food onto a plate to serve",
            "to tell information or facts that you should keep secret, ...",
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell information or facts that you should keep secret, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give back",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ...",
            "same as tune, ...",
            "to give someone something that they owned or had before, ...",
            "talk at length about computing"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone something that they owned or had before, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give in",
        "options": [
            "to reply rudely to someone who has more authority than you",
            "to examine a place by walking around it, ...",
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ...",
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give in to",
        "options": [
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to listen to someone who is speaking about a particular thing, ...",
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ...",
            "to pick up things from several different places and put them together"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give it to",
        "options": [
            "criticise harshly or punish someone for something",
            "to cause problems or delays for someone, ...",
            "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different",
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "criticise harshly or punish someone for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "give it up for",
        "options": [
            "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people",
            "applaud",
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "end in an unsuccessful way"
        ],
        "answer": "applaud"
    },
    {
        "question": "give it up to",
        "options": [
            "to have to leave a school because your work is not satisfactory",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "to rain very hard",
            "applaud"
        ],
        "answer": "applaud"
    },
    {
        "question": "give of",
        "options": [
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "if you give of yourself or your time, you do helpful things for people",
            "to make something using the few things that are available",
            "go to someone"
        ],
        "answer": "if you give of yourself or your time, you do helpful things for people"
    },
    {
        "question": "give off",
        "options": [
            "to produce something such as heat, light, or a smell",
            "to go to sleep very quickly because you are very tired",
            "to blame someone for something, often when they are not responsible, ...",
            "become rigid, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something such as heat, light, or a smell"
    },
    {
        "question": "give onto",
        "options": [
            "same as key",
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want",
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place"
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place"
    },
    {
        "question": "give out",
        "options": [
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to enjoy a particular thing or activity, ...",
            "to give something to several people, ...",
            "same as roll, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give something to several people, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give out to",
        "options": [
            "scold, tell off, nag",
            "to dig something out of the ground, especially with your hands",
            "to spend a lot of money on something",
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious"
        ],
        "answer": "scold, tell off, nag"
    },
    {
        "question": "give over",
        "options": [
            "to draw an X or a line through writing because it is wrong or because you have decided to write something else",
            "to stop doing something",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "to make a place tidy after someone else has made it untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "give over to",
        "options": [
            "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem",
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ...",
            "fairly old, ...",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special"
        ],
        "answer": "to use something for a particular purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give over!",
        "options": [
            "abuse someone because you're angry",
            "to stop doing something",
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "to become sober after being drunk, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "give up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel strange",
            "to stop thinking or believing something, ...",
            "exit rapidly",
            "to suddenly become unconscious, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop thinking or believing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give up on",
        "options": [
            "clock in, ...",
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "to stop hoping that you will find someone alive and stop looking for them, ...",
            "same as build, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop hoping that you will find someone alive and stop looking for them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give up to",
        "options": [
            "same as close, ...",
            "to suddenly say or shout something, ...",
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time"
        ],
        "answer": "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show"
    },
    {
        "question": "give way",
        "options": [
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ...",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to increase the price of something, especially something that you bought for a lower price, ...",
            "collapse, break, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "collapse, break, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give way to",
        "options": [
            "to clean someone or something using your hands or a brush",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers.",
            "same as check, ...",
            "yield, surrender, retreat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "yield, surrender, retreat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "give yourself up",
        "options": [
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to connect a piece of equipment such as a washing machine to the water pipes in a room so that water can flow to and from it",
            "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily",
            "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone"
        ],
        "answer": "surrender to the police or authorities"
    },
    {
        "question": "give yourself up to",
        "options": [
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something",
            "become involved in something despite opposition to your involvement",
            "to have an erection, ...",
            "same as piss"
        ],
        "answer": "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "glance off",
        "options": [
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "to not do something that you promised to do, ...",
            "to spend time relaxing or doing nothing when you should be doing something",
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "glom onto",
        "options": [
            "to say or believe that someone has a particular quality, ...",
            "same as sift",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to become firmly attached to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become firmly attached to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "gloss over",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from a surface using steam",
            "clog or overwhelm",
            "to ignore or avoid unpleasant facts",
            "make yourself comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "to ignore or avoid unpleasant facts"
    },
    {
        "question": "gnaw at",
        "options": [
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry",
            "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off",
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "gnaw away at",
        "options": [
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen",
            "pass (time)",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "go about",
        "options": [
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ...",
            "same as go around, ...",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it"
        ],
        "answer": "same as go around, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go across",
        "options": [
            "to have a particular name, ...",
            "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do",
            "move to another side or place",
            "to stand up straight, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "move to another side or place"
    },
    {
        "question": "go after",
        "options": [
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to gradually reduce the amount or importance of something",
            "to try to catch or stop someone, ...",
            "to suddenly understand or realize something"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to catch or stop someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go against",
        "options": [
            "to be opposed to something, ...",
            "to seem to gradually change into something else",
            "used for telling someone to stop talking or to make less noise",
            "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be opposed to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go ahead",
        "options": [
            "to physically attack someone or something, ...",
            "to expect something to happen and plan for it",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go ahead with",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen",
            "to remain under water, ...",
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go along",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ...",
            "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else",
            "if a spaceship blasts off, it leaves the ground"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go along with",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you, ...",
            "to agree with someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree with someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go around",
        "options": [
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere",
            "to do something that you have planned or agreed to do, especially after not being sure you want to do it",
            "to do something very quickly and not very carefully",
            "to move in a circle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move in a circle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go at",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to attack someone violently, ...",
            "to develop, ...",
            "same as stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone violently, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go away",
        "options": [
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way",
            "to stop existing or being noticeable, ...",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "if a part of a computer screen has been greyed out, the writing in it appears in a dull colour in order to show that you cannot use it"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop existing or being noticeable, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go back",
        "options": [
            "to speak angrily to someone because of something they have done wrong",
            "to have existed since or for a particular time, ...",
            "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ...",
            "to depend on someone or something for the money or food that you need"
        ],
        "answer": "to have existed since or for a particular time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go back on",
        "options": [
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do",
            "to suddenly stop working correctly, ...",
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "go before",
        "options": [
            "to have happened previously, ...",
            "to prevent people from entering an area or a building",
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them",
            "same as flare"
        ],
        "answer": "to have happened previously, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go below",
        "options": [
            "leave the top deck of a ship",
            "to put on clothes, especially quickly",
            "to be built, ...",
            "waste time"
        ],
        "answer": "leave the top deck of a ship"
    },
    {
        "question": "go beyond",
        "options": [
            "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ...",
            "to be more than something, ...",
            "to start doing something immediately, ...",
            "break the surface of soil"
        ],
        "answer": "to be more than something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go by",
        "options": [
            "have a good time by spending a lot of money",
            "same as flatten, ...",
            "if time goes by, it passes, ...",
            "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do"
        ],
        "answer": "if time goes by, it passes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go down",
        "options": [
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to put someone in prison, ...",
            "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go down on",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of someone or something, ...",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have oral sex with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "go down to",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "approach slowly",
            "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable",
            "to invest a lot of money in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go down with",
        "options": [
            "to guard, protect, or be in charge of someone or something",
            "to become ill with a particular illness",
            "break, damage or injure by hitting",
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to become ill with a particular illness"
    },
    {
        "question": "go for",
        "options": [
            "if you report to someone at work, they are in charge of you and responsible for telling you what to do",
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "to attack someone physically, ...",
            "to stop yourself from showing negative emotions like anger and disappointment, especially over a long period, so that these feelings develop in a harmful way"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone physically, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go for it",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "same as get on, ...",
            "explain the reason for a problem",
            "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')"
        ],
        "answer": "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')"
    },
    {
        "question": "go forth",
        "options": [
            "same as pen",
            "leave a place, ...",
            "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ...",
            "to escape with something, especially something stolen"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go forward",
        "options": [
            "to treat something carefully so that it stays in good condition, ...",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead",
            "progress, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "progress, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go in",
        "options": [
            "to search a person or a place very carefully, ...",
            "if information goes in, you understand it, ...",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if information goes in, you understand it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go in for",
        "options": [
            "if people are flooded out, their home becomes filled with water and they are forced to leave",
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to enjoy a particular thing or activity, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to enjoy a particular thing or activity, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go in with",
        "options": [
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "confront someone and let them know you are prepared to fight",
            "to waste time when you should be working"
        ],
        "answer": "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business"
    },
    {
        "question": "go into",
        "options": [
            "to do something that you have planned or agreed to do, especially after not being sure you want to do it",
            "to crash into something, ...",
            "used to tell someone to go away, ...",
            "to continue to do something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to crash into something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go it",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in winning or gaining something from an opponent, ...",
            "move into a lane of traffic without making other cars stop",
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "to not get a benefit that someone else is getting"
        ],
        "answer": "move or drive very fast, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go it alone",
        "options": [
            "blush",
            "do something without help",
            "to examine or read something very carefully and in a lot of detail",
            "introduce a new product; launch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "do something without help"
    },
    {
        "question": "go off",
        "options": [
            "to explain your opinion clearly and defend it in a determined way, ...",
            "same as land, ...",
            "to start to have an effect, ...",
            "to start to sleep, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to sleep, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go off with",
        "options": [
            "to leave with something that belongs to someone else, ...",
            "accept or get money without doing any work",
            "to provide people with everything they want or need",
            "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave with something that belongs to someone else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go on",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion",
            "be bored, upset or sick of something",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go on about",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ...",
            "to tell a player officially to leave the sports field because they have done something that is not allowed by the rules"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go on at",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone regularly or for a long time",
            "to make something explode, ...",
            "same as gobble",
            "to believe that something is true when it is not, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone regularly or for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "go on to",
        "options": [
            "abuse someone because you're angry",
            "same as fence, ...",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go on with",
        "options": [
            "to reach a particular number or amount",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go one",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "act in a dangerous or reckless way, especially when driving fast",
            "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ...",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do"
        ],
        "answer": "a way of encouraging someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "go out",
        "options": [
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ...",
            "to try to influence someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be sent by post, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go out for",
        "options": [
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to switch off a light, machine etc",
            "become a candidate, apply for something",
            "spiil, ruin, contaminate"
        ],
        "answer": "become a candidate, apply for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "go out of",
        "options": [
            "if a feeling or quality goes out of someone or something, they do not have it any longer",
            "to leave a group of people, usually because of a disagreement, ...",
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules",
            "to make an event or activity more lively and enjoyable"
        ],
        "answer": "if a feeling or quality goes out of someone or something, they do not have it any longer"
    },
    {
        "question": "go out to",
        "options": [
            "to fail completely, or to come to an end, ...",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special",
            "keep quiet, say nothing",
            "to be defeated by someone in a competition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be defeated by someone in a competition, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go out with",
        "options": [
            "same as pen, ...",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective"
        ],
        "answer": "to be sent by post, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go over",
        "options": [
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ...",
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to check something carefully, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go over to",
        "options": [
            "to leave or go away, ...",
            "to change to a new system or way of behaving, ...",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "to be important, or to have influence, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to change to a new system or way of behaving, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go past",
        "options": [
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "pass without stopping",
            "to continue to live or do something without having a clear idea of what you want to achieve",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pass without stopping"
    },
    {
        "question": "go round",
        "options": [
            "same as rifle",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "to begin to have an effect on someone, ...",
            "to finish drinking something"
        ],
        "answer": "to move in a circle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go through",
        "options": [
            "to make someone unconscious, ...",
            "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you",
            "to examine or search something very carefully, ...",
            "if something such as a door or window gives onto a place, it leads to that place or you can see through it to that place"
        ],
        "answer": "to examine or search something very carefully, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go through with",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "ruin or spoil something",
            "to do something that you have planned or agreed to do, especially after not being sure you want to do it",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something that you have planned or agreed to do, especially after not being sure you want to do it"
    },
    {
        "question": "go to",
        "options": [
            "sleep on something other than a bed",
            "to be given to someone or something, ...",
            "to criticize someone who has criticized you, ...",
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be given to someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go together",
        "options": [
            "if two or more things go together, they frequently exist together, ...",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "same as top up, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if two or more things go together, they frequently exist together, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go towards",
        "options": [
            "to be used to help to pay for something",
            "calculate how expensive some work is going to be",
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be used to help to pay for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "go under",
        "options": [
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to sink below the surface of the water, ...",
            "to start doing something new or different",
            "to escape with something that you have stolen"
        ],
        "answer": "to sink below the surface of the water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go up",
        "options": [
            "to be built, ...",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need",
            "be lazy, do nothing"
        ],
        "answer": "to be built, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go up to",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you",
            "to make someone tell you something by hitting them, ...",
            "to be built, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be built, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go with",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need",
            "to have sex with someone, ...",
            "to try to discover the facts about something such as a problem or a crime",
            "persuade or deceive someone into doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to have sex with someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "go without",
        "options": [
            "if information goes in, you understand it, ...",
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "to suffer extreme poverty or deprivation, ...",
            "emerge from a place in large numbers"
        ],
        "answer": "to suffer extreme poverty or deprivation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "goad on",
        "options": [
            "to encourage someone to react by making them feel very angry or upset",
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business",
            "to try to deal with or solve a difficult problem",
            "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to encourage someone to react by making them feel very angry or upset"
    },
    {
        "question": "gobble down",
        "options": [
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it",
            "used for warning someone to be careful, especially because they are likely to have an accident",
            "same as step",
            "same as gobble"
        ],
        "answer": "same as gobble"
    },
    {
        "question": "gobble up",
        "options": [
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble",
            "block, slow movement right down",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "same as gobble, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as gobble, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "goof around",
        "options": [
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them",
            "same as fall, ...",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you",
            "to spend your time behaving in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend your time behaving in a silly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "goof off",
        "options": [
            "understand something",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "to move to a particular room or place"
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time when you should be working"
    },
    {
        "question": "goof on",
        "options": [
            "tease, make fun of",
            "to no longer be reasonable, ...",
            "to take a particular amount of time, or to last for a particular amount of time",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "tease, make fun of"
    },
    {
        "question": "goof up",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to accept that something is important or true",
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc",
            "same as goof",
            "same as knock down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as goof"
    },
    {
        "question": "gouge out",
        "options": [
            "break or damage, ...",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to want something very much",
            "to remove something from a surface by cutting or digging with a sharp object"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something from a surface by cutting or digging with a sharp object"
    },
    {
        "question": "grab at",
        "options": [
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way",
            "same as turn",
            "to make something go up into the air, ...",
            "to tell or send someone information that you have discovered, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way"
    },
    {
        "question": "grapple with",
        "options": [
            "to examine a place by walking around it, ...",
            "become excited and lose control",
            "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem",
            "to wish to enter a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "grasp at",
        "options": [
            "accompany someone into an office",
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "to visit somewhere before continuing to another place",
            "to try to take hold of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to take hold of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grass on",
        "options": [
            "get someone into trouble",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to tell someone a secret"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
    },
    {
        "question": "grass over",
        "options": [
            "to believe something, usually wrongly, about someone or something",
            "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ...",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "to cover an area of ground with grass"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover an area of ground with grass"
    },
    {
        "question": "grass up",
        "options": [
            "to have some of a particular quality",
            "study something quickly, revise",
            "approach someone without their knowing",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
    },
    {
        "question": "grey out",
        "options": [
            "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ...",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "if a part of a computer screen has been greyed out, the writing in it appears in a dull colour in order to show that you cannot use it",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a part of a computer screen has been greyed out, the writing in it appears in a dull colour in order to show that you cannot use it"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind away",
        "options": [
            "to be more than something, ...",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ...",
            "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult",
            "an old phrase meaning \u2018to have sex with someone\u2019, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind away at",
        "options": [
            "to mention something so that people know about it",
            "to gradually reduce the strength, value, or importance of something",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to find and arrest people, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually reduce the strength, value, or importance of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind down",
        "options": [
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ...",
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to treat someone in a cruel way over a long period and gradually destroy their confidence or strength"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone in a cruel way over a long period and gradually destroy their confidence or strength"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind into",
        "options": [
            "to consider an idea in a way that is not serious or definite, ...",
            "press or twist something hard into something else",
            "to play in a very lively or rough way",
            "if something falls on someone, it is their responsibility to do it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "press or twist something hard into something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind on",
        "options": [
            "to reduce a number to the nearest whole number, or the nearest number ending in zero",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "if something boring or unpleasant grinds on, it continues happening for a long period of time",
            "same as brighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something boring or unpleasant grinds on, it continues happening for a long period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind out",
        "options": [
            "to produce something in large quantities, especially when this is boring or difficult",
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "to decide that something will not happen, ...",
            "used for telling someone to try harder, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something in large quantities, especially when this is boring or difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "grind up",
        "options": [
            "same as grind",
            "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ...",
            "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as grind"
    },
    {
        "question": "gross out",
        "options": [
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to support someone in a game, competition etc",
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "light a cigarette or joint"
        ],
        "answer": "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill"
    },
    {
        "question": "gross up",
        "options": [
            "to increase an amount of money recorded in financial accounts by adding an amount, usually tax, that is normally taken away when calculations are made",
            "if the rain beats down, it rains very hard, ...",
            "same as linger, ...",
            "to be more important than someone or something else, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase an amount of money recorded in financial accounts by adding an amount, usually tax, that is normally taken away when calculations are made"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow apart",
        "options": [
            "if people grow apart, their relationship gradually changes and they become less close",
            "to escape with something that you have stolen",
            "vomit",
            "to continue a journey, especially after stopping for a period of time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if people grow apart, their relationship gradually changes and they become less close"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow away from",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone in an unfair way, especially by criticizing or blaming them for something, ...",
            "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them",
            "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them",
            "to inform someone about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow back",
        "options": [
            "grow again",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "to use all of something and not have any left, ...",
            "to change your position or opinion and start supporting someone you were arguing or fighting with"
        ],
        "answer": "grow again"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow from",
        "options": [
            "be the reason for something",
            "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them",
            "to make two different things equal in amount or value",
            "to decide not to do something because you are too tired"
        ],
        "answer": "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow in",
        "options": [
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ...",
            "to begin to have more of a particular quality",
            "teach someone the specific skills they will need to carry out a job or task"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to have more of a particular quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow into",
        "options": [
            "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ...",
            "to develop and become a particular thing or person, ...",
            "to write to an organization asking for something, ...",
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to develop and become a particular thing or person, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grow on",
        "options": [
            "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly",
            "to happen, ...",
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more",
            "to leave secretly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow out",
        "options": [
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ...",
            "if coloured, cut, or permed hair grows out, it grows so that it no longer has the colour or style that it had",
            "move a student to a lower level",
            "to agree with an idea"
        ],
        "answer": "if coloured, cut, or permed hair grows out, it grows so that it no longer has the colour or style that it had"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow out of",
        "options": [
            "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ...",
            "focus more closely",
            "same as put about",
            "to forget to take someone or something with you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grow to",
        "options": [
            "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead",
            "to increase in size, ...",
            "to get things from different places or people after people have finished with them",
            "to be very happy about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase in size, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grow together",
        "options": [
            "to remain at a place longer than you had intended to",
            "gradually become attached, united or close",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "if something unpleasant sets in, it starts to happen and have an effect, and is not likely to stop for a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "gradually become attached, united or close"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow up",
        "options": [
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start existing or being seen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grow up on",
        "options": [
            "to deal with or complete something very quickly",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim",
            "to stop doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow upon",
        "options": [
            "to pay attention so that you will see something when it arrives or happens",
            "become gradually more evident, ...",
            "be as good as something",
            "to leave secretly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "become gradually more evident, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "grub up",
        "options": [
            "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective",
            "to have something as a final result, ...",
            "same as rear",
            "to dig something out of the ground, especially with your hands"
        ],
        "answer": "to dig something out of the ground, especially with your hands"
    },
    {
        "question": "guard against",
        "options": [
            "to try to prevent something from happening, ...",
            "if you are driven back by something, it forces you to stop trying to reach a person or place and move back",
            "leave something you don't like",
            "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to prevent something from happening, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "gulp back",
        "options": [
            "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them",
            "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion",
            "to begin returning to a place, ...",
            "have sex with"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion"
    },
    {
        "question": "gulp down",
        "options": [
            "same as gulp",
            "if you fit things together, you join them in the right way to make something, ...",
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference.",
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as gulp"
    },
    {
        "question": "gulp in",
        "options": [
            "same as gulp",
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "same as flush, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as gulp"
    },
    {
        "question": "gum up",
        "options": [
            "to stop a process from working smoothly, ...",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument",
            "to find out what is being done about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop a process from working smoothly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "gun down",
        "options": [
            "to shoot someone and kill them or injure them badly, especially someone who is not guilty of anything, or who is not carrying a gun",
            "get near someone",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "get into trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to shoot someone and kill them or injure them badly, especially someone who is not guilty of anything, or who is not carrying a gun"
    },
    {
        "question": "gun for",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "same as pass, ...",
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ...",
            "to oppose someone or something, especially in a brave or determined way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "gussy up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone or something more attractive or interesting, especially in a way that is intended to impress people but is not useful or necessary",
            "to become partners, or to make people become partners",
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ...",
            "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone or something more attractive or interesting, especially in a way that is intended to impress people but is not useful or necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "gut out",
        "options": [
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "to pay attention so that you will see something when it arrives or happens",
            "manage with little money",
            "to be determined to continue doing something that is difficult or unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to be determined to continue doing something that is difficult or unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "hack around",
        "options": [
            "waste time",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen",
            "same as face",
            "if animals feed off something, they eat it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "waste time"
    },
    {
        "question": "hack into",
        "options": [
            "really want something",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ...",
            "to cough loudly, ...",
            "do something quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to cough loudly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hack off",
        "options": [
            "to find out information about someone, especially secretly",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident",
            "annoy",
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface"
        ],
        "answer": "annoy"
    },
    {
        "question": "hack up",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from your throat or lungs by coughing in a loud rough way, ...",
            "to discover a fact or piece of information, ...",
            "same as rise",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a place, especially by building a wall around it"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something from your throat or lungs by coughing in a loud rough way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hail from",
        "options": [
            "sell something cheaply to get rid of it",
            "to be from a particular place",
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ...",
            "start to have a negative feeling"
        ],
        "answer": "to be from a particular place"
    },
    {
        "question": "ham up",
        "options": [
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ...",
            "to make something go up into the air, ...",
            "perform or act in an excessive way to attract attention or amuse people",
            "to prevent someone from gaining or achieving something"
        ],
        "answer": "perform or act in an excessive way to attract attention or amuse people"
    },
    {
        "question": "hammer away at",
        "options": [
            "to keep attacking someone or something, ...",
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "same as churn, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to keep attacking someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hammer into",
        "options": [
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "same as pen",
            "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it"
    },
    {
        "question": "hammer out",
        "options": [
            "to reach a decision or agreement after discussing it or arguing about it for a long time",
            "same as slacken",
            "to go or travel to different places, ...",
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them"
        ],
        "answer": "to reach a decision or agreement after discussing it or arguing about it for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "hand back",
        "options": [
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is",
            "to start living somewhere, ...",
            "to give something back to someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give something back to someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hand down",
        "options": [
            "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried",
            "same as toss",
            "rob someone at gunpoint, ...",
            "to say officially that someone should receive a particular punishment, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say officially that someone should receive a particular punishment, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hand in",
        "options": [
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to give something to a person in authority, ...",
            "to encourage someone to react by making them feel very angry or upset"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something to a person in authority, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hand on",
        "options": [
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ...",
            "to keep asking someone questions, ...",
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have",
            "to give someone something that was given to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone something that was given to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "hand out",
        "options": [
            "same as gobble, ...",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "to give things to different people in a group, ...",
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them"
        ],
        "answer": "to give things to different people in a group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hand over",
        "options": [
            "if a sound or picture fades out, or if you fade it out, it gradually disappears",
            "to use a comb to make your hair smooth or straight",
            "to give power or control to someone else, ...",
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to give power or control to someone else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hand round",
        "options": [
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way",
            "to give knowledge or teach skills to your children or to younger people",
            "to give things to different people in a group",
            "to put money into your bank account"
        ],
        "answer": "to give things to different people in a group"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang about",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ...",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "same as finish, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as hang, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang about!",
        "options": [
            "to remove all or most of your clothes, ...",
            "same as divide",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hang, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang around",
        "options": [
            "to start doing something immediately, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "put food onto a plate to serve",
            "blush"
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something immediately, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang around with",
        "options": [
            "remove by biting",
            "to turn around quickly where you are standing",
            "to swell because of an injury or illness, ...",
            "to spend time with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang back",
        "options": [
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ...",
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "do something without making much effort or trying to improve",
            "to not do something immediately because you are not confident or you do not feel certain about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to not do something immediately because you are not confident or you do not feel certain about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang back from",
        "options": [
            "affect, ...",
            "delay or avoid doing something",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing"
        ],
        "answer": "delay or avoid doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang in there",
        "options": [
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "persevere, not give up",
            "to visit somewhere before continuing to another place"
        ],
        "answer": "persevere, not give up"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang it up",
        "options": [
            "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ...",
            "retire, quit",
            "to develop or end in a particular way, ...",
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "retire, quit"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang on",
        "options": [
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to",
            "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wait or be patient, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang onto",
        "options": [
            "to take the place of someone temporarily",
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "to keep something",
            "to continue to do something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to keep something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang out",
        "options": [
            "write something quickly",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "if a building, garden etc backs onto a place, that place is directly behind it"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hang, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang out for",
        "options": [
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference.",
            "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ...",
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want"
        ],
        "answer": "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang over",
        "options": [
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force",
            "if something hangs over you, you worry about it or feel upset about it"
        ],
        "answer": "if something hangs over you, you worry about it or feel upset about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang together",
        "options": [
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle",
            "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to",
            "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized",
            "same as get around"
        ],
        "answer": "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized"
    },
    {
        "question": "hang up",
        "options": [
            "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ...",
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ...",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "criticise or nag"
        ],
        "answer": "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang up on",
        "options": [
            "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ...",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation",
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "to start working hard and seriously"
        ],
        "answer": "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hang with",
        "options": [
            "to try to find every member of a group, ...",
            "same as hang",
            "to die, ...",
            "to represent the feelings or opinions of another person or group of people"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hang"
    },
    {
        "question": "hanker after",
        "options": [
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "think about something",
            "go to someone",
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it"
        ],
        "answer": "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it"
    },
    {
        "question": "hanker for",
        "options": [
            "to say that something bad has happened, ...",
            "to try to find something",
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it"
    },
    {
        "question": "happen along",
        "options": [
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "to come to a particular place without planning to",
            "to injure someone severely by hitting them",
            "to come out of a place or thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to come to a particular place without planning to"
    },
    {
        "question": "happen on",
        "options": [
            "to prevent someone from gaining or achieving something",
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "repeatedly criticise someone verbally",
            "to meet someone or to find something without planning to"
        ],
        "answer": "to meet someone or to find something without planning to"
    },
    {
        "question": "happen to",
        "options": [
            "to work hard in order to find something",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm",
            "used for asking where something is, ...",
            "to measure an exact amount of something"
        ],
        "answer": "used for asking where something is, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hark at",
        "options": [
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "same as sketch",
            "used for showing that you are surprised, impressed, or offended by something that someone has just said",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for showing that you are surprised, impressed, or offended by something that someone has just said"
    },
    {
        "question": "hark back to",
        "options": [
            "to express your opinions loudly, especially in an unreasonable way",
            "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone",
            "to be similar to something from the past, ...",
            "same as block in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be similar to something from the past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "harp on",
        "options": [
            "to keep talking or complaining about something in a way that makes people bored or annoyed",
            "to return something that is not satisfactory",
            "to begin a new business or new type of business, ...",
            "to stop something from happening"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep talking or complaining about something in a way that makes people bored or annoyed"
    },
    {
        "question": "hash out",
        "options": [
            "to do something, especially something that you should not do",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details"
    },
    {
        "question": "hash up",
        "options": [
            "to cover something with steam, or to become covered with steam",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "to do something very badly",
            "same as rise"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very badly"
    },
    {
        "question": "hatch out",
        "options": [
            "same as hatch",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group",
            "to believe that something is effective"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hatch"
    },
    {
        "question": "hate on",
        "options": [
            "to be the reason why something exists or happens, ...",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work",
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier",
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
        ],
        "answer": "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "haul in",
        "options": [
            "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it",
            "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ...",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do",
            "same as haul, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as haul, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "haul off",
        "options": [
            "to take someone away to a place they do not want to go",
            "used for asking where something is, ...",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone away to a place they do not want to go"
    },
    {
        "question": "have against",
        "options": [
            "to gradually destroy something",
            "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ...",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private",
            "to make something accepted officially by voting"
        ],
        "answer": "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "have around",
        "options": [
            "be as good as something",
            "to put your hand into a container in order to get something, ...",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ...",
            "entertain someone in your home"
        ],
        "answer": "entertain someone in your home"
    },
    {
        "question": "have away",
        "options": [
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ...",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to exist or try to live in a situation where there are serious difficulties or problems, ...",
            "to put your hand into a container in order to get something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have sex with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "have down as",
        "options": [
            "eat something",
            "think of someone or something in a particular way",
            "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do",
            "to have an erection, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "think of someone or something in a particular way"
    },
    {
        "question": "have got against",
        "options": [
            "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ...",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "to be determined to continue doing something that is difficult or unpleasant",
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting"
        ],
        "answer": "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "have in",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place suddenly, ...",
            "if a shop has something in, it is available in the shop for you to buy, ...",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to take a particular amount of time, or to last for a particular amount of time"
        ],
        "answer": "if a shop has something in, it is available in the shop for you to buy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "have in for",
        "options": [
            "to deal with an unpleasant situation in a confident, patient, and determined way",
            "to not do something that you promised to do, ...",
            "to succeed in a very difficult situation, or to help someone to do this, ...",
            "to want to cause trouble for someone because you dislike them"
        ],
        "answer": "to want to cause trouble for someone because you dislike them"
    },
    {
        "question": "have it away",
        "options": [
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "not pay attention, ...",
            "to fail a test or a course at school, ...",
            "have sex with someone, especially casual sex"
        ],
        "answer": "have sex with someone, especially casual sex"
    },
    {
        "question": "have it in for",
        "options": [
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "hold a grudge",
            "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it"
        ],
        "answer": "hold a grudge"
    },
    {
        "question": "have it off",
        "options": [
            "to stay somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "have sex"
        ],
        "answer": "have sex"
    },
    {
        "question": "have it out with",
        "options": [
            "to measure a particular length, width, height etc, often at a point where something is to be cut",
            "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "to murder someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "have off",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "to take an opportunity that is offered to you in a very enthusiastic way"
        ],
        "answer": "to have sex with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "have on",
        "options": [
            "to die",
            "associate with, ...",
            "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ...",
            "get near someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "have out",
        "options": [
            "same as get",
            "to gradually change to a quieter or less active state, ...",
            "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with",
            "to have a tooth removed from your mouth or an organ removed from your body, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a tooth removed from your mouth or an organ removed from your body, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "have over",
        "options": [
            "if you have someone over, they come to your house to visit you or to stay with you",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ...",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident",
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball"
        ],
        "answer": "if you have someone over, they come to your house to visit you or to stay with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "have round",
        "options": [
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like",
            "to make someone leave a job or position so that you or someone else can take their place",
            "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house"
        ],
        "answer": "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house"
    },
    {
        "question": "have up",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to a court of law because they have been accused of a crime",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone to a court of law because they have been accused of a crime"
    },
    {
        "question": "head for",
        "options": [
            "emerge from a place in large numbers",
            "to become known by the public",
            "move or travel towards",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something"
        ],
        "answer": "move or travel towards"
    },
    {
        "question": "head off",
        "options": [
            "to spend time thinking about someone who you are attracted to rather than doing anything useful",
            "get money from someone under false pretences",
            "to leave, ...",
            "to start behaving in a bad way"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "head out",
        "options": [
            "go out",
            "to increase in size, ...",
            "to make someone tell you something by hitting them, ...",
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "go out"
    },
    {
        "question": "head up",
        "options": [
            "same as head",
            "be as good as something",
            "same as block",
            "to stop existing or being noticeable, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as head"
    },
    {
        "question": "heal over",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ...",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "if an injury heals over, new skin forms over it and it becomes healthy again"
        ],
        "answer": "if an injury heals over, new skin forms over it and it becomes healthy again"
    },
    {
        "question": "heal up",
        "options": [
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "be suitable, have the necessary qualities",
            "if an injury heals up, the skin or bone grows back together and becomes healthy again",
            "become rigid, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if an injury heals up, the skin or bone grows back together and becomes healthy again"
    },
    {
        "question": "heap up",
        "options": [
            "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands",
            "to become covered with a layer of ice",
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure",
            "same as heap"
        ],
        "answer": "same as heap"
    },
    {
        "question": "hear about",
        "options": [
            "to separate something from the main part by biting, ...",
            "to receive information about something, ...",
            "if a group of people crowd in on someone, they move close to them and then surround them, ...",
            "same as bring round"
        ],
        "answer": "to receive information about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hear from",
        "options": [
            "to listen to someone who is speaking about a particular thing, ...",
            "to continue encouraging and persuading someone to do something",
            "criticise someone strongly",
            "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to listen to someone who is speaking about a particular thing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hear of",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ...",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ...",
            "to receive news about someone, ...",
            "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film"
        ],
        "answer": "to receive news about someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hear out",
        "options": [
            "to decide that something will not happen, ...",
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ...",
            "to listen to someone until they have finished speaking, without interrupting them",
            "drink quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to listen to someone until they have finished speaking, without interrupting them"
    },
    {
        "question": "heat through",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "to eat a particular type of food, especially an expensive one",
            "to heat food that has already been cooked, until every part of it is very hot",
            "be good enough, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to heat food that has already been cooked, until every part of it is very hot"
    },
    {
        "question": "heat up",
        "options": [
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "to pay a particular amount of money for something",
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "same as heat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as heat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "heave to",
        "options": [
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed",
            "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to.",
            "improve a document",
            "focus more closely"
        ],
        "answer": "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to."
    },
    {
        "question": "heave up",
        "options": [
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to say that something bad has happened, ...",
            "same as heave",
            "a way of expressing disbelief, or telling someone that they're wrong or have an incorrect opinion"
        ],
        "answer": "same as heave"
    },
    {
        "question": "hedge in",
        "options": [
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility",
            "to end a letter, ...",
            "to surround someone or something, ...",
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to surround someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hedge with",
        "options": [
            "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ...",
            "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition",
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules",
            "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules"
    },
    {
        "question": "help along",
        "options": [
            "to make someone stop liking or supporting someone or something, ...",
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly",
            "to make something happen more quickly or easily",
            "to search for someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something happen more quickly or easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "help out",
        "options": [
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it",
            "to count all the things or people in a group",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
        ],
        "answer": "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money"
    },
    {
        "question": "hem in",
        "options": [
            "to enclose someone or something and prevent them from moving or leaving, ...",
            "same as wake, ...",
            "like",
            "if a particular job or duty falls to someone, it is their responsibility"
        ],
        "answer": "to enclose someone or something and prevent them from moving or leaving, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "herd together",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "spend a lot of money buying something",
            "to make people come together to form a group",
            "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make people come together to form a group"
    },
    {
        "question": "hew to",
        "options": [
            "same as charge",
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "to make something flat, ...",
            "conform, adhere"
        ],
        "answer": "conform, adhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "hide away",
        "options": [
            "criticise, find fault",
            "to put something in a place where no one can find it, ...",
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "same as drop back"
        ],
        "answer": "to put something in a place where no one can find it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hide behind",
        "options": [
            "to come from a particular place, family, or situation, ...",
            "to use something as a way of preventing people from discovering information about you",
            "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult",
            "to not leave a person or place"
        ],
        "answer": "to use something as a way of preventing people from discovering information about you"
    },
    {
        "question": "hide out",
        "options": [
            "to be built, ...",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "to go somewhere where no one can find you",
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it"
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere where no one can find you"
    },
    {
        "question": "hike up",
        "options": [
            "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it",
            "same as hike, ...",
            "to reduce the value of something by a large amount",
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hike, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hinge on",
        "options": [
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ...",
            "to depend on something",
            "to try to start a conversation with someone because you are sexually attracted to them",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it"
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hinge upon",
        "options": [
            "divert money illegally, ...",
            "to search through a collection of things in order to find something",
            "to not tell someone something",
            "depend very much or completely"
        ],
        "answer": "depend very much or completely"
    },
    {
        "question": "hire out",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need",
            "same as hire, ...",
            "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ...",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hire, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hit back",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone who has criticized you, ...",
            "to continue to do something, ...",
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ...",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone who has criticized you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hit for",
        "options": [
            "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme",
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone for something, especially money"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit it off",
        "options": [
            "share accommodation with a number of people because of the high rent",
            "to spoil something by doing it wrongly",
            "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ...",
            "have a good relationship from the first time you meet a person"
        ],
        "answer": "have a good relationship from the first time you meet a person"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit it off with",
        "options": [
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "like someone from the first time you meet them",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "like someone from the first time you meet them"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit on",
        "options": [
            "if time drags by, it seems to pass very slowly",
            "to stop doing something",
            "to suddenly have an idea, ...",
            "to develop a career or position for yourself by working hard"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly have an idea, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hit out",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ...",
            "to refuse to listen to someone, or to accept that something might be true or important",
            "to practise or learn something in a slow patient way, or to show someone how to do something",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hit out at",
        "options": [
            "to want something very much",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "to be important, or to have influence, ...",
            "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hit up",
        "options": [
            "to be completely certain of something",
            "to get ready to play a game such as tennis by hitting the ball over the net",
            "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens",
            "to blame or criticize someone in an unpleasant, unkind way"
        ],
        "answer": "to get ready to play a game such as tennis by hitting the ball over the net"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit up on",
        "options": [
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ...",
            "inject drugs",
            "if a spaceship blasts off, it leaves the ground",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "inject drugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit upon",
        "options": [
            "same as hit on",
            "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "used for telling someone to be quiet, ...",
            "to try to make people support you or buy something from you"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hit on"
    },
    {
        "question": "hit with",
        "options": [
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "to start doing something as a habit, ...",
            "to say or write the letters of a word in the correct order, ...",
            "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hitch up",
        "options": [
            "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film",
            "to hide something by putting wooden boards over or around it",
            "same as hitch, ...",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does"
        ],
        "answer": "same as hitch, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hive off",
        "options": [
            "same as spread, ...",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ...",
            "to consider something as separate from other things, ...",
            "to include something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to consider something as separate from other things, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hoe in",
        "options": [
            "emerge from a place in large numbers",
            "to ignore someone or something, or to refuse to consider them",
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm"
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold against",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "what someone is really trying to say",
            "go into the pits (car racing)",
            "to feel angry with someone, because of something that they have done in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "to feel angry with someone, because of something that they have done in the past"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold back",
        "options": [
            "same as feed off, ...",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in",
            "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ...",
            "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold back from",
        "options": [
            "same as blank, ...",
            "make an empty space inside in something, reduce power or authority",
            "not allow yourself to do something",
            "spend a lot of money buying something"
        ],
        "answer": "not allow yourself to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold down",
        "options": [
            "try to find someone for a task or requirement",
            "to succeed in keeping a job, ...",
            "to burn someone\u2019s home so that they have to leave it, ...",
            "if a shop has something in, it is available in the shop for you to buy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in keeping a job, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold forth",
        "options": [
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "to hold something so that someone else can reach it or see it, ...",
            "to prepare someone for something, ...",
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hold something so that someone else can reach it or see it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold in",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to accept less than what you are asking for",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to not allow your feelings to show, ...",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not allow your feelings to show, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold off",
        "options": [
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ...",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "to attack someone violently",
            "to stop something from happening, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop something from happening, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold on",
        "options": [
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "let, grant a service or allow usage for a fee",
            "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ...",
            "to wait, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wait, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold on to",
        "options": [
            "have sex with",
            "escape notice and be approved",
            "to hunt another creature in order to eat it, ...",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue feeling or believing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold onto",
        "options": [
            "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ...",
            "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ...",
            "leave somewhere in a defiant or pompous manner"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue feeling or believing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold out",
        "options": [
            "do something quickly",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "to continue to be enough or continue to exist, ...",
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to be enough or continue to exist, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold out against",
        "options": [
            "try to reject",
            "to move a knife or other object backwards and forwards several times across something, especially in order to cut it",
            "travel somewhere to visit",
            "to remove something that covers something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "try to reject"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold out for",
        "options": [
            "to not accept an offer because you want a better one",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "to force someone to leave a place by preventing them from getting enough food",
            "to waste time, energy, or money"
        ],
        "answer": "to not accept an offer because you want a better one"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold out on",
        "options": [
            "to give money, often without wanting to give it",
            "to not tell someone something",
            "to refuse to accept that something is important or true",
            "to murder someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not tell someone something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold over",
        "options": [
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth",
            "to hold something above someone or something, ...",
            "to start to do something in a different way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hold something above someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold to",
        "options": [
            "to ask several people for information or advice",
            "to do what you have promised or decided, ...",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do what you have promised or decided, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold together",
        "options": [
            "to take no action when something bad is happening",
            "to remain in one piece and not break apart, or to make something do this, ...",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "enter a restricted area of a computer system"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain in one piece and not break apart, or to make something do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold up",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from your throat or lungs by coughing in a loud rough way, ...",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ...",
            "to stop doing something that is annoying someone, ...",
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hold up as",
        "options": [
            "to pay for something",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "to say that someone or something is an example of something, usually something good"
        ],
        "answer": "to say that someone or something is an example of something, usually something good"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold with",
        "options": [
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to stay friendly with someone, especially someone who can help you",
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "to gain an advantage over someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to not approve of an activity or action"
    },
    {
        "question": "hole up",
        "options": [
            "same as fill, ...",
            "block, slow movement right down",
            "if you hole up or are holed up somewhere, you stay there, especially because you are hiding",
            "to spend an amount of money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you hole up or are holed up somewhere, you stay there, especially because you are hiding"
    },
    {
        "question": "hollow out",
        "options": [
            "same as come on to, ...",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ...",
            "make an empty space inside in something, reduce power or authority"
        ],
        "answer": "make an empty space inside in something, reduce power or authority"
    },
    {
        "question": "home in on",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "to aim at something and move quickly and directly to it, ...",
            "make progress, often after a pause or delay"
        ],
        "answer": "to aim at something and move quickly and directly to it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hone in on",
        "options": [
            "to give all your attention to something",
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ...",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ...",
            "if an injury scars over, it forms a scar as it becomes better"
        ],
        "answer": "to give all your attention to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hook into",
        "options": [
            "to become connected to something such as a computer network or phone system, ...",
            "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour",
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
        ],
        "answer": "to become connected to something such as a computer network or phone system, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hook up",
        "options": [
            "make something like a cushion bigger and softer by shaking it",
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "close access to a place because of bad weather"
        ],
        "answer": "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hook up to",
        "options": [
            "to have to leave a school because your work is not satisfactory",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "to phone from one part of a building to another"
        ],
        "answer": "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hoon around",
        "options": [
            "to use or do something else after other things have failed",
            "act in a dangerous or reckless way, especially when driving fast",
            "to meet someone unexpectedly, ...",
            "to criticize someone angrily for doing something wrong"
        ],
        "answer": "act in a dangerous or reckless way, especially when driving fast"
    },
    {
        "question": "hoover up",
        "options": [
            "to clean the dirt or dust from a carpet or floor with a vacuum cleaner",
            "sleep away from your home, often without planning to",
            "to spend time with someone, ...",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair"
        ],
        "answer": "to clean the dirt or dust from a carpet or floor with a vacuum cleaner"
    },
    {
        "question": "horse around",
        "options": [
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ...",
            "to play in a very lively or rough way",
            "to find a successful way of dealing with something by thinking about it",
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to play in a very lively or rough way"
    },
    {
        "question": "hose down",
        "options": [
            "to beat an opponent very easily, ...",
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "to use a hose to clean something",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls into a place, they stop there"
        ],
        "answer": "to use a hose to clean something"
    },
    {
        "question": "hound out",
        "options": [
            "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc.",
            "to talk continuously in an annoying or boring way",
            "to discuss something until you find a solution or reach an agreement",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
        ],
        "answer": "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc."
    },
    {
        "question": "hover around",
        "options": [
            "move about a place",
            "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ...",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "move about a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "howl down",
        "options": [
            "same as stop, ...",
            "same as turn",
            "to show that something is possible",
            "to stop someone from speaking or being heard by shouting loudly and angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop someone from speaking or being heard by shouting loudly and angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "hunker down",
        "options": [
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "talk too much",
            "same as lead to"
        ],
        "answer": "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hunt down",
        "options": [
            "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife",
            "to try to find every member of a group, ...",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "to travel by plane, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find every member of a group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hunt out",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a group of things into a series",
            "to search very hard for something, ...",
            "to use a comb to make your hair smooth or straight",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)"
        ],
        "answer": "to search very hard for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hunt up",
        "options": [
            "to find something or someone that is difficult to find",
            "to die, ...",
            "to suddenly find something or think of something",
            "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to find something or someone that is difficult to find"
    },
    {
        "question": "hurry up",
        "options": [
            "to want to cause trouble for someone because you dislike them",
            "to prevent an opponent from winning in a game or competition, ...",
            "to do something or move somewhere more quickly, ...",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something or move somewhere more quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hush up",
        "options": [
            "to reach a particular amount, ...",
            "to spend an amount of money, ...",
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ...",
            "used for telling someone to be quiet, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to be quiet, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "hutch up",
        "options": [
            "take to another place quickly",
            "same as fill, ...",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "share accommodation with a number of people because of the high rent"
        ],
        "answer": "share accommodation with a number of people because of the high rent"
    },
    {
        "question": "hype up",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a warning or secret information about something",
            "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is",
            "to remove a person or political party from a position by voting",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is"
    },
    {
        "question": "ice over",
        "options": [
            "to become covered with ice",
            "to make something be successful, ...",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in",
            "to build an extra part onto a building"
        ],
        "answer": "to become covered with ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "ice up",
        "options": [
            "to take control of something, ...",
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it",
            "spiil, ruin, contaminate",
            "to become covered with ice"
        ],
        "answer": "to become covered with ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "identify with",
        "options": [
            "same as show, ...",
            "to send someone to be looked after by someone else, ...",
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "fall, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "idle away",
        "options": [
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something",
            "write something quickly",
            "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing",
            "to end a relationship or a discussion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "impress on",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ...",
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to start doing something new or different"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make someone understand how important something is"
    },
    {
        "question": "improve on",
        "options": [
            "used for showing that you are surprised, impressed, or offended by something that someone has just said",
            "to remind someone of something in the past, ...",
            "to make something better than it was before, or to do something better than you did before",
            "to say something loudly and quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something better than it was before, or to do something better than you did before"
    },
    {
        "question": "inform on",
        "options": [
            "to go more slowly, especially when you are driving or running fast, ...",
            "if something dies down, it becomes much less noisy, powerful, or active",
            "same as build on",
            "to secretly give the police or someone in authority information about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to secretly give the police or someone in authority information about someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "ink in",
        "options": [
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ...",
            "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod",
            "to finish a drawing of something using ink",
            "same as drop"
        ],
        "answer": "to finish a drawing of something using ink"
    },
    {
        "question": "inquire after",
        "options": [
            "to sell something after buying it from someone else",
            "to ask someone about someone else, especially about how they are or what they are doing",
            "to think about something carefully for a long time, before making a decision about it",
            "disappear gradually"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone about someone else, especially about how they are or what they are doing"
    },
    {
        "question": "inquire into",
        "options": [
            "to ask questions and examine the answers in order to find out the truth about something",
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "choose, select",
            "to start driving in a higher gear"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask questions and examine the answers in order to find out the truth about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "inquire of",
        "options": [
            "criticise, find fault",
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "to ask someone something",
            "to begin to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone something"
    },
    {
        "question": "insist on",
        "options": [
            "to say very firmly that something must happen or must be done, ...",
            "to tell someone in authority about something bad that another person has done",
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to go somewhere or to talk to someone by telephone in order to let them know that you are ready to start working or that you are in a particular place"
        ],
        "answer": "to say very firmly that something must happen or must be done, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "insure against",
        "options": [
            "to do something to stop something bad from happening",
            "to be unable to think of anything to say, especially because you are nervous, ...",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "get something by chance"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something to stop something bad from happening"
    },
    {
        "question": "interfere with",
        "options": [
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ...",
            "if something dawns on you, you realize it for the first time",
            "to get rid of someone or something because it is no longer interesting or valuable to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "invest in",
        "options": [
            "become a candidate, apply for something",
            "if something that you do pays off, it brings you some benefit, ...",
            "to change to a new system or way of behaving, ...",
            "to use something such as time or effort for a particular purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use something such as time or effort for a particular purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "invest with",
        "options": [
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ...",
            "avoid doing something because you lack confidence",
            "to give something or someone a particular quality, ...",
            "like something"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something or someone a particular quality, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "invite along",
        "options": [
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "same as grind",
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you",
            "move or travel towards"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "invite back",
        "options": [
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something",
            "to invite someone to your house after you have been to their house, ...",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to invite someone to your house after you have been to their house, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "invite in",
        "options": [
            "to phone someone again, or to phone someone who phoned you earlier when you were away or were too busy to speak to them",
            "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ...",
            "to dig ground in order to prepare it for new plants",
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "invite out",
        "options": [
            "to mention something so that people know about it",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ...",
            "to invite someone to go somewhere such as a restaurant or cinema with you, often because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "to reach a particular amount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to invite someone to go somewhere such as a restaurant or cinema with you, often because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "invite over",
        "options": [
            "to divide something among people so that each one gets a small amount",
            "to begin a new career or way of life, ...",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "to invite someone to your house, for example for a meal"
        ],
        "answer": "to invite someone to your house, for example for a meal"
    },
    {
        "question": "invite round",
        "options": [
            "to employ someone to do a job, ...",
            "same as invite",
            "to do a lot of activities in a short time",
            "to be covered in insects, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as invite"
    },
    {
        "question": "iron out",
        "options": [
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "be near a time",
            "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ...",
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil"
        ],
        "answer": "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "issue forth",
        "options": [
            "to come out of a place or thing",
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat",
            "to happen or exist immediately before something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to come out of a place or thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "issue from",
        "options": [
            "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized",
            "clock in, ...",
            "to make people understand something",
            "if something such as a sound or smell issues from a place, it comes out from there"
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as a sound or smell issues from a place, it comes out from there"
    },
    {
        "question": "jabber away",
        "options": [
            "talk fast or incomprehensibly",
            "same as fill, ...",
            "to sink below the surface of the water, ...",
            "to start a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "talk fast or incomprehensibly"
    },
    {
        "question": "jack around",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ...",
            "to ask or persuade someone to do something",
            "to begin a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time doing stupid things, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jack in",
        "options": [
            "charge more for something",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jack up",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something for success",
            "to count things one by one, ...",
            "to refuse to obey instructions, ...",
            "visit someone for a short time."
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to obey instructions, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jam on",
        "options": [
            "pass without stopping",
            "to wish to enter a place, ...",
            "to agree with an idea",
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "jam up",
        "options": [
            "to begin a new business or new type of business, ...",
            "to discover a fact or piece of information, ...",
            "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before",
            "same as jam"
        ],
        "answer": "same as jam"
    },
    {
        "question": "jaw away",
        "options": [
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "to cover something with steam, or to become covered with steam",
            "to gradually become weaker or to disappear"
        ],
        "answer": "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say"
    },
    {
        "question": "jazz up",
        "options": [
            "to make something more lively, exciting, or interesting",
            "to pray for something bad to happen to someone",
            "same as haul, ...",
            "to prevent someone from making progress, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something more lively, exciting, or interesting"
    },
    {
        "question": "jerk around",
        "options": [
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument",
            "to behave in a stupid way, ...",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a stupid way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jerk off",
        "options": [
            "to masturbate",
            "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about",
            "to put something around something else",
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to masturbate"
    },
    {
        "question": "jib at",
        "options": [
            "to be unwilling to do or accept something",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to be suitable or right for something, ...",
            "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be unwilling to do or accept something"
    },
    {
        "question": "jockey into",
        "options": [
            "same as land, ...",
            "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "persuade or deceive someone into doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "persuade or deceive someone into doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "jog along",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to think about something unpleasant",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting",
            "make very secure"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting"
    },
    {
        "question": "join in",
        "options": [
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "to do an activity with people who are already doing it",
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems",
            "have too much work"
        ],
        "answer": "to do an activity with people who are already doing it"
    },
    {
        "question": "join up",
        "options": [
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "same as save",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "same as join, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as join, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "join with",
        "options": [
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to raise a flag to the top of a pole, ...",
            "eat or drink slowly",
            "have sex"
        ],
        "answer": "to say or do something with someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "joke around",
        "options": [
            "to make something better than it was before, or to do something better than you did before",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites",
            "be funny, or try to"
        ],
        "answer": "be funny, or try to"
    },
    {
        "question": "jolly along",
        "options": [
            "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit",
            "to leave or go away, ...",
            "to add more details about something in order to make it easier to understand or imagine",
            "to continue encouraging and persuading someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue encouraging and persuading someone to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "jolly up",
        "options": [
            "to make an event or activity more lively and enjoyable",
            "to apply to buy shares in a company",
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "be connected with"
        ],
        "answer": "to make an event or activity more lively and enjoyable"
    },
    {
        "question": "jot down",
        "options": [
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ...",
            "employ someone for something specific",
            "make a quick note",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "make a quick note"
    },
    {
        "question": "juice up",
        "options": [
            "to do the same activity for a very long time",
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something",
            "keep afloat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful"
    },
    {
        "question": "jump at",
        "options": [
            "to find something or to meet someone by chance",
            "provide something needed",
            "to take an opportunity that is offered to you in a very enthusiastic way",
            "if two people who ended their sexual or romantic relationship get back together, they start having a relationship with each other again"
        ],
        "answer": "to take an opportunity that is offered to you in a very enthusiastic way"
    },
    {
        "question": "jump in",
        "options": [
            "if a feeling wears off, it gradually disappears, ...",
            "to interrupt someone while they are talking, ...",
            "to stop working, ...",
            "go somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "to interrupt someone while they are talking, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jump into",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to leave, ...",
            "to be connected with something or to influence it",
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "to become ill with a particular illness"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jump off",
        "options": [
            "to remove something, or to be removed, by burning",
            "same as catch, ...",
            "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ...",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice"
        ],
        "answer": "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice"
    },
    {
        "question": "jump on",
        "options": [
            "same as jump, ...",
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly",
            "same as post",
            "to bring a business, organization, or project into existence, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as jump, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "jump out at",
        "options": [
            "if something jumps out at you, you notice it immediately",
            "to stop asking for something, or to stop saying that you will do something, because a lot of people oppose you",
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to not be willing to do something difficult, or to not deal with something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "if something jumps out at you, you notice it immediately"
    },
    {
        "question": "jump up",
        "options": [
            "move to another side or place",
            "to clearly need something a lot",
            "same as jump, ...",
            "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family"
        ],
        "answer": "same as jump, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keel over",
        "options": [
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "to switch on a light, machine etc",
            "to suddenly stop working correctly, ...",
            "to make someone become very excited, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly stop working correctly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep around",
        "options": [
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "keep something near you",
            "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level",
            "to hit someone with enough force to make them fall down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "keep something near you"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep at",
        "options": [
            "continue with something difficult",
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball",
            "to make a room look tidy after someone else has made it untidy",
            "to ask someone for help, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "continue with something difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep away",
        "options": [
            "to shout something",
            "to avoid someone or something, or to make someone else do this",
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument",
            "same as drop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid someone or something, or to make someone else do this"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep back",
        "options": [
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "to prevent someone from making progress, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent someone from making progress, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep down",
        "options": [
            "become gradually more evident, ...",
            "to make a noise less loud, ...",
            "same as test, ...",
            "to become fatter"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a noise less loud, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep from",
        "options": [
            "to take no action when something bad is happening",
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "same as split, ...",
            "same as burn off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not tell someone something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep in",
        "options": [
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you",
            "to copy a way of doing something or a system, ...",
            "to make someone stay in a place, especially in school as a punishment",
            "sleep on something other than a bed"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone stay in a place, especially in school as a punishment"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep in with",
        "options": [
            "to reduce an amount of something, ...",
            "same as warm, ...",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "to stay friendly with someone, especially someone who can help you"
        ],
        "answer": "to stay friendly with someone, especially someone who can help you"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep off",
        "options": [
            "ignore, exclude, ...",
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ...",
            "to slightly change something that you previously said, or to slightly change your opinion on an issue"
        ],
        "answer": "to not go onto a particular area of land, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep on",
        "options": [
            "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ...",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair",
            "to continue doing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep out",
        "options": [
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way",
            "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep out of",
        "options": [
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "criticise someone strongly",
            "to not become involved with something",
            "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not become involved with something"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep to",
        "options": [
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document",
            "same as muddle",
            "same as hang",
            "to prevent an amount or number from passing a limit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent an amount or number from passing a limit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep up",
        "options": [
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "same as share",
            "to continue to do something, ...",
            "to give something to someone officially and formally"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "keep up at",
        "options": [
            "continue, not quit",
            "to stop paying attention",
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future",
            "get money from someone under false pretences"
        ],
        "answer": "continue, not quit"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep up with",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something, ...",
            "discuss or argue an issue to improve a situation",
            "to ask someone a question, ...",
            "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "key down",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the size of a group of people or things so that you only keep the best or most useful ones",
            "to say that someone is responsible for something bad",
            "to say something in support of someone or something",
            "relax, unwind"
        ],
        "answer": "relax, unwind"
    },
    {
        "question": "key in",
        "options": [
            "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ...",
            "to ask for someone to come to you, ...",
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want",
            "same as key"
        ],
        "answer": "same as key"
    },
    {
        "question": "key in on",
        "options": [
            "if you screw up your eyes, you close them tightly, ...",
            "focus attention on, single out",
            "to deal with or organize something, ...",
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "focus attention on, single out"
    },
    {
        "question": "key on",
        "options": [
            "to be part of a particular group, or to include someone or something among a particular group",
            "target, focus on (sport)",
            "to improve, ...",
            "to cheat by not obeying the rules on something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "target, focus on (sport)"
    },
    {
        "question": "key to",
        "options": [
            "same as tone",
            "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose",
            "enter a parking area in reverse gear",
            "to remove something by cutting it"
        ],
        "answer": "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose"
    },
    {
        "question": "key up",
        "options": [
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "get as a result of something",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something"
        ],
        "answer": "make someone excited or nervous"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick about",
        "options": [
            "increase",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ...",
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "perform surgery"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kick against",
        "options": [
            "to obey a rule, law, agreement etc, ...",
            "add an additional point to something written or spoken",
            "to react against someone or something that you do not like but cannot change",
            "same as linger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to react against someone or something that you do not like but cannot change"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick around",
        "options": [
            "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ...",
            "sign a document joining or agreeing to something",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ...",
            "to leave the main part of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kick around with",
        "options": [
            "to borrow a book from a library, ...",
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to prepare something to eat very quickly, ...",
            "spend time with"
        ],
        "answer": "spend time with"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick back",
        "options": [
            "to relax",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ...",
            "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad",
            "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times"
        ],
        "answer": "to relax"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick down",
        "options": [
            "to cause something, or to produce something",
            "same as stand",
            "to go to sleep",
            "break something with your feet"
        ],
        "answer": "break something with your feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick in",
        "options": [
            "to receive news about someone, ...",
            "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens",
            "to start to have an effect, ...",
            "if a piece of cloth or clothing rucks up, or if you ruck it up, it forms untidy folds"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to have an effect, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kick in the teeth",
        "options": [
            "if something such as a deal, plan, or arrangement falls through, it fails to happen",
            "something that makes you feel very disappointed or upset, especially when you have been trying hard to achieve something",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "to try to take hold of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "something that makes you feel very disappointed or upset, especially when you have been trying hard to achieve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick off",
        "options": [
            "turn around quickly, ...",
            "to begin, or to begin something, ...",
            "entertain someone in your home",
            "have sex with"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin, or to begin something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kick out",
        "options": [
            "criticise something strongly",
            "to continue to live or do something without having a clear idea of what you want to achieve",
            "to arrange a later time for something, ...",
            "to force someone to leave a place or organization, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to leave a place or organization, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kick over",
        "options": [
            "to start to sleep, ...",
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit",
            "to kill someone with a gun, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of"
    },
    {
        "question": "kick up",
        "options": [
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "move a student to a lower level",
            "to make something go up into the air, ...",
            "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something go up into the air, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kid around",
        "options": [
            "to admit something, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "retire, quit",
            "confuse, deceive"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "kill off",
        "options": [
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "same as file",
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "to stop, get rid of, or destroy something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop, get rid of, or destroy something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kip down",
        "options": [
            "sleep away from your home, often without planning to",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours",
            "to become mentally ill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "sleep away from your home, often without planning to"
    },
    {
        "question": "kip down on",
        "options": [
            "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen",
            "to remove something from your throat or lungs by coughing in a loud rough way, ...",
            "sleep on something other than a bed",
            "same as check, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "sleep on something other than a bed"
    },
    {
        "question": "kiss away",
        "options": [
            "same as cut down, ...",
            "to help someone to get rid of feelings of sadness, worry, or anger by kissing them to show that you are sympathetic",
            "to examine or search something very carefully, ...",
            "to interrupt someone while they are talking, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to help someone to get rid of feelings of sadness, worry, or anger by kissing them to show that you are sympathetic"
    },
    {
        "question": "kiss off",
        "options": [
            "visit a place to check something",
            "to forget to take someone or something with you, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "used to tell someone to go away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used to tell someone to go away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "kiss up to",
        "options": [
            "same as tape",
            "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ...",
            "to try to please a powerful person, because you want them to do something for you",
            "become involved, often against one\ufffds will"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to please a powerful person, because you want them to do something for you"
    },
    {
        "question": "knock about",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone a lot, ...",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ...",
            "to suddenly leave your wife, husband, or partner",
            "same as deal, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit someone a lot, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock around",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone a lot, ...",
            "to try to discover the facts about something such as a problem or a crime",
            "to listen carefully to try and hear a sound",
            "to suddenly let something bad or unpleasant have its full effect on someone or something in an uncontrolled way"
        ],
        "answer": "to hit someone a lot, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock back",
        "options": [
            "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it",
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer",
            "to cause problems or delays for someone, ...",
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to cause problems or delays for someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock down",
        "options": [
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ...",
            "to say that someone is responsible for something bad",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce a price or amount, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock it off!",
        "options": [
            "stop doing something annoying",
            "go out",
            "to start to criticize or blame someone angrily, ...",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
        ],
        "answer": "stop doing something annoying"
    },
    {
        "question": "knock off",
        "options": [
            "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ...",
            "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens",
            "to stop working, ...",
            "to find out whether information is accurate or useful by comparing it with other information"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop working, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock out",
        "options": [
            "be near a time",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job, ...",
            "to make someone unconscious, ...",
            "same as cover, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone unconscious, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock over",
        "options": [
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "same as pour",
            "same as put, ...",
            "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket"
        ],
        "answer": "same as knock down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock together",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them",
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something quickly and easily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knock up",
        "options": [
            "appear",
            "same as call, ...",
            "same as knock, ...",
            "try to maintain beliefs, hopes, etc."
        ],
        "answer": "same as knock, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "know from",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use",
            "to do what someone tells you to do",
            "to provide something that is needed or wanted",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things"
        ],
        "answer": "to recognize the difference between two people or things"
    },
    {
        "question": "know of",
        "options": [
            "to know about someone or something, but not know any details, ...",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "to stop doing something for a period of time, ...",
            "to press a cigarette hard against a surface to make it stop burning"
        ],
        "answer": "to know about someone or something, but not know any details, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "knuckle down",
        "options": [
            "to gradually start using something",
            "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen",
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier",
            "to search a person or a place very carefully, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier"
    },
    {
        "question": "knuckle under",
        "options": [
            "same as catch, ...",
            "to be or become stuck in soft wet ground, ...",
            "to get rid of someone or something, ...",
            "to do what someone tells you to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to do what someone tells you to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "labour under",
        "options": [
            "to exist or try to live in a situation where there are serious difficulties or problems, ...",
            "have a good time by spending a lot of money",
            "to not leave a person or place",
            "to remain in your home for a period of time"
        ],
        "answer": "to exist or try to live in a situation where there are serious difficulties or problems, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ladle out",
        "options": [
            "to hunt another creature in order to eat it, ...",
            "same as ladle, ...",
            "to be very obvious or noticeable, ...",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a boring and annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "same as ladle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "land in",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something for success",
            "to bring a plane down to the ground, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to start to do something in a different way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to bring a plane down to the ground, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "land on",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone severely",
            "same as bundle, ...",
            "to be part of a particular group, or to include someone or something among a particular group",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone severely"
    },
    {
        "question": "land up",
        "options": [
            "same as land, ...",
            "to try hard to develop or improve something",
            "criticise something strongly",
            "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as land, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "land up in",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly stop talking or explaining something, because you are embarrassed, unhappy, or want to keep a secret",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ...",
            "to try to find or catch someone, usually in order to punish or harm them",
            "arrive, end a journey in a place, often without planning"
        ],
        "answer": "arrive, end a journey in a place, often without planning"
    },
    {
        "question": "land with",
        "options": [
            "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it",
            "same as burn off, ...",
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ...",
            "to give someone an unpleasant job that no one else wants to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone an unpleasant job that no one else wants to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "lap up",
        "options": [
            "same as lap, ...",
            "to treat someone in an extremely unfair way",
            "marry someone of the same ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "to keep attacking someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as lap, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lapse into",
        "options": [
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it",
            "to gradually change to a quieter or less active state, ...",
            "to be shocked by something",
            "revise"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually change to a quieter or less active state, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "large it up",
        "options": [
            "to try to start a conversation with someone because you are sexually attracted to them",
            "have a good time when intoxicated",
            "same as curl, ...",
            "same as tally"
        ],
        "answer": "have a good time when intoxicated"
    },
    {
        "question": "lark about",
        "options": [
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ...",
            "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ...",
            "behave in a silly way",
            "same as tumble, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "behave in a silly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "lark around",
        "options": [
            "fill a venue",
            "to move away from someone or something, ...",
            "to have confidence in someone or something",
            "behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "behave in a silly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "lark it up",
        "options": [
            "to draw a line through something on a list to show that you have dealt with it",
            "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly",
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen",
            "to tell a player officially to leave the sports field because they have done something that is not allowed by the rules"
        ],
        "answer": "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly"
    },
    {
        "question": "lash down",
        "options": [
            "pass quickly",
            "to behave in a stupid way, ...",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force",
            "to suddenly attack someone violently, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force"
    },
    {
        "question": "lash into",
        "options": [
            "criticise someone strongly",
            "mean, try to say",
            "to agree with someone or something, ...",
            "criticise harshly or punish someone for something"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise someone strongly"
    },
    {
        "question": "lash out",
        "options": [
            "make very secure",
            "to say or write the letters of a word in the correct order, ...",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to stop the flow of something, usually water or electricity, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of money on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lash out against",
        "options": [
            "criticise something strongly",
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want",
            "to continue to do or use something, and not change it, ...",
            "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise something strongly"
    },
    {
        "question": "lash out at",
        "options": [
            "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them",
            "do a lot to try to help or please someone",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of money on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lash out on",
        "options": [
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "to start a journey by ship, ...",
            "spend a lot of money buying something",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise"
        ],
        "answer": "spend a lot of money buying something"
    },
    {
        "question": "last out",
        "options": [
            "to reach a decision or agreement after discussing it or arguing about it for a long time",
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to be enough for what people need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "latch on",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly understand or realize something",
            "if a piece of clothing rides up, it gradually moves upwards on your body",
            "same as tangle",
            "to start driving in a higher gear"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly understand or realize something"
    },
    {
        "question": "latch on to",
        "options": [
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "understand something, often after a long time",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to be lucky"
        ],
        "answer": "understand something, often after a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "latch onto",
        "options": [
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ...",
            "to go with someone who does not want to be with you, ...",
            "to officially ask for something, ...",
            "to make someone feel very annoyed or upset"
        ],
        "answer": "to go with someone who does not want to be with you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "laugh at",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of something, ...",
            "to say unkind things about someone when they are not there, ...",
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say unkind things about someone when they are not there, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "laugh off",
        "options": [
            "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ...",
            "to joke about something in order to show that you think it is not important or serious",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to"
        ],
        "answer": "to joke about something in order to show that you think it is not important or serious"
    },
    {
        "question": "launch into",
        "options": [
            "same as feed off, ...",
            "to lie down, or to put someone else into a bed or another place to sleep",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm",
            "to move things so that they are in different places or positions"
        ],
        "answer": "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm"
    },
    {
        "question": "launch out",
        "options": [
            "approach someone discreetly",
            "to turn the pages of a book, newspaper, or magazine quickly without reading or looking at it carefully. The usual British word is leaf through",
            "eat a big meal, ...",
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay about",
        "options": [
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "charge more for something",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to attack someone by hitting them"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone by hitting them"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay aside",
        "options": [
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ...",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way",
            "to talk too much, ...",
            "to promise to stop doing or using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lay before",
        "options": [
            "to beat someone in something such as a competition or election by a small amount",
            "to think that something will happen and plan for it",
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc",
            "behave as if you are better or more important than others"
        ],
        "answer": "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay down",
        "options": [
            "a way of saying \u2018lie down\u2019 that many people think is incorrect, ...",
            "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone",
            "sleep somewhere for the night",
            "pay attention after not doing so"
        ],
        "answer": "a way of saying \u2018lie down\u2019 that many people think is incorrect, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lay in",
        "options": [
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "if something gets chewed up, it becomes torn apart and destroyed, ...",
            "to get and keep a supply of something such as food to use in the future",
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to get and keep a supply of something such as food to use in the future"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay into",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "teach someone the specific skills they will need to carry out a job or task",
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them",
            "to find a job easily, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay off",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something that is annoying someone, ...",
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "same as share",
            "to begin an attack in boxing with a particular hand or hit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something that is annoying someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lay on",
        "options": [
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ...",
            "to call out loudly, ...",
            "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc.",
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lay out",
        "options": [
            "to think about something carefully or discuss it carefully with other people before making a decision about it",
            "to increase something, ...",
            "to spend an amount of money, ...",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend an amount of money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lay to",
        "options": [
            "if you lay a ship to, or if it lays to, it stops",
            "to remove something from a list or record, ...",
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "if you lay a ship to, or if it lays to, it stops"
    },
    {
        "question": "lay up",
        "options": [
            "to invite someone to your house after you have been to their house, ...",
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to shout loudly in order to encourage someone",
            "to try to influence someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as lay, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "laze around",
        "options": [
            "to enjoy something very much",
            "to plant young plants outdoors",
            "same as laze",
            "to write something again exactly as it has been written"
        ],
        "answer": "same as laze"
    },
    {
        "question": "laze away",
        "options": [
            "same as tail off",
            "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you",
            "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work"
    },
    {
        "question": "lead into",
        "options": [
            "same as freshen, ...",
            "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement",
            "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort",
            "same as lead to"
        ],
        "answer": "same as lead to"
    },
    {
        "question": "lead off",
        "options": [
            "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are",
            "invest in something",
            "to begin something by doing or saying something",
            "to tick off something"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin something by doing or saying something"
    },
    {
        "question": "lead on",
        "options": [
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ...",
            "to take out, ...",
            "same as tape",
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have"
        ],
        "answer": "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have"
    },
    {
        "question": "lead on to",
        "options": [
            "if a missile or a vehicle carrying missiles locks onto something, it finds out its position and prepares to destroy it",
            "same as lead to",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them",
            "to use a comb to make your hair smooth or straight"
        ],
        "answer": "same as lead to"
    },
    {
        "question": "lead to",
        "options": [
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "to be more than something, ...",
            "grow again",
            "to make someone think something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone think something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lead up to",
        "options": [
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc",
            "same as pick, ...",
            "to happen or exist immediately before something, ...",
            "to make people understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen or exist immediately before something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lead with",
        "options": [
            "to begin an attack in boxing with a particular hand or hit, ...",
            "to not go to bed",
            "to stop criticizing someone or telling them what to do, ...",
            "to give something, such as food or money, to a particular group of people or to every person in a group"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin an attack in boxing with a particular hand or hit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "leak out",
        "options": [
            "same as lock",
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to become known by the public",
            "to start to win or increase quickly and easily"
        ],
        "answer": "to become known by the public"
    },
    {
        "question": "lean on",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ...",
            "to officially ask a court for something, for example ask them to give you a divorce or state officially that you are bankrupt",
            "try to find someone for a task or requirement",
            "to depend on someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "leap at",
        "options": [
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them",
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "to give someone something such as a look, smile, or answer to a question"
        ],
        "answer": "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention"
    },
    {
        "question": "leap in",
        "options": [
            "to make something using the few things that are available",
            "to manage to say something, ...",
            "to do something immediately, and often with enthusiasm, as soon as you have the chance to do it",
            "to move in a circle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something immediately, and often with enthusiasm, as soon as you have the chance to do it"
    },
    {
        "question": "leap on",
        "options": [
            "to start having a conversation with someone, ...",
            "to cause problems for someone, ...",
            "leave something you don't like",
            "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something"
    },
    {
        "question": "leap out at",
        "options": [
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ...",
            "to speak in an angry way to someone who has done something wrong, ...",
            "when an aircraft or space vehicle lifts off, it goes up from the ground into the air"
        ],
        "answer": "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention"
    },
    {
        "question": "leap upon",
        "options": [
            "sleep away from your home, often without planning to",
            "end in an unsuccessful way",
            "visit someone for a short time.",
            "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something"
    },
    {
        "question": "leave aside",
        "options": [
            "to provide something for someone, ...",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you have arrived at work",
            "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead",
            "to produce something in large quantities quickly and often carelessly"
        ],
        "answer": "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead"
    },
    {
        "question": "leave behind",
        "options": [
            "same as light, ...",
            "to use a piece of software continuously to check for problems",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to forget to take someone or something with you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to forget to take someone or something with you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "leave off",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something",
            "same as connect, ...",
            "to become fatter",
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "leave on",
        "options": [
            "if a regular event comes round, it happens again, ...",
            "not turn off",
            "to have something as a final result, ...",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married"
        ],
        "answer": "not turn off"
    },
    {
        "question": "leave out",
        "options": [
            "store or hide something in a safe place",
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language",
            "to not include someone or something, ...",
            "applaud"
        ],
        "answer": "to not include someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "leave over",
        "options": [
            "same as tighten, ...",
            "to still exist from the past, ...",
            "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ...",
            "if a missile or a vehicle carrying missiles locks onto something, it finds out its position and prepares to destroy it"
        ],
        "answer": "to still exist from the past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let down",
        "options": [
            "mess up, ruin",
            "to eat food, especially a lot of food, quickly or in an enthusiastic way",
            "same as hang",
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let in",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "if something boring or unpleasant grinds on, it continues happening for a long period of time",
            "to behave according to a particular set of beliefs or principles",
            "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let in on",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone a secret",
            "to divide or share something",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ...",
            "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone a secret"
    },
    {
        "question": "let into",
        "options": [
            "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ...",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "same as let, ...",
            "to treat someone badly and in an unfair way, especially by giving them orders"
        ],
        "answer": "same as let, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let off",
        "options": [
            "to dig holes in an area of land, ...",
            "to use a spoon or knife to add something slowly and gently to a mixture, ...",
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people",
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fire a gun or bullet, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let on",
        "options": [
            "to try to become a member of a team or to get a part in a play or film by showing someone how well you can play or perform",
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ...",
            "to admit something, ...",
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something"
        ],
        "answer": "to admit something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let out",
        "options": [
            "to make a noise, ...",
            "to stop doing something",
            "to make someone understand what you are trying to say, ...",
            "to develop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a noise, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "let up",
        "options": [
            "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you",
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ...",
            "same as button, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "level at",
        "options": [
            "to fix a picture to a wall, ...",
            "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ...",
            "to point a weapon at someone, ...",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence"
        ],
        "answer": "to point a weapon at someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "level off",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place quickly or suddenly",
            "to make something flat, ...",
            "break a piece off something",
            "same as lock away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something flat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "level out",
        "options": [
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to not include someone or something, ...",
            "to make something flat, ...",
            "same as check, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something flat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "level up",
        "options": [
            "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "burn brightly",
            "same as stay, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type"
    },
    {
        "question": "level with",
        "options": [
            "to be honest with someone",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you or to be friendly to you",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ...",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "to be honest with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "lie about",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ...",
            "same as polish",
            "to deal with something or someone, ...",
            "approach slowly"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lie ahead",
        "options": [
            "scold, tell off, nag",
            "to force or persuade someone to tell you something when they do not want to",
            "to remain under water, ...",
            "if something lies ahead, especially something difficult or unpleasant, it is going to happen in the future and you will have to deal with it"
        ],
        "answer": "if something lies ahead, especially something difficult or unpleasant, it is going to happen in the future and you will have to deal with it"
    },
    {
        "question": "lie around",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ...",
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to",
            "to improve, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lie back",
        "options": [
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ...",
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "to suddenly understand or realize something"
        ],
        "answer": "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "lie behind",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "to make something using the few things that are available",
            "to be the real reason for a decision or action"
        ],
        "answer": "to be the real reason for a decision or action"
    },
    {
        "question": "lie down",
        "options": [
            "same as lie, ...",
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ...",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "same as lie, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lie in",
        "options": [
            "to decide or agree on something, ...",
            "same as double",
            "to stay in bed in the morning for longer than usual",
            "if something dries out or is dried out, some or all the water comes out of it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stay in bed in the morning for longer than usual"
    },
    {
        "question": "lie with",
        "options": [
            "lower the top part of your body",
            "to go away, or to leave",
            "an old phrase meaning \u2018to have sex with someone\u2019, ...",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm"
        ],
        "answer": "an old phrase meaning \u2018to have sex with someone\u2019, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lift off",
        "options": [
            "produce or issue, usually from a machine",
            "when an aircraft or space vehicle lifts off, it goes up from the ground into the air",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to put a saddle on a horse"
        ],
        "answer": "when an aircraft or space vehicle lifts off, it goes up from the ground into the air"
    },
    {
        "question": "lift up",
        "options": [
            "understand something, often after a long time",
            "to admit that you have done something bad or embarrassing",
            "to stop the flow of something, usually water or electricity, ...",
            "same as lift"
        ],
        "answer": "same as lift"
    },
    {
        "question": "light on",
        "options": [
            "short circuit",
            "to connect one thing or person to another, ...",
            "to suddenly find something or think of something",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly find something or think of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "light out",
        "options": [
            "leave suddenly",
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it",
            "to get rid of someone or something because it is no longer interesting or valuable to you"
        ],
        "answer": "leave suddenly"
    },
    {
        "question": "light up",
        "options": [
            "revise",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "make it clear you are sexually attracted to someone",
            "same as light, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as light, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lighten up",
        "options": [
            "same as lap, ...",
            "do something quickly",
            "pass (time)",
            "same as lighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as lighten, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "limber up",
        "options": [
            "have sex with",
            "to do gentle exercises that make your muscles stretch, especially in order to prepare for taking part in a sport",
            "to talk quickly and for a long time",
            "treat someone badly"
        ],
        "answer": "to do gentle exercises that make your muscles stretch, especially in order to prepare for taking part in a sport"
    },
    {
        "question": "limber up for",
        "options": [
            "prepare for something that will require a great effort",
            "if something falls on someone, it is their responsibility to do it, ...",
            "if time goes by, it passes, ...",
            "to cost a particular amount"
        ],
        "answer": "prepare for something that will require a great effort"
    },
    {
        "question": "line up",
        "options": [
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc",
            "to form a row, or to put people or things in a row, ...",
            "same as broaden",
            "to listen carefully to try and hear a sound"
        ],
        "answer": "to form a row, or to put people or things in a row, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "linger on",
        "options": [
            "try to keep something",
            "if a sound or picture fades in, or if you fade it in, it gradually becomes louder or clearer",
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "same as linger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as linger, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "link up",
        "options": [
            "to make a place smell very unpleasant",
            "to connect one thing or person to another, ...",
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people",
            "same as put aside"
        ],
        "answer": "to connect one thing or person to another, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "link up with",
        "options": [
            "to make someone give a formal promise in a law court or at an official ceremony",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility",
            "connect with someone or contact them",
            "to earn a lot of money"
        ],
        "answer": "connect with someone or contact them"
    },
    {
        "question": "listen in",
        "options": [
            "same as spread, ...",
            "to relax",
            "to listen to a radio programme, ...",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to listen to a radio programme, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "listen out for",
        "options": [
            "same as lock",
            "to get ready to play a game such as tennis by hitting the ball over the net",
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time, ...",
            "to listen carefully to try and hear a sound"
        ],
        "answer": "to listen carefully to try and hear a sound"
    },
    {
        "question": "listen up",
        "options": [
            "to do something because you have been given information, advice, or orders",
            "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ...",
            "used for getting the attention of a noisy group of people"
        ],
        "answer": "used for getting the attention of a noisy group of people"
    },
    {
        "question": "live by",
        "options": [
            "to not tell someone something",
            "to begin a new career or way of life, ...",
            "to behave according to a particular set of beliefs or principles",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave according to a particular set of beliefs or principles"
    },
    {
        "question": "live down",
        "options": [
            "think of someone or something in a particular way",
            "to make something by joining all its parts, ...",
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "to make people forget about something embarrassing or silly that you have done"
        ],
        "answer": "to make people forget about something embarrassing or silly that you have done"
    },
    {
        "question": "live for",
        "options": [
            "to want something to happen very much, ...",
            "same as chill",
            "enter a place quickly",
            "make a fire burn less, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to want something to happen very much, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "live in",
        "options": [
            "leave a place quietly or secretly",
            "to live at the place where you work or study",
            "to make people understand something",
            "to press hard into something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to live at the place where you work or study"
    },
    {
        "question": "live it up",
        "options": [
            "to invite someone to your house, for example for a meal",
            "same as tidy, ...",
            "have a good time by spending a lot of money",
            "to not allow your feelings to show, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "have a good time by spending a lot of money"
    },
    {
        "question": "live off",
        "options": [
            "to depend on someone or something for the money or food that you need",
            "to trick someone by pretending something or by behaving dishonestly",
            "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket",
            "to lose all of an amount of money by gambling"
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on someone or something for the money or food that you need"
    },
    {
        "question": "live on",
        "options": [
            "move in a place making a lot of noise",
            "to have existed since or for a particular time, ...",
            "to sit or lie with your body against someone else\u2019s because you want to feel warm, protected, or loved",
            "to eat a particular kind of food, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to eat a particular kind of food, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "live out",
        "options": [
            "to not live at the place where you work or study, ...",
            "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it",
            "to clean the inside of something thoroughly",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice"
        ],
        "answer": "to not live at the place where you work or study, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "live through",
        "options": [
            "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it",
            "to leave a place, usually suddenly",
            "do something slowly, with difficulty, unwillingly or considerable effort",
            "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose"
        ],
        "answer": "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it"
    },
    {
        "question": "live together",
        "options": [
            "if two people live together, they are not married but live in the same house and have a sexual relationship",
            "to give power or control to someone else, ...",
            "to realize or understand something",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people live together, they are not married but live in the same house and have a sexual relationship"
    },
    {
        "question": "live up to",
        "options": [
            "to be as good as what was expected or promised",
            "to go back to an activity after an interruption, ...",
            "criticise angrily",
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it"
        ],
        "answer": "to be as good as what was expected or promised"
    },
    {
        "question": "live with",
        "options": [
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ...",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "try to find someone for a task or requirement",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "liven up",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them",
            "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family",
            "to lose all of an amount of money by gambling",
            "to give something a more interesting appearance, taste, or other quality, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give something a more interesting appearance, taste, or other quality, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "load down",
        "options": [
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "same as catch, ...",
            "improve your knowledge quickly",
            "if you are loaded down with a lot of heavy things, you are carrying them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you are loaded down with a lot of heavy things, you are carrying them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "load up",
        "options": [
            "same as load",
            "put something in a liquid for a short time",
            "to go to bed at night, ...",
            "to continue for longer than expected or planned, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as load"
    },
    {
        "question": "load up on",
        "options": [
            "to ring bells to celebrate the beginning of a new year, ...",
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "to buy a lot of something so that it is available when you need it",
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to buy a lot of something so that it is available when you need it"
    },
    {
        "question": "lock away",
        "options": [
            "same as slow, ...",
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ...",
            "pay a debt over time",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time"
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lock down",
        "options": [
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "to clean someone or something using your hands or a brush",
            "make very secure",
            "have sex"
        ],
        "answer": "make very secure"
    },
    {
        "question": "lock in",
        "options": [
            "to put someone in a room and lock the door so they cannot leave, ...",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen",
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "to make strong steady progress, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put someone in a room and lock the door so they cannot leave, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lock in on",
        "options": [
            "same as lock",
            "to organize data (=computer information) according to different levels of detail, each level more detailed than the previous one",
            "to start to win or increase quickly and easily",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as lock"
    },
    {
        "question": "lock into",
        "options": [
            "to move towards a place, ...",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it",
            "invite someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it"
    },
    {
        "question": "lock onto",
        "options": [
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc",
            "to try to achieve a particular thing",
            "if a missile or a vehicle carrying missiles locks onto something, it finds out its position and prepares to destroy it"
        ],
        "answer": "if a missile or a vehicle carrying missiles locks onto something, it finds out its position and prepares to destroy it"
    },
    {
        "question": "lock out",
        "options": [
            "to become friends with someone, ...",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "same as truss, ...",
            "to prevent someone from coming into a room or building by locking the door, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent someone from coming into a room or building by locking the door, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lock up",
        "options": [
            "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it",
            "same as lock away, ...",
            "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way"
        ],
        "answer": "same as lock away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lock yourself away",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ...",
            "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "go somewhere away from people to study or work",
            "to stop the continuation of a court case, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere away from people to study or work"
    },
    {
        "question": "log in",
        "options": [
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word",
            "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else",
            "to continue feeling or believing something, ...",
            "to be more than something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word"
    },
    {
        "question": "log into",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place to the place where someone else is, especially their home",
            "plead guilty to get a reduced sentence or fine",
            "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ...",
            "enter a restricted area of a computer system"
        ],
        "answer": "enter a restricted area of a computer system"
    },
    {
        "question": "log off",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "to attract very large audiences, ...",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way",
            "let down, snub"
        ],
        "answer": "to finish your working day, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "log on",
        "options": [
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word",
            "to succeed in a very difficult situation, or to help someone to do this, ...",
            "to die, ...",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident"
        ],
        "answer": "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word"
    },
    {
        "question": "log out",
        "options": [
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "same as strike on",
            "to finish your working day, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to finish your working day, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look after",
        "options": [
            "to be responsible for something, ...",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ...",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)"
        ],
        "answer": "to be responsible for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look ahead",
        "options": [
            "to think about what is likely to happen, or to plan what you are going to do in the future",
            "to persuade someone to lower the price of something, ...",
            "to try to prevent something from happening, ...",
            "to draw a line through written words"
        ],
        "answer": "to think about what is likely to happen, or to plan what you are going to do in the future"
    },
    {
        "question": "look around",
        "options": [
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ...",
            "to pretend that you have not noticed something or do not know about it, because you do not approve of it",
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something that you want or need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look at",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way",
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "if a ship puts in, it stops at a port, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "not very attractive, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look back",
        "options": [
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way",
            "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times",
            "to think about a time or event in the past, ...",
            "store or hide something in a safe place"
        ],
        "answer": "to think about a time or event in the past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look down on",
        "options": [
            "to think that you are better or more important than someone else, or to think that something is not good enough for you",
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "to refuse to accept or continue something"
        ],
        "answer": "to think that you are better or more important than someone else, or to think that something is not good enough for you"
    },
    {
        "question": "look for",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "to search for someone or something, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ...",
            "to send someone to prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to search for someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look forward to",
        "options": [
            "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers.",
            "treat someone badly",
            "if a vehicle moves off, it starts to move"
        ],
        "answer": "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "look in",
        "options": [
            "check in at a hotel, ...",
            "remove quickly, ...",
            "continue, not quit",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
        ],
        "answer": "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
    },
    {
        "question": "look in on",
        "options": [
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ...",
            "to break a door or gate in order to get through it",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
        ],
        "answer": "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help"
    },
    {
        "question": "look into",
        "options": [
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something",
            "to try to discover the facts about something such as a problem or a crime",
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to discover the facts about something such as a problem or a crime"
    },
    {
        "question": "look on",
        "options": [
            "reach inside something quickly",
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "to not approve of something, ...",
            "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc."
        ],
        "answer": "to not approve of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look on as",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "to make strong steady progress, ...",
            "to not approve of something, ...",
            "to examine something, usually quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not approve of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look out",
        "options": [
            "used for warning someone to be careful, especially because they are likely to have an accident",
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "same as bust, ...",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for warning someone to be careful, especially because they are likely to have an accident"
    },
    {
        "question": "look out for",
        "options": [
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen",
            "focus more closely",
            "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look over",
        "options": [
            "to produce a loud clear sound",
            "to ask questions and examine the answers in order to find out the truth about something",
            "to examine something, usually quickly, ...",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to examine something, usually quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look round",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ...",
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized",
            "to express your opinions loudly, especially in an unreasonable way",
            "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something that you want or need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look through",
        "options": [
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "same as bust, ...",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "to search for something among a lot of other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to search for something among a lot of other things, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look to",
        "options": [
            "to direct your thoughts or attention to something, ...",
            "to try to bite something without in fact managing to bite it",
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like",
            "to have something as a final result, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to direct your thoughts or attention to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look up",
        "options": [
            "to wait for something to happen, usually noticing every day or moment that passes until it happens",
            "to serve food, ...",
            "if a situation is looking up, it is getting better, ...",
            "same as cover, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation is looking up, it is getting better, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "look up to",
        "options": [
            "to admire and respect someone",
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ...",
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "to continue to do something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to admire and respect someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "look upon as",
        "options": [
            "consider, regard",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ...",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to die, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "consider, regard"
    },
    {
        "question": "loose on",
        "options": [
            "same as stock",
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to tell someone that they must stop doing something and that if they do not something bad will happen to them",
            "to suddenly let something bad or unpleasant have its full effect on someone or something in an uncontrolled way"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly let something bad or unpleasant have its full effect on someone or something in an uncontrolled way"
    },
    {
        "question": "loosen up",
        "options": [
            "relax, unwind",
            "to make people forget about something embarrassing or silly that you have done",
            "to relax, or to become less serious, ...",
            "to keep one area separate from another"
        ],
        "answer": "to relax, or to become less serious, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lop off",
        "options": [
            "put food onto a plate to serve",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "to have an erection, ...",
            "to reduce something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "lord it over",
        "options": [
            "be involved in",
            "move in front of",
            "to include something as part of something else",
            "behave in a superior manner"
        ],
        "answer": "behave in a superior manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "lose out",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere with someone, ...",
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ...",
            "to not get a benefit that someone else is getting",
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not get a benefit that someone else is getting"
    },
    {
        "question": "lose out on",
        "options": [
            "to make someone stop liking or supporting someone or something, ...",
            "to be determined to continue doing something that is difficult or unpleasant",
            "not gain or have something advantageous",
            "to not allow someone to enter a particular place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "not gain or have something advantageous"
    },
    {
        "question": "lose out to",
        "options": [
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "be less successful"
        ],
        "answer": "be less successful"
    },
    {
        "question": "lounge around",
        "options": [
            "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature",
            "to increase something such as a rate or level, especially the rate at which goods are produced",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "to spend time relaxing or doing nothing when you should be doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time relaxing or doing nothing when you should be doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "luck into",
        "options": [
            "to continue to work at something difficult or unpleasant in a determined way",
            "to start to have an effect, ...",
            "get something by chance",
            "to help someone to get rid of feelings of sadness, worry, or anger by kissing them to show that you are sympathetic"
        ],
        "answer": "get something by chance"
    },
    {
        "question": "luck out",
        "options": [
            "same as flare",
            "to hold something above someone or something, ...",
            "to go somewhere quickly, especially in order to escape",
            "to be lucky"
        ],
        "answer": "to be lucky"
    },
    {
        "question": "lust after",
        "options": [
            "if a situation pans out in a particular way, it develops in that way",
            "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ...",
            "to want something very much, ...",
            "to ask someone a question, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to want something very much, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "magic away",
        "options": [
            "same as lead to",
            "to increase the price of something, especially something that you bought for a lower price, ...",
            "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily",
            "to annoy someone by frequently complaining to them about something that they do"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "mail off",
        "options": [
            "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim",
            "to cover something with wooden boards",
            "to listen to a radio programme, ...",
            "same as mail"
        ],
        "answer": "same as mail"
    },
    {
        "question": "mail out",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in keeping a job, ...",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to send many copies of a letter, advertisement etc by post at one time",
            "make it clear you are sexually attracted to someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to send many copies of a letter, advertisement etc by post at one time"
    },
    {
        "question": "make after",
        "options": [
            "to chase someone",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "move into a lane of traffic without making other cars stop",
            "arrive"
        ],
        "answer": "to chase someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "make away with",
        "options": [
            "to escape with something that you have stolen",
            "to want something very much",
            "to not include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "be ill"
        ],
        "answer": "to escape with something that you have stolen"
    },
    {
        "question": "make do with",
        "options": [
            "same as pine",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "become gradually more evident, ...",
            "accept something less satisfactory because there's no alternative"
        ],
        "answer": "accept something less satisfactory because there's no alternative"
    },
    {
        "question": "make for",
        "options": [
            "have sex with",
            "to leave, ...",
            "to move towards a place, ...",
            "same as blow, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move towards a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make into",
        "options": [
            "to have everything that you need, ...",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "to consider the good and bad aspects of something in order to reach a decision about it",
            "to move away from someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to change someone or something so that they become something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "make it",
        "options": [
            "to try to become a member of a team or to get a part in a play or film by showing someone how well you can play or perform",
            "arrive or get a result",
            "to reduce the positive effect or success of something",
            "to calculate the total of several numbers or amounts, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "arrive or get a result"
    },
    {
        "question": "make it up to",
        "options": [
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "try to compensate for doing something wrong",
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere",
            "to do what someone tells you to do"
        ],
        "answer": "try to compensate for doing something wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "make of",
        "options": [
            "to make something be successful, ...",
            "pass quickly",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it",
            "same as ladle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something be successful, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make off",
        "options": [
            "if two people square up, one pays what they owe so that both people are equal, ...",
            "to take off all your clothes, ...",
            "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong",
            "charge more for something"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "make off with",
        "options": [
            "to not keep a secret, ...",
            "to think that something is the right thing to do, ...",
            "to escape with something, especially something stolen",
            "same as tally"
        ],
        "answer": "to escape with something, especially something stolen"
    },
    {
        "question": "make out",
        "options": [
            "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ...",
            "to pretend that something is true, ...",
            "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pretend that something is true, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make over",
        "options": [
            "to officially make someone else the owner of something, ...",
            "to prepare someone for something, ...",
            "to become tired of something or bored with it",
            "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to officially make someone else the owner of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make towards",
        "options": [
            "to have to leave a school because your work is not satisfactory",
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "to go in the direction of someone or something",
            "same as stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to go in the direction of someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "make up",
        "options": [
            "to bail out of a plane, ...",
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ...",
            "to begin talking in a boring or annoying way, usually complaining or criticizing someone or something",
            "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger"
        ],
        "answer": "to invent a story, poem etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make up for",
        "options": [
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to take the place of something that has been lost or damaged, ...",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ...",
            "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to take the place of something that has been lost or damaged, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make up to",
        "options": [
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "to do something good that helps someone to feel better after you did something bad to them, ...",
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something good that helps someone to feel better after you did something bad to them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "make with",
        "options": [
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else",
            "to escape with something that you have stolen",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something"
        ],
        "answer": "to escape with something that you have stolen"
    },
    {
        "question": "man down",
        "options": [
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something",
            "behave without courage or conviction",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ...",
            "same as blot"
        ],
        "answer": "behave without courage or conviction"
    },
    {
        "question": "man up",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing one thing and start doing another, ...",
            "to start being brave and dealing with a difficult situation",
            "to answer a question or remark quickly and in an angry way",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "to start being brave and dealing with a difficult situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "manage down",
        "options": [
            "to focus on being an effective manager for the people you are responsible for in an organization, more than on satisfying the people who are above you",
            "accompany someone into an office",
            "to make something by joining all its parts, ...",
            "to continue a journey, especially after stopping for a period of time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to focus on being an effective manager for the people you are responsible for in an organization, more than on satisfying the people who are above you"
    },
    {
        "question": "manage up",
        "options": [
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "to have something as a final result, ...",
            "to focus on satisfying the people who are above you in an organization, more than on the people you are responsible for",
            "to try to deal with or solve a difficult problem"
        ],
        "answer": "to focus on satisfying the people who are above you in an organization, more than on the people you are responsible for"
    },
    {
        "question": "map onto",
        "options": [
            "to reduce something, ...",
            "to say unkind things about someone when they are not there, ...",
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure"
    },
    {
        "question": "map out",
        "options": [
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "to have another use or job as something",
            "to plan in detail how something will happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to plan in detail how something will happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "mark as",
        "options": [
            "same as mark, ...",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "to phone from one part of a building to another",
            "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about"
        ],
        "answer": "same as mark, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mark down",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the price of something, ...",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "to hold something so that someone else can reach it or see it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the price of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mark down as",
        "options": [
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things",
            "to find something or to meet someone by chance",
            "to turn around quickly where you are standing",
            "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide that you think someone or something is a particular type of person or thing, especially when you first see them"
    },
    {
        "question": "mark off",
        "options": [
            "really want something",
            "sleep somewhere for the night",
            "same as mark out, ...",
            "to find and arrest people, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as mark out, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mark out",
        "options": [
            "pay attention after not doing so",
            "to try hard to catch someone or to get something that you need",
            "to show the shape of something by drawing it on a surface, ...",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to show the shape of something by drawing it on a surface, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mark out for",
        "options": [
            "show promise for the future",
            "exploit, use to your advantage",
            "move to another side or place",
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed"
        ],
        "answer": "show promise for the future"
    },
    {
        "question": "mark out from",
        "options": [
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "same as tone",
            "to do gentle exercises that make your muscles stretch, especially in order to prepare for taking part in a sport",
            "stand out because of certain qualities"
        ],
        "answer": "stand out because of certain qualities"
    },
    {
        "question": "mark up",
        "options": [
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ...",
            "to put any profits made by a business back into it in order to make it more successful",
            "same as get across, ...",
            "to increase the price of something, especially something that you bought for a lower price, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase the price of something, especially something that you bought for a lower price, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "marry in",
        "options": [
            "to put money in a safe place so that you can use it later, ...",
            "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to.",
            "marry someone of the same ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "clog or overwhelm"
        ],
        "answer": "marry someone of the same ethnicity, religion, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "marry into",
        "options": [
            "to make information publicly known, ...",
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language",
            "be ill",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it"
        ],
        "answer": "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it"
    },
    {
        "question": "marry off",
        "options": [
            "to try to find or get something in a relaxed way",
            "to find a husband or wife for someone",
            "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ...",
            "to end a romantic or sexual relationship with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to find a husband or wife for someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "marry out",
        "options": [
            "to send a copy of a message or letter to someone",
            "marry someone of a different ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone",
            "to rain very hard"
        ],
        "answer": "marry someone of a different ethnicity, religion, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "marry up",
        "options": [
            "be elsewhere; on holiday, etc.",
            "to make two things fit or match each other, or to fit or match in this way",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to order something and ask for it to be delivered to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to make two things fit or match each other, or to fit or match in this way"
    },
    {
        "question": "mash up",
        "options": [
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk",
            "same as rifle",
            "break or damage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "break or damage, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "match up",
        "options": [
            "to be as good as someone or something, ...",
            "to agree to ask for or pay a lower price, ...",
            "ruin or spoil something",
            "to start a new activity, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be as good as someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "max out",
        "options": [
            "to reach the limit of something, or to use all of a supply of something, ...",
            "same as check, ...",
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ...",
            "to stop doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to reach the limit of something, or to use all of a supply of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "measure against",
        "options": [
            "evaluate or judge by comparison",
            "to officially state that a particular legal decision will no longer be followed, ...",
            "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ...",
            "leave a place angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "evaluate or judge by comparison"
    },
    {
        "question": "measure off",
        "options": [
            "to measure a particular length, width, height etc, often at a point where something is to be cut",
            "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ...",
            "to begin to have an effect on someone, ...",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "to measure a particular length, width, height etc, often at a point where something is to be cut"
    },
    {
        "question": "measure out",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone with a gun, ...",
            "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount",
            "arrive",
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "measure up",
        "options": [
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "try to find or get"
        ],
        "answer": "to be good enough, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "measure up to",
        "options": [
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "form a pair with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to be good enough, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "meet up",
        "options": [
            "approach slowly",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "to encourage someone to do something that they should not do",
            "same as gobble"
        ],
        "answer": "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "meet up with",
        "options": [
            "to sell something after buying it from someone else",
            "have sex with",
            "if animals feed off something, they eat it, ...",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "meet with",
        "options": [
            "to talk or write about something for a long time in a way that is boring, annoying, or confusing",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to enclose someone or something and prevent them from moving or leaving, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as meet, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mellow out",
        "options": [
            "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm",
            "have a good relationship from the first time you meet a person",
            "let down, snub",
            "to begin, or to begin something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm"
    },
    {
        "question": "melt away",
        "options": [
            "same as melt, ...",
            "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract",
            "to do something, or to deal with something, very easily",
            "same as buy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as melt, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "melt down",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to heat a metal until it becomes liquid, especially in order to make something new from it",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to try to catch or stop someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to heat a metal until it becomes liquid, especially in order to make something new from it"
    },
    {
        "question": "mess about",
        "options": [
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls up, they stop, ...",
            "to spend time doing things in a relaxed way, ...",
            "same as get on, ...",
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time doing things in a relaxed way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mess about with",
        "options": [
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "get someone to help or become involved, usually when they don't want to",
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "to sink below the surface of the water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mess around",
        "options": [
            "let down, snub",
            "sell something in an auction",
            "treat someone badly, ...",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism"
        ],
        "answer": "treat someone badly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mess around with",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "if an injury heals up, the skin or bone grows back together and becomes healthy again"
        ],
        "answer": "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mess over",
        "options": [
            "to make someone remember something that happened in the past, ...",
            "make a hand signal to tell someone to keep moving",
            "to attack a child by touching them sexually, ...",
            "treat someone badly"
        ],
        "answer": "treat someone badly"
    },
    {
        "question": "mess up",
        "options": [
            "get money off someone",
            "try to find something",
            "to make something happen, especially to cause changes in a situation",
            "to damage or spoil something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to damage or spoil something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mess with",
        "options": [
            "to make someone angry, or to argue with them, ...",
            "to give something to several people, ...",
            "used for telling someone to try to be happier, ...",
            "include someone or something in a group, category, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone angry, or to argue with them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mete out",
        "options": [
            "to give a punishment to someone",
            "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ...",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "same as join, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give a punishment to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "mill around",
        "options": [
            "an old phrase meaning \u2018to have sex with someone\u2019, ...",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose",
            "to make a horse stop or go more slowly by pulling its reins, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose"
    },
    {
        "question": "miss out",
        "options": [
            "same as gobble, ...",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "when a space vehicle splashes down, it lands in the sea after being in space",
            "go out"
        ],
        "answer": "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "miss out on",
        "options": [
            "start to have a negative feeling",
            "deliver, ...",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to slow down, or to become less"
        ],
        "answer": "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mistake for",
        "options": [
            "to think that a person or thing is someone or something else",
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone",
            "to make something using the few things that are available",
            "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people"
        ],
        "answer": "to think that a person or thing is someone or something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "mix up",
        "options": [
            "behave as if you are better or more important than others",
            "to allow someone bail when they are waiting to appear in court, ...",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "to put things together without any order, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put things together without any order, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mock up",
        "options": [
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like",
            "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ...",
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation",
            "to stay until the end of something, especially if you are not enjoying it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like"
    },
    {
        "question": "model on",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere quickly, especially in order to escape",
            "to become involved in something, ...",
            "to copy a way of doing something or a system, ...",
            "to avoid dealing directly with a problem, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to copy a way of doing something or a system, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "moggy off",
        "options": [
            "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to leave secretly, ...",
            "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)"
        ],
        "answer": "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)"
    },
    {
        "question": "monkey around",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to send someone to prison, ...",
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "mooch about",
        "options": [
            "to decorate something in a particular way, or to wear a particular set of clothes",
            "to order someone to do something, ...",
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose"
    },
    {
        "question": "mooch around",
        "options": [
            "become excited and lose control",
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "to eat dinner in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose"
    },
    {
        "question": "moon around",
        "options": [
            "to destroy or to completely remove something, ...",
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to spend time doing nothing useful or important",
            "put something in a place without taking care"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time doing nothing useful or important"
    },
    {
        "question": "moon over",
        "options": [
            "to be about a subject, ...",
            "to tie the ends of something together, ...",
            "to do something very quickly and not very carefully",
            "to spend time thinking about someone who you are attracted to rather than doing anything useful"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time thinking about someone who you are attracted to rather than doing anything useful"
    },
    {
        "question": "mop up",
        "options": [
            "to make a short visit to a person or place",
            "same as mop, ...",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "to give someone something that they owned or had before, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as mop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mope about",
        "options": [
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "to express your opinions loudly, especially in an unreasonable way",
            "to spend time in a relaxed way when you have nothing else to do",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy"
    },
    {
        "question": "mope around",
        "options": [
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "same as chop",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "to increase something such as a rate or level, especially the rate at which goods are produced"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy"
    },
    {
        "question": "mount up",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone in an unkind or unfair way",
            "think of someone or something in a particular way",
            "same as mount, ...",
            "to phone someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as mount, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mouth off",
        "options": [
            "feel tears starting, ...",
            "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ...",
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something",
            "to prevent the flavour, smell, or juice of a food from getting out"
        ],
        "answer": "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "move ahead",
        "options": [
            "if something sweeps you along, you become very involved in it because you are so excited about it",
            "make progress, often after a pause or delay",
            "to turn the pages of a book, newspaper, or magazine quickly without reading or looking at it carefully. The usual British word is leaf through",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely"
        ],
        "answer": "make progress, often after a pause or delay"
    },
    {
        "question": "move along",
        "options": [
            "to be connected with someone or something, ...",
            "to tell someone to move away from a place, ...",
            "employ someone for something specific",
            "to not go to school or work when you do not have a good reason for staying away"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone to move away from a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move away",
        "options": [
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to phone several people or companies etc in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "to stop living in one place and go to live in another"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop living in one place and go to live in another"
    },
    {
        "question": "move away from",
        "options": [
            "to blame or criticize someone in an unpleasant, unkind way",
            "same as freshen, ...",
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "to come to a particular place without planning to"
        ],
        "answer": "stop doing or using something to change to something different"
    },
    {
        "question": "move down",
        "options": [
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ...",
            "act in a dangerous or reckless way, especially when driving fast",
            "move a student to a lower level",
            "to deal again with something that you were dealing with earlier"
        ],
        "answer": "move a student to a lower level"
    },
    {
        "question": "move in",
        "options": [
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have",
            "to start living in a different house or flat, ...",
            "to have a good result, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start living in a different house or flat, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move in on",
        "options": [
            "to calculate the cost, amount, size etc of something",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "to try to control something that someone else controlled before, ...",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to control something that someone else controlled before, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move into",
        "options": [
            "to have some of a particular quality",
            "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ...",
            "to begin a new business or new type of business, ...",
            "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a new business or new type of business, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move off",
        "options": [
            "to discuss a problem thoroughly with someone who disagrees with you about it",
            "if a vehicle moves off, it starts to move",
            "to remove one part of something",
            "cut completely into pieces or slices"
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle moves off, it starts to move"
    },
    {
        "question": "move on",
        "options": [
            "to leave one place and travel to another, ...",
            "to masturbate, ...",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave one place and travel to another, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move out",
        "options": [
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business",
            "to drink all of your drink",
            "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something",
            "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business"
    },
    {
        "question": "move over",
        "options": [
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious",
            "to start to do something in a different way, ...",
            "to manage to reach or touch something, ...",
            "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to do something in a different way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move towards",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "behave in a silly way",
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas",
            "to formally state that something is true, especially in a court of law"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "move up",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "to begin something or begin to take part in something",
            "to go to a better job, higher level etc, ...",
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go to a better job, higher level etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "mow down",
        "options": [
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "think about something",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ...",
            "to kill a lot of people quickly and violently, especially by shooting them"
        ],
        "answer": "to kill a lot of people quickly and violently, especially by shooting them"
    },
    {
        "question": "muddle along",
        "options": [
            "to start to feel relaxed and happy, or to make someone start to feel relaxed and happy",
            "try to find someone for a task or requirement",
            "to continue to live or do something without having a clear idea of what you want to achieve",
            "to react angrily towards someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to live or do something without having a clear idea of what you want to achieve"
    },
    {
        "question": "muddle through",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "not gain or have something advantageous",
            "to start eating in a very enthusiastic way, ...",
            "to succeed in doing something despite having no clear plan, method, or suitable equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in doing something despite having no clear plan, method, or suitable equipment"
    },
    {
        "question": "muddle up",
        "options": [
            "to officially ask for something, ...",
            "same as muddle",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation",
            "to be the real reason for a decision or action"
        ],
        "answer": "same as muddle"
    },
    {
        "question": "mug up",
        "options": [
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination",
            "to offer help to someone who needs it",
            "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger",
            "if it is peeing down, a lot of rain is falling"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination"
    },
    {
        "question": "mug up on",
        "options": [
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them",
            "study something quickly, revise"
        ],
        "answer": "study something quickly, revise"
    },
    {
        "question": "mull over",
        "options": [
            "to think carefully about something over a period of time",
            "to start doing something in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy",
            "same as curl, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to think carefully about something over a period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "muscle in",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place, situation, or person",
            "travel somewhere to visit",
            "to use your power or influence to get involved in a situation in which you are not needed or wanted",
            "stop working or functioning, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use your power or influence to get involved in a situation in which you are not needed or wanted"
    },
    {
        "question": "muscle in on",
        "options": [
            "to make a path through something by cutting, ...",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions",
            "become involved in something despite opposition to your involvement",
            "to start a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "become involved in something despite opposition to your involvement"
    },
    {
        "question": "muscle into",
        "options": [
            "become involved even though there is opposition to your involvement",
            "to make someone stop wanting something or stop wanting to be with someone",
            "to keep something",
            "to treat someone in a cruel way over a long period and gradually destroy their confidence or strength"
        ],
        "answer": "become involved even though there is opposition to your involvement"
    },
    {
        "question": "muscle out",
        "options": [
            "to try to discover in a careful or indirect way what a situation is like or what someone\u2019s attitude is",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to",
            "use power, contacts, etc, to force someone out"
        ],
        "answer": "use power, contacts, etc, to force someone out"
    },
    {
        "question": "naff off",
        "options": [
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "reach inside something quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone rudely to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "nag at",
        "options": [
            "repeatedly criticise someone verbally",
            "to search carefully among things",
            "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ...",
            "to get or borrow money from someone"
        ],
        "answer": "repeatedly criticise someone verbally"
    },
    {
        "question": "nail down",
        "options": [
            "leave a place, ...",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "to make something flat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "nail up",
        "options": [
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "to suddenly put someone somewhere that they cannot escape from",
            "to fix something to a wall with a nail or nails, ...",
            "to make something using the few things that are available"
        ],
        "answer": "to fix something to a wall with a nail or nails, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "name after",
        "options": [
            "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something",
            "to stand up straight, ...",
            "criticise angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family"
    },
    {
        "question": "name for",
        "options": [
            "to gradually reduce the strength, value, or importance of something",
            "to give a place or an object the same name as a person or another thing",
            "to make someone feel strange",
            "say something quickly without thinking, especially if you shouldn't"
        ],
        "answer": "to give a place or an object the same name as a person or another thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "narrow down",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the number of possibilities or choices",
            "to count things one by one, ...",
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the number of possibilities or choices"
    },
    {
        "question": "nerd out",
        "options": [
            "to attract very large audiences, ...",
            "to belong to a particular group or class, ...",
            "discuss something in great detail, ...",
            "to make a short visit somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "discuss something in great detail, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "nibble away at",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it",
            "press or twist something hard into something else",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to use a hose to clean something"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "nick off",
        "options": [
            "to go away, or to leave",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to accept someone or something that is not exactly what you wanted because you cannot have what you wanted",
            "same as roll, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go away, or to leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "nip off",
        "options": [
            "to use something such as time or effort for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to score a goal when your team is losing in a football match, ...",
            "go somewhere quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "nip out",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere quickly",
            "to eat all of something, ...",
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "nod off",
        "options": [
            "to notice something that is not very obvious, ...",
            "sit and do nothing, especially when you should be working",
            "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to",
            "same as ease off, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to"
    },
    {
        "question": "nod through",
        "options": [
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to treat someone in an unfair way or trick them, in a way that shows you do not respect them",
            "pass a law, regulation, etc, without considering or debating it seriously",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to leave a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pass a law, regulation, etc, without considering or debating it seriously"
    },
    {
        "question": "nose about",
        "options": [
            "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem",
            "to eat food, especially a lot of food, quickly or in an enthusiastic way",
            "to find out whether information is accurate or useful by comparing it with other information",
            "to try to find out information about someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out information about someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "nose around",
        "options": [
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it",
            "to try to find out information about someone or something",
            "say numbers aloud in a sequence",
            "same as bust, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out information about someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "nose into",
        "options": [
            "applaud",
            "to begin to like someone or something",
            "to go somewhere with someone else although you are not needed",
            "to try to find out information about something"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out information about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "nose out",
        "options": [
            "to find out information, especially something that someone does not want you to know",
            "to quickly produce something such as a meal using whatever is available",
            "to gradually destroy something",
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to find out information, especially something that someone does not want you to know"
    },
    {
        "question": "notch up",
        "options": [
            "to win something, or to achieve something",
            "to use all of a supply of something",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to win something, or to achieve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "note down",
        "options": [
            "same as head",
            "remove quickly, ...",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference."
        ],
        "answer": "write something short like a phone number for future reference."
    },
    {
        "question": "number among",
        "options": [
            "agree with or accept something you had previously disapproved of or disliked.",
            "to be part of a particular group, or to include someone or something among a particular group",
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly",
            "to become tired of something or bored with it"
        ],
        "answer": "to be part of a particular group, or to include someone or something among a particular group"
    },
    {
        "question": "number off",
        "options": [
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to waste someone else\u2019s time or treat them in a bad way, ...",
            "to give each person in a group a number that is used for referring to them",
            "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ...",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does"
        ],
        "answer": "to give each person in a group a number that is used for referring to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "nut out",
        "options": [
            "same as slough, ...",
            "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "find an answer to a problem"
        ],
        "answer": "find an answer to a problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "occur to",
        "options": [
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "finish or complete, often with some decisive action",
            "to eat all of something, ...",
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it"
        ],
        "answer": "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "offer up",
        "options": [
            "cut the electricity to a computer or device to turn it off",
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "force someone to leave",
            "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "open out",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "to develop, ...",
            "if a path or passage opens out, it becomes wider at the end, ...",
            "to send many copies of a letter, advertisement etc by post at one time"
        ],
        "answer": "if a path or passage opens out, it becomes wider at the end, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "open up",
        "options": [
            "same as open, ...",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to continue to do something, ...",
            "to put something around something else"
        ],
        "answer": "same as open, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "operate on",
        "options": [
            "to choose one thing or person from a group, ...",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "perform surgery"
        ],
        "answer": "perform surgery"
    },
    {
        "question": "opt for",
        "options": [
            "to make a choice or decision from a range of possibilities",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm",
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ...",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a choice or decision from a range of possibilities"
    },
    {
        "question": "opt in",
        "options": [
            "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention",
            "continue, not quit",
            "persevere, not give up",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "opt into",
        "options": [
            "same as stoop",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "to do what someone tells you to do",
            "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "opt out",
        "options": [
            "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ...",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "to still exist from the past, ...",
            "to decide not to take part in something or to stop taking part in it"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to take part in something or to stop taking part in it"
    },
    {
        "question": "order about",
        "options": [
            "to physically attack someone",
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people",
            "to want something very much, ...",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people"
    },
    {
        "question": "order around",
        "options": [
            "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ...",
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "to get rid of a bad feeling or condition by going for a walk, ...",
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people"
    },
    {
        "question": "order in",
        "options": [
            "behave in a silly way",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to clean and remove dirt, glass, dust etc from a floor or the ground using a brush or broom",
            "focus less closely"
        ],
        "answer": "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "order off",
        "options": [
            "to tell a player officially to leave the sports field because they have done something that is not allowed by the rules",
            "to cover an area of ground with grass",
            "return somewhere",
            "to give something to someone although you would prefer to keep it"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell a player officially to leave the sports field because they have done something that is not allowed by the rules"
    },
    {
        "question": "order out",
        "options": [
            "need or want something",
            "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to pretend to agree with someone or something, especially in order to get what you want or avoid an argument"
        ],
        "answer": "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "order out for",
        "options": [
            "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ...",
            "have food delivered",
            "do something out of a car",
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it"
        ],
        "answer": "have food delivered"
    },
    {
        "question": "order up",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ...",
            "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong",
            "be the reason for something",
            "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone to do something, provide something, or deliver something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "owe to",
        "options": [
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers.",
            "to make a problem seem less serious",
            "be the reason for something"
        ],
        "answer": "be the reason for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "own up",
        "options": [
            "same as heave",
            "surprise or shock",
            "to admit that you have done something bad or embarrassing",
            "to deal with or take responsibility for someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to admit that you have done something bad or embarrassing"
    },
    {
        "question": "pace out",
        "options": [
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "consume",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other"
        ],
        "answer": "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other"
    },
    {
        "question": "pack away",
        "options": [
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "have sex with someone, especially casual sex",
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ...",
            "to start to realize something"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat a large quantity of food, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pack in",
        "options": [
            "to be about to happen soon, ...",
            "used for telling someone to be quiet, ...",
            "to attract very large audiences, ...",
            "to think that a person or thing is someone or something else"
        ],
        "answer": "to attract very large audiences, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pack into",
        "options": [
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ...",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them",
            "to become involved in something that other people are doing that is fun or interesting, or that makes money",
            "to fit into a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fit into a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pack it in",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "stop doing something (used as an imperative)",
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "to say the words that you are reading so that people can hear them"
        ],
        "answer": "stop doing something (used as an imperative)"
    },
    {
        "question": "pack off",
        "options": [
            "to send someone away somewhere suddenly",
            "if a storm blows over, it ends, ...",
            "to produce things in large numbers without caring much about their quality",
            "to kill someone by hanging them"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone away somewhere suddenly"
    },
    {
        "question": "pack out",
        "options": [
            "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ...",
            "fill a venue",
            "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with",
            "to leave an official position or job, especially so that someone else can take your place"
        ],
        "answer": "fill a venue"
    },
    {
        "question": "pack up",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something, especially a job, ...",
            "be as good as something",
            "to reach the time when something should happen",
            "to go to work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something, especially a job, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pad down",
        "options": [
            "what someone is really trying to say",
            "sleep somewhere for the night",
            "same as pine",
            "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it"
        ],
        "answer": "sleep somewhere for the night"
    },
    {
        "question": "pad out",
        "options": [
            "to put unnecessary information into something to make it longer",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ...",
            "have no more left",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen"
        ],
        "answer": "to put unnecessary information into something to make it longer"
    },
    {
        "question": "pad up",
        "options": [
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers.",
            "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket",
            "talk fast or incomprehensibly",
            "do something enthusiastically or energetically"
        ],
        "answer": "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket"
    },
    {
        "question": "page down",
        "options": [
            "to admit something, ...",
            "persuade someone not to do something",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen",
            "if words pop out, you say them suddenly without thinking about it first"
        ],
        "answer": "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen"
    },
    {
        "question": "page through",
        "options": [
            "to turn the pages of a book, newspaper, or magazine quickly without reading or looking at it carefully. The usual British word is leaf through",
            "if two or more teams or players who have the same number of points in a competition play off, they play a game or games to see who is the winner",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "to turn the pages of a book, newspaper, or magazine quickly without reading or looking at it carefully. The usual British word is leaf through"
    },
    {
        "question": "page up",
        "options": [
            "spend time doing very little or being unproductive",
            "to turn a container upside down so that the things inside it come out, ...",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen",
            "break, damage or injure by hitting"
        ],
        "answer": "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen"
    },
    {
        "question": "pair off",
        "options": [
            "to start a romantic relationship with someone, or to bring two people together because you want them to have a relationship with each other",
            "make electrical connections",
            "to become involved in something by accident",
            "to ignore someone\u2019s ideas, feelings, or opinions because you do not think they are important"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a romantic relationship with someone, or to bring two people together because you want them to have a relationship with each other"
    },
    {
        "question": "pair off with",
        "options": [
            "form a pair with someone",
            "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour",
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "be late paying instalments for something."
        ],
        "answer": "form a pair with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pair up",
        "options": [
            "to form a pair, or to make two people form a pair",
            "to make a short visit to a person or place",
            "to be ready to do something, ...",
            "to be made at a particular time in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "to form a pair, or to make two people form a pair"
    },
    {
        "question": "pal about",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to do or to accept something",
            "same as pass",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to break a door or gate in order to get through it"
        ],
        "answer": "be friendly and spend time with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pal around",
        "options": [
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ...",
            "if something that you do pays off, it brings you some benefit, ...",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "be friendly and spend time with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pal up",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing or person to another, ...",
            "become friends",
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "become friends"
    },
    {
        "question": "palm off",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "to spread objects or parts out, often in the shape of a semi-circle, ...",
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "to vomit food from your stomach out of your mouth"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pan out",
        "options": [
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people",
            "remove by biting",
            "to become involved in something by accident",
            "if a situation pans out in a particular way, it develops in that way"
        ],
        "answer": "if a situation pans out in a particular way, it develops in that way"
    },
    {
        "question": "paper over",
        "options": [
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it",
            "to keep telling someone something in order to make them understand or accept it",
            "to do something that you have planned or agreed to do, especially after not being sure you want to do it",
            "same as brighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it"
    },
    {
        "question": "parachute in",
        "options": [
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ...",
            "to suddenly put someone in a new job when people do not expect it",
            "to expect more than you should get or have a right to, especially in your relationships with other people",
            "to move smoothly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly put someone in a new job when people do not expect it"
    },
    {
        "question": "pare back",
        "options": [
            "to masturbate",
            "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers.",
            "to happen after something, and often as the next part or stage of it",
            "sell something in an auction"
        ],
        "answer": "if you pare something back, you reduce the size or numbers."
    },
    {
        "question": "pare down",
        "options": [
            "get into trouble",
            "to turn a container upside down so that the things inside it come out, ...",
            "reduce, decrease",
            "to stop someone from moving their car out of a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "reduce, decrease"
    },
    {
        "question": "part with",
        "options": [
            "leave, depart",
            "to turn and face in the opposite direction",
            "to begin to have an effect on someone, ...",
            "to give something to someone although you would prefer to keep it"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something to someone although you would prefer to keep it"
    },
    {
        "question": "partake of",
        "options": [
            "to have some of a particular quality",
            "same as get",
            "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ...",
            "improve your knowledge quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to have some of a particular quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "partition off",
        "options": [
            "to leave or go away, ...",
            "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily",
            "intend, plan",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a room with a partition"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate an area from the rest of a room with a partition"
    },
    {
        "question": "partner up",
        "options": [
            "to form a row, or to put people or things in a row, ...",
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation",
            "to become partners, or to make people become partners",
            "same as curl, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become partners, or to make people become partners"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass around",
        "options": [
            "same as pass",
            "to make a short visit to a person or place",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way",
            "to be as good as someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass as",
        "options": [
            "to introduce a new law or system, ...",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "same as pass",
            "force a person to leave or go away"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass away",
        "options": [
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ...",
            "to become smaller or lower in amount, level, value etc, ...",
            "to fit into a place, ...",
            "to die. This word is used to avoid saying \u2018die\u2019 when you think this might upset someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to die. This word is used to avoid saying \u2018die\u2019 when you think this might upset someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass back",
        "options": [
            "return",
            "to fall asleep, ...",
            "same as double",
            "to increase something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "return"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass by",
        "options": [
            "to go past, ...",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ...",
            "to put money into your bank account",
            "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass down",
        "options": [
            "depend very much or completely",
            "to try hard not to feel or express an emotion that you are starting to feel",
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to give knowledge or teach skills to your children or to younger people"
        ],
        "answer": "to give knowledge or teach skills to your children or to younger people"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass for",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with someone, especially someone who you are not married to",
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ...",
            "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing",
            "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass off",
        "options": [
            "to take the place of an actor by pretending to be them in difficult or dangerous parts of a film",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way",
            "same as pass, ...",
            "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pass, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass on",
        "options": [
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "same as pass, ...",
            "same as get",
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pass, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass on to",
        "options": [
            "change topic or subject",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them"
        ],
        "answer": "change topic or subject"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass out",
        "options": [
            "to give something to each member of a group, ...",
            "to fix something to a wall with a nail or nails, ...",
            "to write exactly what someone has written or said",
            "to produce things in large numbers without caring much about their quality"
        ],
        "answer": "to give something to each member of a group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass over",
        "options": [
            "to gradually become smaller or weaker before coming to an end or disappearing completely",
            "persuade someone to do something",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ...",
            "same as call on"
        ],
        "answer": "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass round",
        "options": [
            "to get connected to the internet on your computer by using a modem and telephone line",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours",
            "same as check, ...",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass through",
        "options": [
            "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ...",
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "same as put, ...",
            "to go to a place for only a short period of time before continuing a journey"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to a place for only a short period of time before continuing a journey"
    },
    {
        "question": "pass to",
        "options": [
            "to want something very much, ...",
            "to die, ...",
            "to succeed after great difficulty",
            "move or drive very fast, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to die, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pass up",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a noisy silly way, ...",
            "to not take advantage of an opportunity",
            "to shoot at someone or something a lot of times, ...",
            "leave, depart"
        ],
        "answer": "to not take advantage of an opportunity"
    },
    {
        "question": "pat down",
        "options": [
            "same as box",
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "to grow trees, plants, or seeds in a container or an area so that they fill it completely"
        ],
        "answer": "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport"
    },
    {
        "question": "patch together",
        "options": [
            "make yourself popular with someone",
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas",
            "come to nothing, produce no results",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas"
    },
    {
        "question": "patch up",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to repair something, often quickly and not very well, ...",
            "make something like a cushion bigger and softer by shaking it",
            "applaud"
        ],
        "answer": "to repair something, often quickly and not very well, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pave over",
        "options": [
            "to cover an area of ground by paving it",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a very boring way"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover an area of ground by paving it"
    },
    {
        "question": "pawn off",
        "options": [
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "to persuade someone to buy or accept something that you do not want, especially something of low quality",
            "if you put something down to a particular reason, you think it has happened for that reason, ...",
            "to enjoy yourself in a social situation, often by spending a lot of money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to buy or accept something that you do not want, especially something of low quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "pawn off as",
        "options": [
            "to stop considering something as a possibility",
            "same as piss",
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else"
        ],
        "answer": "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "pay back",
        "options": [
            "look in a place to try to find something",
            "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy",
            "to give someone the same amount of money that you borrowed from them, ...",
            "to call someone by telephone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone the same amount of money that you borrowed from them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pay down",
        "options": [
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ...",
            "to avoid going to school or work when you should go",
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "pay a debt over time"
        ],
        "answer": "pay a debt over time"
    },
    {
        "question": "pay for",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to attack someone violently",
            "to have a good result, ...",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a good result, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pay in",
        "options": [
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "same as put, ...",
            "go somewhere quickly",
            "to put money into your bank account"
        ],
        "answer": "to put money into your bank account"
    },
    {
        "question": "pay into",
        "options": [
            "to serve food, ...",
            "to put money into your bank account, ...",
            "to make something end quickly, especially by using force, ...",
            "same as shade"
        ],
        "answer": "to put money into your bank account, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pay off",
        "options": [
            "arrive or get a result",
            "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ...",
            "if something that you do pays off, it brings you some benefit, ...",
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly"
        ],
        "answer": "if something that you do pays off, it brings you some benefit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pay out",
        "options": [
            "to stay somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "to spend or pay money, especially a lot of money, ...",
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend or pay money, especially a lot of money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pay up",
        "options": [
            "keep afloat, ...",
            "to pay money that you owe, especially when you are unwilling to pay",
            "to escape from prison, ...",
            "to refuse to listen to someone, or to accept that something might be true or important"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay money that you owe, especially when you are unwilling to pay"
    },
    {
        "question": "peal out",
        "options": [
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound"
        ],
        "answer": "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound"
    },
    {
        "question": "peck at",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "to attack someone violently, ...",
            "to eat only a small amount of a meal, without much interest"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat only a small amount of a meal, without much interest"
    },
    {
        "question": "pee down",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from a surface by cutting or digging with a sharp object",
            "if it is peeing down, a lot of rain is falling",
            "same as bust, ...",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely"
        ],
        "answer": "if it is peeing down, a lot of rain is falling"
    },
    {
        "question": "peel away",
        "options": [
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ...",
            "same as sketch",
            "become very disturbed or angry",
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "peel away from",
        "options": [
            "to press hard into a surface",
            "to annoy someone by frequently complaining to them about something that they do",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "cut completely into pieces or slices"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a group by moving in a different direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "peel off",
        "options": [
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ...",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "to pay no attention to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "peel off from",
        "options": [
            "behave in a silly way",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help",
            "same as mount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave a group by moving in a different direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "peel out",
        "options": [
            "to make a careless mistake",
            "to suddenly make a car start moving very quickly so that it makes a lot of noise",
            "to do something, especially something that you should not do",
            "to stop thinking or believing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly make a car start moving very quickly so that it makes a lot of noise"
    },
    {
        "question": "peg away",
        "options": [
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like",
            "same as hatch",
            "to keep doing something in a determined way, especially when it is boring or difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep doing something in a determined way, especially when it is boring or difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "peg back",
        "options": [
            "to connect something with something else",
            "same as heave",
            "to prevent an opponent from winning in a game or competition, ...",
            "have a good time by spending a lot of money"
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent an opponent from winning in a game or competition, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "peg down",
        "options": [
            "fasten something to the ground",
            "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective",
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened",
            "to give someone something that was given to you"
        ],
        "answer": "fasten something to the ground"
    },
    {
        "question": "peg it",
        "options": [
            "to provide something for someone, ...",
            "die",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "finish or complete, often with some decisive action"
        ],
        "answer": "die"
    },
    {
        "question": "peg out",
        "options": [
            "to die, ...",
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way",
            "if a sports game or other outside event is rained off, it does not happen because of rain"
        ],
        "answer": "to die, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pen in",
        "options": [
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort",
            "to do the opposite of what a person, set of rules etc says you should do, because you disagree with them",
            "same as pen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pen up",
        "options": [
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "same as pen",
            "to live at the place where you work or study"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pen"
    },
    {
        "question": "pencil in",
        "options": [
            "to arrange for something to happen or for someone to do something, knowing that it may have to be changed later",
            "to prepare yourself, or to prepare something for an activity or event",
            "to not approach someone or something",
            "to escape from a person or place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange for something to happen or for someone to do something, knowing that it may have to be changed later"
    },
    {
        "question": "pep up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone or something more active and lively",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ...",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "to meet someone and start a sexual relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone or something more active and lively"
    },
    {
        "question": "perk up",
        "options": [
            "to take off clothes, especially quickly, ...",
            "to become more interesting or exciting, or to make something do this, ...",
            "if you are loaded down with a lot of heavy things, you are carrying them, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to become more interesting or exciting, or to make something do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "permit of",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something",
            "same as catch, ...",
            "to reduce the number of people or things, or the size of something",
            "to make something possible"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "peter out",
        "options": [
            "to give thanks, praise, or prayers to God, ...",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is",
            "to gradually become smaller or weaker before coming to an end or disappearing completely"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually become smaller or weaker before coming to an end or disappearing completely"
    },
    {
        "question": "phase in",
        "options": [
            "to clean and remove dirt, glass, dust etc from a floor or the ground using a brush or broom",
            "to gradually start using something",
            "criticise something strongly",
            "to contain an extremely large number of people, animals, or objects that are all moving around"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually start using something"
    },
    {
        "question": "phase out",
        "options": [
            "same as choke",
            "consume",
            "to slightly change something that you previously said, or to slightly change your opinion on an issue",
            "to gradually stop using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually stop using something"
    },
    {
        "question": "phone back",
        "options": [
            "to phone someone again, or to phone someone who phoned you earlier when you were away or were too busy to speak to them",
            "same as strike on",
            "to hit or kick someone who is attacking you, ...",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone someone again, or to phone someone who phoned you earlier when you were away or were too busy to speak to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "phone in",
        "options": [
            "to improve the appearance of someone or something",
            "to die, ...",
            "to telephone the place where you work in order to give a message, ...",
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to telephone the place where you work in order to give a message, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "phone round",
        "options": [
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "rob someone at gunpoint, ...",
            "to phone several people or companies in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone several people or companies in order to arrange something or to get information"
    },
    {
        "question": "phone through",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone",
            "to remove a tight or wet piece of clothing, ...",
            "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ...",
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone"
    },
    {
        "question": "phone up",
        "options": [
            "to murder someone, ...",
            "to choose someone or something after considering the situation, ...",
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened",
            "same as phone"
        ],
        "answer": "same as phone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick apart",
        "options": [
            "criticise, find fault",
            "to eat dinner in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "to fill something with air using a pump, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "criticise, find fault"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick at",
        "options": [
            "to shout or sing something loudly, or to play something loudly on a musical instrument",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "to become calm again, ...",
            "same as pick, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pick, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick off",
        "options": [
            "reach inside something quickly",
            "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ...",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance"
        ],
        "answer": "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick on",
        "options": [
            "to find out what is being done about something, ...",
            "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ...",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "to choose one thing or person from a group, ...",
            "to invest a lot of money in something in order to improve it or make it successful, ...",
            "to suddenly find something or think of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to choose one thing or person from a group, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick over",
        "options": [
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way",
            "to talk about something in detail, ...",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk about something in detail, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick through",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere quickly, especially in order to escape",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "to search through a collection of things in order to find something",
            "if a good feeling or quality shines through, it is very noticeable"
        ],
        "answer": "to search through a collection of things in order to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick up",
        "options": [
            "to improve, ...",
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ...",
            "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way",
            "criticise"
        ],
        "answer": "to improve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick up after",
        "options": [
            "to make a place clean and tidy, especially after someone else has used it",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "to not leave a person or place",
            "to stop something from happening, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a place clean and tidy, especially after someone else has used it"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick up on",
        "options": [
            "to reduce an amount, ...",
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly",
            "to steal something or to take it without permission, ...",
            "to notice something that is not very obvious, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to notice something that is not very obvious, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pick yourself up",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone severely",
            "to pay money that you owe, especially when you are unwilling to pay",
            "to improve, ...",
            "to remove something from a surface by gently touching it several times with something such as a piece of cloth"
        ],
        "answer": "to improve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "piddle around",
        "options": [
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "if an injury scars over, it forms a scar as it becomes better",
            "to be covered in insects, ...",
            "to spend time doing things that are not important"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time doing things that are not important"
    },
    {
        "question": "piddle away",
        "options": [
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things that are very similar",
            "to steal something, ...",
            "to waste time, energy, or money",
            "to spend time doing things in a relaxed way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time, energy, or money"
    },
    {
        "question": "pig off",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel very annoyed or upset",
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "to add something to a liquid or substance and mix it",
            "same as fill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel very annoyed or upset"
    },
    {
        "question": "pig out",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "same as slacken",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat an extremely large amount of food"
    },
    {
        "question": "pile in",
        "options": [
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting",
            "find an answer to a problem",
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things",
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
    },
    {
        "question": "pile into",
        "options": [
            "to get into a place or something such as a car, especially in large numbers or in a way that is not organized",
            "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ...",
            "same as polish",
            "to recognize a particular quality in someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get into a place or something such as a car, especially in large numbers or in a way that is not organized"
    },
    {
        "question": "pile on",
        "options": [
            "to get permission from someone to do something, ...",
            "go somewhere",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ...",
            "to make a bad situation much worse for someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a bad situation much worse for someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pile out",
        "options": [
            "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ...",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "to leave a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
    },
    {
        "question": "pile up",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help",
            "same as pile, ...",
            "not turn off",
            "return"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pile, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pin down",
        "options": [
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to understand or describe something exactly, ...",
            "to go to bed later than usual, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to understand or describe something exactly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pin on",
        "options": [
            "to blame someone for something, often when they are not responsible, ...",
            "to tell someone a secret",
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things",
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to blame someone for something, often when they are not responsible, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pin up",
        "options": [
            "to be better than other things of the same type, ...",
            "to take off all your clothes, ...",
            "to remove part of the original sound from a recording, especially a film",
            "to fix a picture to a wall, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fix a picture to a wall, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pine away",
        "options": [
            "fall asleep",
            "to try to influence someone, ...",
            "same as pine",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pine"
    },
    {
        "question": "pine for",
        "options": [
            "to lead someone around a place for the first time, so that they can see all parts of it",
            "to be very sad because you want to be with someone who you love, or want something that you do not have",
            "to get permission from someone to do something, ...",
            "same as deal, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be very sad because you want to be with someone who you love, or want something that you do not have"
    },
    {
        "question": "pipe down",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to stop talking or to make less noise",
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "leave a place, ...",
            "to become friends with someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling someone to stop talking or to make less noise"
    },
    {
        "question": "pipe up",
        "options": [
            "prepare for something that will require a great effort",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ...",
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to enter a conversation, for example by interrupting or speaking for the first time"
        ],
        "answer": "to enter a conversation, for example by interrupting or speaking for the first time"
    },
    {
        "question": "piss about",
        "options": [
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language",
            "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ...",
            "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit",
            "accuse somebody of a crime"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way that annoys other people, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "piss away",
        "options": [
            "to waste time, energy, or money",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to make a careless mistake",
            "to say or believe that someone has a particular quality, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time, energy, or money"
    },
    {
        "question": "piss down",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "reconcile different positions",
            "to make a person or animal fatter",
            "same as piss"
        ],
        "answer": "same as piss"
    },
    {
        "question": "piss off",
        "options": [
            "to invite someone to go somewhere such as a restaurant or cinema with you, often because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "to succeed in persuading someone to agree to something, ...",
            "to leave somewhere, ...",
            "to remove a person or political party from a position by voting"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave somewhere, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pit against",
        "options": [
            "to stop the continuation of a court case, ...",
            "withdraw from company",
            "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ...",
            "to make the muscles in a part of your body stronger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pit out",
        "options": [
            "go into the pits (car racing)",
            "to do the job of a particular kind of person or thing",
            "to put traffic cones across a road in order to prevent traffic from going along the road",
            "if people grow apart, their relationship gradually changes and they become less close"
        ],
        "answer": "go into the pits (car racing)"
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch against",
        "options": [
            "to not come home at night",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "if something gets chewed up, it becomes torn apart and destroyed, ...",
            "to make someone fight or compete against someone else"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone fight or compete against someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch for",
        "options": [
            "same as lap, ...",
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ...",
            "to do something that will cause problems in the future, ...",
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a sound at a particular level, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch in",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place or an organization",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "go somewhere away from people to study or work",
            "to join with other people in doing a job, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to join with other people in doing a job, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch into",
        "options": [
            "to deal with something or someone, ...",
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ...",
            "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry"
        ],
        "answer": "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch out",
        "options": [
            "go to someone",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch up",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to have one side or edge touching something, or to put something in this position",
            "same as play, ...",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way"
    },
    {
        "question": "pivot on",
        "options": [
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to be based on or planned around a particular idea or event",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to make something accepted officially by voting"
        ],
        "answer": "to be based on or planned around a particular idea or event"
    },
    {
        "question": "plan on",
        "options": [
            "to babysit, ...",
            "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "to stop something from falling by putting something under it or against it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "plant out",
        "options": [
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to take a young plant that is growing in a container and put it in the ground to grow",
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "to be able to understand something or to solve a problem, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take a young plant that is growing in a container and put it in the ground to grow"
    },
    {
        "question": "plant over",
        "options": [
            "to take an opportunity that is offered to you in a very enthusiastic way",
            "to grow plants or trees on an area of ground so that it is covered with them",
            "to become ill with a particular illness",
            "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult"
        ],
        "answer": "to grow plants or trees on an area of ground so that it is covered with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "plant up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want",
            "used about things that suddenly arrive or appear, ...",
            "to start doing something in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to grow trees, plants, or seeds in a container or an area so that they fill it completely"
        ],
        "answer": "to grow trees, plants, or seeds in a container or an area so that they fill it completely"
    },
    {
        "question": "plaster over",
        "options": [
            "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost",
            "to make someone go away or leave a place, especially by chasing them, ...",
            "cancel an appointment by sending a text message",
            "to cover a hole or surface with plaster"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover a hole or surface with plaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "plate up",
        "options": [
            "to increase the speed of a vehicle by increasing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "put food onto a plate to serve",
            "to sell something after buying it from someone else",
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "put food onto a plate to serve"
    },
    {
        "question": "play about",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "to call someone by telephone, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way, especially when you should be doing something else",
            "to give all your attention to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a silly way, especially when you should be doing something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "play along",
        "options": [
            "to eat your evening meal at home, or at a hotel when you are staying there, instead of at a restaurant",
            "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off",
            "to pretend to agree with someone or something, especially in order to get what you want or avoid an argument",
            "if something centres around a place, or if you centre something around it, it happens mainly there, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pretend to agree with someone or something, especially in order to get what you want or avoid an argument"
    },
    {
        "question": "play around",
        "options": [
            "same as play, ...",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "move or travel towards",
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation"
        ],
        "answer": "same as play, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play at",
        "options": [
            "to do something without being very serious about it, ...",
            "to give all your attention to something",
            "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them",
            "to return to a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something without being very serious about it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play away",
        "options": [
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play back",
        "options": [
            "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it",
            "to suddenly start doing something, ...",
            "concentrate",
            "to put a saddle on a horse"
        ],
        "answer": "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it"
    },
    {
        "question": "play down",
        "options": [
            "to try hard to catch someone or to get something that you need",
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ...",
            "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is",
            "have sex with"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is"
    },
    {
        "question": "play off",
        "options": [
            "used for asking where something is, ...",
            "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ...",
            "if two or more teams or players who have the same number of points in a competition play off, they play a game or games to see who is the winner",
            "same as mark, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if two or more teams or players who have the same number of points in a competition play off, they play a game or games to see who is the winner"
    },
    {
        "question": "play off against",
        "options": [
            "if you play two people off against each other, you try to cause an argument between them because you think that this will give you more power or control in a situation",
            "to spend time doing nothing useful or important",
            "same as let, ...",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you play two people off against each other, you try to cause an argument between them because you think that this will give you more power or control in a situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "play on",
        "options": [
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "to listen to someone who is speaking about a particular thing, ...",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play out",
        "options": [
            "to get ready to play a game such as tennis by hitting the ball over the net",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended",
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them",
            "to develop or end in a particular way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to develop or end in a particular way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play up",
        "options": [
            "to make something happen later than it should happen, ...",
            "to not tell someone something",
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "play up to",
        "options": [
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "to behave in a very friendly or polite way to someone because you want them to like you or to do something for you",
            "to stay somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "to continue walking in your intended direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to behave in a very friendly or polite way to someone because you want them to like you or to do something for you"
    },
    {
        "question": "play upon",
        "options": [
            "like",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you",
            "to spend an amount of money, ...",
            "exploit a weakness"
        ],
        "answer": "exploit a weakness"
    },
    {
        "question": "play with",
        "options": [
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "to masturbate, ...",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to masturbate, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plead out",
        "options": [
            "treat someone badly",
            "go somewhere quickly",
            "plead guilty to get a reduced sentence or fine",
            "to leave one place and travel to another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "plead guilty to get a reduced sentence or fine"
    },
    {
        "question": "plod along",
        "options": [
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "to progress at a very slow steady rate",
            "if a sound or picture fades in, or if you fade it in, it gradually becomes louder or clearer",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well"
        ],
        "answer": "to progress at a very slow steady rate"
    },
    {
        "question": "plonk down",
        "options": [
            "die",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ...",
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave someone somewhere to do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plop down",
        "options": [
            "to sit down carelessly but gently",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "to be a natural result of something",
            "to continue to be enough for what people need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to sit down carelessly but gently"
    },
    {
        "question": "plough ahead",
        "options": [
            "to advertise or describe someone or something in a particular way, especially in order to make them sound interesting or important",
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing",
            "same as heave",
            "to be unwilling to do or accept something"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing"
    },
    {
        "question": "plough back",
        "options": [
            "to put any profits made by a business back into it in order to make it more successful",
            "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to leave, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put any profits made by a business back into it in order to make it more successful"
    },
    {
        "question": "plough into",
        "options": [
            "mess up, ruin",
            "to invest a lot of money in something in order to improve it or make it successful, ...",
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked",
            "to start a journey, especially one that is long or difficult, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to invest a lot of money in something in order to improve it or make it successful, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plough on",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something that takes a lot of effort or is likely to cause you problems",
            "to move a knife or other object backwards and forwards several times across something, especially in order to cut it",
            "to treat someone in an unfair way, especially by criticizing or blaming them for something, ...",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something that takes a lot of effort or is likely to cause you problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "plough through",
        "options": [
            "a loud sound or music",
            "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ...",
            "exploit a weakness",
            "to divide or share something"
        ],
        "answer": "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plough up",
        "options": [
            "to speak angrily to someone because they have done something wrong",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "to get and keep a supply of something such as food to use in the future"
        ],
        "answer": "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plow back",
        "options": [
            "re-invest money you have made into a business",
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy",
            "improve a document",
            "if time creeps by, it passes very slowly"
        ],
        "answer": "re-invest money you have made into a business"
    },
    {
        "question": "plow into",
        "options": [
            "to choose one thing or person from a group, ...",
            "if something hangs over you, you worry about it or feel upset about it",
            "collide into at speed",
            "to remain in your home for a period of time"
        ],
        "answer": "collide into at speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "plow on",
        "options": [
            "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm",
            "continue doing something you don't want to",
            "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme",
            "if time creeps by, it passes very slowly"
        ],
        "answer": "continue doing something you don't want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "plow through",
        "options": [
            "eat a big meal, ...",
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ...",
            "burn brightly",
            "to avoid someone or something, or to make someone else do this"
        ],
        "answer": "eat a big meal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plow up",
        "options": [
            "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something",
            "break the surface of soil",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "break the surface of soil"
    },
    {
        "question": "pluck at",
        "options": [
            "to pull something gently and quickly several times",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "same as watch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pull something gently and quickly several times"
    },
    {
        "question": "pluck up",
        "options": [
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group",
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "muster, acquire, gather"
        ],
        "answer": "muster, acquire, gather"
    },
    {
        "question": "plug away",
        "options": [
            "leave somebody angrily",
            "to send a copy of a message or letter to someone",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties",
            "try to find something"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties"
    },
    {
        "question": "plug in",
        "options": [
            "to be connected to an electricity supply or to another piece of equipment, ...",
            "become calm or regain control of your emotions",
            "to start a journey, especially one that is long or difficult, ...",
            "pass or succeed easily"
        ],
        "answer": "to be connected to an electricity supply or to another piece of equipment, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plug into",
        "options": [
            "to leave, ...",
            "to stop living in one place and go to live in another",
            "to become connected or involved with someone or something and get some benefit from them, ...",
            "to be very happy about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become connected or involved with someone or something and get some benefit from them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plumb in",
        "options": [
            "to quickly produce something such as a meal using whatever is available",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "to connect a piece of equipment such as a washing machine to the water pipes in a room so that water can flow to and from it",
            "to make a car go backwards, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to connect a piece of equipment such as a washing machine to the water pipes in a room so that water can flow to and from it"
    },
    {
        "question": "plump down",
        "options": [
            "to spend your time thinking pleasant thoughts but not really achieving anything",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "put something in a place without taking care"
        ],
        "answer": "put something in a place without taking care"
    },
    {
        "question": "plump for",
        "options": [
            "to think that a person or thing is someone or something else",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do",
            "to say that something bad has happened, ...",
            "reconcile different positions"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "plump out",
        "options": [
            "to become fatter",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "sit down heavily"
        ],
        "answer": "to become fatter"
    },
    {
        "question": "plump up",
        "options": [
            "to have another use or job as something",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "to move away from someone, ...",
            "make something like a cushion bigger and softer by shaking it"
        ],
        "answer": "make something like a cushion bigger and softer by shaking it"
    },
    {
        "question": "plump yourself down",
        "options": [
            "fasten or secure so that it doesn't obstruct",
            "finish or complete, often with some decisive action",
            "sit down heavily",
            "to escape from a plane by parachute, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "sit down heavily"
    },
    {
        "question": "plunge in",
        "options": [
            "to ignore or avoid unpleasant facts",
            "to phone several people or companies in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to quickly jump or dive into water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly jump or dive into water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plunge into",
        "options": [
            "if money is sloshing around, a lot of it is available or people are spending a lot of it",
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ...",
            "same as get",
            "to jump or dive into water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to jump or dive into water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "plunk down",
        "options": [
            "to pay a particular amount of money for something",
            "used for telling someone to move away from a person or place, ...",
            "order something by post",
            "to spend your time thinking pleasant thoughts but not really achieving anything"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay a particular amount of money for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "ply with",
        "options": [
            "to keep asking someone questions, ...",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another",
            "improve, ...",
            "to spend a period of time relaxing or sleeping after doing something tiring"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep asking someone questions, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "point out",
        "options": [
            "to point a weapon at someone, ...",
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it",
            "to tell information or facts that you should keep secret, ...",
            "to tell someone something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "point to",
        "options": [
            "to make a photograph bigger, ...",
            "to show the truth or importance of something",
            "same as muddle",
            "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem"
        ],
        "answer": "to show the truth or importance of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "point up",
        "options": [
            "to represent the feelings or opinions of another person or group of people",
            "to emphasize something",
            "to shout something",
            "to buy a lot of something so that it is available when you need it"
        ],
        "answer": "to emphasize something"
    },
    {
        "question": "poke about",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ...",
            "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is",
            "to start to sleep",
            "to have enough money to pay for the things that you really need in order to live, but no more"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "poke around",
        "options": [
            "same as tuck in",
            "to find something or someone that is difficult to find",
            "to try to find out information about something",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "polish off",
        "options": [
            "to put on the clothes you were wearing originally, before you took them off, ...",
            "to start to have an effect, ...",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ...",
            "talk at length about computing"
        ],
        "answer": "to defeat or kill someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "polish up",
        "options": [
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "same as polish",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ...",
            "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as polish"
    },
    {
        "question": "pony up",
        "options": [
            "become calm or regain control of your emotions",
            "to think about a time or event in the past, ...",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to pay for something"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "poop out",
        "options": [
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "to decide not to do something because you are too tired",
            "to spoil something by doing it wrongly",
            "to read the measurement on a piece of equipment or graph"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to do something because you are too tired"
    },
    {
        "question": "poop out on",
        "options": [
            "to criticize or punish someone severely",
            "fail to keep an appointment",
            "connect with someone or contact them",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fail to keep an appointment"
    },
    {
        "question": "pootle along",
        "options": [
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car",
            "to gradually become less involved in something, ...",
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "to waste time when you should be working"
        ],
        "answer": "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop down",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing or person to another, ...",
            "leave something you don't like",
            "travel somewhere to visit",
            "store or hide something in a safe place"
        ],
        "answer": "travel somewhere to visit"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop down to",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere quickly to do something, often to buy or get something",
            "to develop or end in a particular way, ...",
            "to tell information or facts that you should keep secret, ...",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere quickly to do something, often to buy or get something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop in",
        "options": [
            "short circuit",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "visit for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop off",
        "options": [
            "try to keep something",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to die",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time"
        ],
        "answer": "to die"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop out",
        "options": [
            "if words pop out, you say them suddenly without thinking about it first",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ...",
            "not go to school or work, or leave early when you shouldn't"
        ],
        "answer": "if words pop out, you say them suddenly without thinking about it first"
    },
    {
        "question": "pop up",
        "options": [
            "to go to a place for only a short period of time before continuing a journey",
            "get money off someone",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly"
        ],
        "answer": "to appear very quickly or suddenly"
    },
    {
        "question": "pore over",
        "options": [
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "to examine or read something very carefully and in a lot of detail",
            "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing",
            "same as shade"
        ],
        "answer": "to examine or read something very carefully and in a lot of detail"
    },
    {
        "question": "pose as",
        "options": [
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people",
            "to succeed in a very difficult situation, or to help someone to do this, ...",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people"
    },
    {
        "question": "post off",
        "options": [
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "same as post",
            "to reduce an amount, ...",
            "fill a venue"
        ],
        "answer": "same as post"
    },
    {
        "question": "post up",
        "options": [
            "same as muddle",
            "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another",
            "same as post"
        ],
        "answer": "same as post"
    },
    {
        "question": "pot on",
        "options": [
            "to move a plant into a larger container because it has grown bigger",
            "if something dawns on you, you realize it for the first time",
            "to get rid of a bad feeling or condition by going for a walk, ...",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another"
        ],
        "answer": "to move a plant into a larger container because it has grown bigger"
    },
    {
        "question": "potter about",
        "options": [
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "retract a statement",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure"
        ],
        "answer": "spend time doing little things for pleasure"
    },
    {
        "question": "potter around",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone give you something without asking for it directly",
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want",
            "to try to bite something without in fact managing to bite it"
        ],
        "answer": "spend some time doing little things for pleasure"
    },
    {
        "question": "pound into",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "argue with someone about a specific subject",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism"
        ],
        "answer": "to teach someone something by repeating it many times"
    },
    {
        "question": "pound out",
        "options": [
            "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth",
            "be depressed, ...",
            "to do something in a very short period of time, ...",
            "to continue to do or use something, and not change it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something in a very short period of time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pour down",
        "options": [
            "to move away from someone or something, ...",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you",
            "same as pour",
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as pour"
    },
    {
        "question": "pour forth",
        "options": [
            "come to understand",
            "emerge from a place in large numbers",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ...",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "emerge from a place in large numbers"
    },
    {
        "question": "pour into",
        "options": [
            "to move up and come into view with a short quick movement",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "force someone to leave",
            "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to give a lot of effort, money, or help to someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pour out",
        "options": [
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference.",
            "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ...",
            "to make someone feel strange",
            "do something quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "power down",
        "options": [
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "same as haul, ...",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ...",
            "to switch a computer off in the correct way"
        ],
        "answer": "to switch a computer off in the correct way"
    },
    {
        "question": "power off",
        "options": [
            "to sleep in someone\u2019s house as a guest for one night",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "cut the electricity to a computer or device to turn it off",
            "do something slowly, with difficulty, unwillingly or considerable effort"
        ],
        "answer": "cut the electricity to a computer or device to turn it off"
    },
    {
        "question": "power up",
        "options": [
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ...",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "to switch a computer on in the correct way"
        ],
        "answer": "to switch a computer on in the correct way"
    },
    {
        "question": "practise on",
        "options": [
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely",
            "to force or persuade someone to tell you something when they do not want to",
            "to do something bad or unpleasant to someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something bad or unpleasant to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "prattle on",
        "options": [
            "make progress, often after a pause or delay",
            "talk too much",
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "same as put forward, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "talk too much"
    },
    {
        "question": "preside over",
        "options": [
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to relax",
            "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening",
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them"
        ],
        "answer": "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening"
    },
    {
        "question": "press ahead",
        "options": [
            "an imperative used to tell someone to go faster, especially when driving",
            "to continue sleeping after the time that you usually wake up",
            "to tell someone in authority about something bad that another person has done",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions"
    },
    {
        "question": "press for",
        "options": [
            "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ...",
            "same as open, ...",
            "to give something back to someone, ...",
            "to borrow a book from a library, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "press forward with",
        "options": [
            "criticise something strongly",
            "employ someone for something specific",
            "continue or go ahead with a project, process, plan, etc",
            "an imperative used to tell someone to go faster, especially when driving"
        ],
        "answer": "continue or go ahead with a project, process, plan, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "press into",
        "options": [
            "same as piss",
            "bring or force into use",
            "to begin a new business or new type of business, ...",
            "abuse someone because you're angry"
        ],
        "answer": "bring or force into use"
    },
    {
        "question": "press on",
        "options": [
            "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ...",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something",
            "same as press, ...",
            "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as press, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "press upon",
        "options": [
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is"
        ],
        "answer": "pressure someone to accept something offered"
    },
    {
        "question": "presume on",
        "options": [
            "to continue sleeping for a long time, ...",
            "to make a noise less loud, ...",
            "if a building, garden etc backs onto a place, that place is directly behind it",
            "to expect more than you should get or have a right to, especially in your relationships with other people"
        ],
        "answer": "to expect more than you should get or have a right to, especially in your relationships with other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "prevail on",
        "options": [
            "to ask or persuade someone to do something",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to do something to stop something bad from happening"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask or persuade someone to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "prey on",
        "options": [
            "to hunt another creature in order to eat it, ...",
            "same as block in, ...",
            "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it",
            "to win a prize, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hunt another creature in order to eat it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "prey upon",
        "options": [
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way",
            "act in a dangerous or reckless way, especially when driving fast",
            "exploit or harm, ...",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place"
        ],
        "answer": "exploit or harm, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "price in",
        "options": [
            "to mix something into the ground by digging, ...",
            "to hit someone hard in the face, ...",
            "include the affects of possible future events when assessing the value of something",
            "to not tell someone something"
        ],
        "answer": "include the affects of possible future events when assessing the value of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "price up",
        "options": [
            "charge more for something",
            "to leave, ...",
            "to make it seem that someone is guilty of a crime when they are not, ...",
            "to be good enough, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "charge more for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "prick out",
        "options": [
            "same as put, ...",
            "to make a profit from something, ...",
            "to study hard or learn about something in order to prepare for a test, meeting etc",
            "to move a small young plant into a larger pot or container so that it can grow bigger"
        ],
        "answer": "to move a small young plant into a larger pot or container so that it can grow bigger"
    },
    {
        "question": "print out",
        "options": [
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer"
    },
    {
        "question": "prise out of",
        "options": [
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "to stop living in one place and go to live in another",
            "to move to a particular room or place",
            "have a good time when intoxicated"
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty"
    },
    {
        "question": "proceed against",
        "options": [
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way",
            "to draw a line through written words",
            "to push a sword through someone\u2019s body, ...",
            "to begin a case against someone in a court of law"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a case against someone in a court of law"
    },
    {
        "question": "proceed from",
        "options": [
            "to feel sympathy for someone",
            "same as mop, ...",
            "same as get around",
            "to have a particular cause or origin"
        ],
        "answer": "to have a particular cause or origin"
    },
    {
        "question": "profit from",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear",
            "confront someone and let them know you are prepared to fight",
            "to make a profit from something, ...",
            "to remove things from a group, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a profit from something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pronounce on",
        "options": [
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way",
            "have sex",
            "to remove the dirt from something, especially from an upright surface"
        ],
        "answer": "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way"
    },
    {
        "question": "prop up",
        "options": [
            "same as curl, ...",
            "to become covered with ice",
            "to stop something from falling by putting something under it or against it, ...",
            "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop something from falling by putting something under it or against it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "provide against",
        "options": [
            "ruin or spoil something",
            "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme",
            "to arrange for yourself or someone else to stay at a hotel, hospital etc, ...",
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "provide for",
        "options": [
            "to make it possible for something to happen in the future, ...",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "be connected with",
            "to be sent by post, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make it possible for something to happen in the future, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pry out",
        "options": [
            "to improve, ...",
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident",
            "to treat something carefully so that it stays in good condition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up"
    },
    {
        "question": "psych out",
        "options": [
            "to react against someone or something that you do not like but cannot change",
            "to talk or behave very confidently in order to make someone who you are competing against feel nervous and less likely to succeed",
            "to push someone or something hard so that they fall from the position that they are in",
            "to give someone an unpleasant job that no one else wants to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk or behave very confidently in order to make someone who you are competing against feel nervous and less likely to succeed"
    },
    {
        "question": "psych up",
        "options": [
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to drink something, usually alcohol, quickly, swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to stop something from happening, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pucker up",
        "options": [
            "to admit something, ...",
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "same as ring",
            "same as pucker"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pucker"
    },
    {
        "question": "puff out",
        "options": [
            "to avoid using something, or to use less of it, ...",
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want",
            "if air or smoke puffs out, or if you puff it out, you blow it out with a short breath, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if air or smoke puffs out, or if you puff it out, you blow it out with a short breath, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "puff up",
        "options": [
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly",
            "depart furtively",
            "to encourage someone to react by making them feel very angry or upset",
            "to swell because of an injury or illness, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to swell because of an injury or illness, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull ahead",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ...",
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter",
            "to improve, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to make progress faster than someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull apart",
        "options": [
            "to measure part of someone\u2019s body in order to give them the right shoes or clothing, ...",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting",
            "same as pass, ...",
            "to arrange for something to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to separate two people or animals that are fighting"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull away",
        "options": [
            "to do something quickly, easily, and without much effort, ...",
            "same as pull, ...",
            "become nervous, tense or unable to relax",
            "to clearly need something a lot"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pull, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull back",
        "options": [
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time",
            "to score a goal when your team is losing in a football match, ...",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well",
            "to give a place or an object the same name as a person or another thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to score a goal when your team is losing in a football match, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull down",
        "options": [
            "to earn a particular amount of money, ...",
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas",
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like",
            "to ignore someone\u2019s ideas, feelings, or opinions because you do not think they are important"
        ],
        "answer": "to earn a particular amount of money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull for",
        "options": [
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ...",
            "to forget to take someone or something with you, ...",
            "to feel sympathy for someone",
            "support"
        ],
        "answer": "support"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull in",
        "options": [
            "to buy something expensive",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "same as pull, ...",
            "to depend on something or someone"
        ],
        "answer": "same as pull, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull into",
        "options": [
            "make a fire burn less, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls into a place, they stop there",
            "to ask several people for information or advice",
            "to ask someone about someone else, especially about how they are or what they are doing"
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle or driver pulls into a place, they stop there"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull off",
        "options": [
            "to produce a loud clear sound",
            "same as come at, ...",
            "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ...",
            "to take off clothes, especially quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take off clothes, especially quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull on",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them",
            "to put on clothes, especially quickly",
            "to discover a fact or piece of information, ...",
            "exchange something for money, collect winnings, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put on clothes, especially quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull out",
        "options": [
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "same as mail"
        ],
        "answer": "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull over",
        "options": [
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly",
            "to dig something out of the ground, especially with your hands",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls over, they stop by the side of the road, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle or driver pulls over, they stop by the side of the road, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull round",
        "options": [
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "same as hire, ...",
            "to start to get better after being ill or in a bad situation",
            "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to get better after being ill or in a bad situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull through",
        "options": [
            "to make someone learn or understand something by repeating it many times",
            "to succeed in a very difficult situation, or to help someone to do this, ...",
            "same as foul, ...",
            "to move so that you are behind someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in a very difficult situation, or to help someone to do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull to",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "close a door or window that has been left open",
            "to stop something from having any effect",
            "to start eating in a very enthusiastic way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "close a door or window that has been left open"
    },
    {
        "question": "pull together",
        "options": [
            "produce or issue, usually from a machine",
            "break or damage, ...",
            "to dress or behave in public in a particular way, especially when this makes you look or seem silly",
            "to combine different things so that they form a single unit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to combine different things so that they form a single unit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull up",
        "options": [
            "avoid doing something",
            "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls up, they stop, ...",
            "to grow taller very quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a vehicle or driver pulls up, they stop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pull yourself together",
        "options": [
            "become calm or regain control of your emotions",
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk",
            "to combine different things so that they form a single unit, ...",
            "to consider the facts about something in an organized and thorough way"
        ],
        "answer": "become calm or regain control of your emotions"
    },
    {
        "question": "pump (money) into",
        "options": [
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ...",
            "invest in something",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too"
        ],
        "answer": "invest in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pump in",
        "options": [
            "to progress at a very slow steady rate",
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "make a decision by throwing a coin and seeing which side lands face up"
        ],
        "answer": "to invest a lot of money in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pump into",
        "options": [
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to invest a lot of money in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to invest a lot of money in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "pump out",
        "options": [
            "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ...",
            "to begin working on something or dealing with something, ...",
            "be elsewhere; on holiday, etc.",
            "to produce a lot of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a lot of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "pump up",
        "options": [
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ...",
            "to fill something with air using a pump, ...",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way"
        ],
        "answer": "to fill something with air using a pump, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "punch in",
        "options": [
            "to live or work in a place in which you have a lot more space than you need",
            "a loud sound or music",
            "to try to make someone or something leave a place, ...",
            "clock in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "clock in, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "punch out",
        "options": [
            "same as balance",
            "to clock off, ...",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things that are very similar",
            "to make someone feel very annoyed or upset"
        ],
        "answer": "to clock off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "punch up",
        "options": [
            "to wish to enter a place, ...",
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure",
            "to make information appear on something such as the screen of a computer or the screen of a till in a shop, by pressing keys or buttons",
            "to become a member of a family, religion, social group etc by becoming the husband or wife of someone who already belongs to it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make information appear on something such as the screen of a computer or the screen of a till in a shop, by pressing keys or buttons"
    },
    {
        "question": "push about",
        "options": [
            "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way",
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting",
            "to start a new activity, ...",
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way"
    },
    {
        "question": "push ahead",
        "options": [
            "to target, ...",
            "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to",
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want",
            "to continue trying to achieve something despite opposition or difficulties"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue trying to achieve something despite opposition or difficulties"
    },
    {
        "question": "push along",
        "options": [
            "to arrive unexpectedly, ...",
            "to decide not to do something that you had promised or agreed to do",
            "to stay friendly with someone, especially someone who can help you",
            "leave, go home"
        ],
        "answer": "leave, go home"
    },
    {
        "question": "push around",
        "options": [
            "be ill",
            "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done",
            "to clearly need something a lot"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep telling someone what to do in an unfair and unpleasant way"
    },
    {
        "question": "push aside",
        "options": [
            "to make a vehicle stop by waving your arm or hand at the driver",
            "pay a debt over time",
            "to think that you are better or more important than someone else, or to think that something is not good enough for you",
            "to refuse to think about something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to think about something unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "push away",
        "options": [
            "perform surgery",
            "to say or write the letters of a word in the correct order, ...",
            "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention",
            "to join together in a group to hurt, frighten, or fight someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to show that you do not want someone\u2019s help or attention"
    },
    {
        "question": "push back",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a later time for something, ...",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something",
            "to waste time, energy, or money",
            "if two or more teams or players who have the same number of points in a competition play off, they play a game or games to see who is the winner"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange a later time for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "push for",
        "options": [
            "to formally offer an idea or proposal to someone for them to consider or accept",
            "to try hard to get or achieve something, ...",
            "to keep telling other people what to do",
            "same as top up, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try hard to get or achieve something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "push forward",
        "options": [
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "same as push, ...",
            "to make someone feel very tired, ...",
            "be submitted, arrive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as push, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "push in",
        "options": [
            "to stand in front of people who have been waiting longer than you, in a way that is unfair",
            "invite",
            "same as lead to",
            "to consider something as separate from other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stand in front of people who have been waiting longer than you, in a way that is unfair"
    },
    {
        "question": "push off",
        "options": [
            "to put someone in prison, ...",
            "to turn around quickly where you are standing",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to make something happen, especially to cause changes in a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "push on",
        "options": [
            "to search very hard for something, ...",
            "to continue a journey, especially after stopping for a period of time, ...",
            "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ...",
            "move into a lane of traffic without making other cars stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue a journey, especially after stopping for a period of time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "push out",
        "options": [
            "to start a journey by ship, ...",
            "if a shop has something in, it is available in the shop for you to buy, ...",
            "force someone to leave",
            "used for asking someone to repeat what they have just said, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "force someone to leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "push over",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something that takes a lot of effort or is likely to cause you problems",
            "to push someone or something hard so that they fall from the position that they are in",
            "applaud",
            "to happen, especially by chance, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to push someone or something hard so that they fall from the position that they are in"
    },
    {
        "question": "push through",
        "options": [
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ...",
            "same as rain",
            "to succeed in getting a law, agreement etc accepted quickly although a lot of people oppose it"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in getting a law, agreement etc accepted quickly although a lot of people oppose it"
    },
    {
        "question": "put about",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with a lot of different people, ...",
            "criticise harshly or punish someone for something",
            "pass quickly",
            "use correction fluid to cover a mistake in a written text"
        ],
        "answer": "to have sex with a lot of different people, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put across",
        "options": [
            "to explain an idea, belief etc in a way that is easy to understand, ...",
            "to deliberately put someone in an unfavorable situation",
            "to go to work, ...",
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to explain an idea, belief etc in a way that is easy to understand, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put around",
        "options": [
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "same as put about",
            "to do something to stop something bad from happening"
        ],
        "answer": "same as put about"
    },
    {
        "question": "put aside",
        "options": [
            "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it",
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ...",
            "leave the top deck of a ship"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put at",
        "options": [
            "to calculate the cost, amount, size etc of something",
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem",
            "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to calculate the cost, amount, size etc of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "put away",
        "options": [
            "same as spy, ...",
            "do something out of a car",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to move around noisily in water"
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put back",
        "options": [
            "to avoid dealing directly with a problem, ...",
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to make something happen later than it should happen, ...",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something happen later than it should happen, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put before",
        "options": [
            "used for asking where something is, ...",
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim",
            "to formally offer an idea or proposal to someone for them to consider or accept"
        ],
        "answer": "to formally offer an idea or proposal to someone for them to consider or accept"
    },
    {
        "question": "put by",
        "options": [
            "same as put aside",
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to succeed in keeping a job, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as put aside"
    },
    {
        "question": "put down",
        "options": [
            "to take out, ...",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ...",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to write something on a piece of paper, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write something on a piece of paper, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put down as",
        "options": [
            "to continue to talk about something unpleasant that someone else no longer wants to talk or think about",
            "to meet someone and start a sexual relationship with them",
            "to think that someone is a particular type of person",
            "same as file"
        ],
        "answer": "to think that someone is a particular type of person"
    },
    {
        "question": "put down for",
        "options": [
            "to write on a list that someone agrees to give or take something, ...",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "to buy part of a business, especially in order to get control of it, ...",
            "to move away from someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write on a list that someone agrees to give or take something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put down to",
        "options": [
            "to prevent someone from making progress, ...",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "if you put something down to a particular reason, you think it has happened for that reason, ...",
            "to be about a subject, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you put something down to a particular reason, you think it has happened for that reason, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put forth",
        "options": [
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ...",
            "to be as good as someone or something, ...",
            "if a regular event comes round, it happens again, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to state or offer an idea, opinion, plan etc, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put forward",
        "options": [
            "to get and keep a supply of something such as food to use in the future",
            "to think about something carefully or discuss it carefully with other people before making a decision about it",
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "to kill someone by shooting them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put in",
        "options": [
            "to jump or dive into water, ...",
            "to deal with or take responsibility for someone or something",
            "if a ship puts in, it stops at a port, ...",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you"
        ],
        "answer": "if a ship puts in, it stops at a port, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put in for",
        "options": [
            "to phone someone, ...",
            "if you fit things together, you join them in the right way to make something, ...",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair",
            "to officially ask for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to officially ask for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put into",
        "options": [
            "to not become involved with something",
            "to invest money in something, ...",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way"
        ],
        "answer": "to invest money in something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put off",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ...",
            "to physically attack someone",
            "to bring a business, organization, or project into existence, ...",
            "to add something to something else to make it bigger or more satisfactory"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put on",
        "options": [
            "same as put, ...",
            "to make something necessary or suitable, ...",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to go somewhere where no one can find you"
        ],
        "answer": "same as put, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put onto",
        "options": [
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ...",
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress",
            "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need",
            "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need"
    },
    {
        "question": "put out",
        "options": [
            "same as mount, ...",
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "surprise or shock",
            "to get rid of a bad feeling or condition by going for a walk, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to switch off a light, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put over",
        "options": [
            "same as put, ...",
            "to improve the appearance of someone or something",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as put, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put round",
        "options": [
            "to use a spoon or knife to add something slowly and gently to a mixture, ...",
            "same as put about",
            "to discuss a problem or a plan",
            "to officially make someone else the owner of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as put about"
    },
    {
        "question": "put through",
        "options": [
            "to persuade someone to do something that they do not really want to do",
            "to make someone do or experience something difficult or unpleasant, ...",
            "to start to get better after being ill or in a bad situation",
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone do or experience something difficult or unpleasant, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put to",
        "options": [
            "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ...",
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to ask someone a question, ...",
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone a question, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put together",
        "options": [
            "drive a vehicle as fast as possible",
            "to make something by joining all its parts, ...",
            "to get something again that you had lost such as power, especially gradually and with difficulty, ...",
            "same as open, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something by joining all its parts, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put towards",
        "options": [
            "fail to keep a promise, arrangement, etc",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something",
            "to defeat or kill someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something"
    },
    {
        "question": "put under",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way, especially when you should be doing something else",
            "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening",
            "to calculate the total of several numbers or amounts, ...",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug"
    },
    {
        "question": "put up",
        "options": [
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to suddenly put someone somewhere that they cannot escape from",
            "make reasonable progress without any serious problems",
            "same as finish, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as put forward, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "put up to",
        "options": [
            "criticise, find fault",
            "to encourage someone to do something stupid or wrong",
            "make electrical connections",
            "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to encourage someone to do something stupid or wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "put up with",
        "options": [
            "close a particular computer program that requires a name and password",
            "to stop considering something as a possibility",
            "go out",
            "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept someone or something unpleasant in a patient way"
    },
    {
        "question": "puzzle out",
        "options": [
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it",
            "to stop talking or making a noise, ...",
            "to leave a place quickly, ...",
            "make something smart or more presentable"
        ],
        "answer": "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "puzzle over",
        "options": [
            "to raise something upwards, especially your arm or hand, ...",
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "used to tell someone to go away because they're annoying you"
        ],
        "answer": "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them"
    },
    {
        "question": "quarrel out",
        "options": [
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm",
            "argue with someone about a specific subject",
            "retract a statement",
            "to prevent an opponent from winning in a game or competition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "argue with someone about a specific subject"
    },
    {
        "question": "quarrel with",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone violently",
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "to cheat by not obeying the rules on something, ...",
            "to cover a window or door with wooden boards"
        ],
        "answer": "to think someone or something is wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "queer up",
        "options": [
            "to have some of a particular quality",
            "express or display emotions openly, ...",
            "mess up, ruin",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "mess up, ruin"
    },
    {
        "question": "quieten down",
        "options": [
            "to get permission from someone to do something, ...",
            "fall silent",
            "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ...",
            "to show something to a lot of people because you want to impress them"
        ],
        "answer": "fall silent"
    },
    {
        "question": "quit on",
        "options": [
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner",
            "stop working or functioning, ...",
            "leave the top deck of a ship"
        ],
        "answer": "stop working or functioning, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "race off",
        "options": [
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "bring or force into use"
        ],
        "answer": "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "rack off",
        "options": [
            "to move in order to make more room for someone else",
            "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ...",
            "to make someone angry, or to argue with them, ...",
            "used to tell someone to go away because they're annoying you"
        ],
        "answer": "used to tell someone to go away because they're annoying you"
    },
    {
        "question": "rack out",
        "options": [
            "to be careful",
            "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it",
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "sleep, take a nap"
        ],
        "answer": "sleep, take a nap"
    },
    {
        "question": "rack up",
        "options": [
            "be connected with",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to get a large amount of sales or profits, ...",
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word"
        ],
        "answer": "to get a large amount of sales or profits, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "railroad through",
        "options": [
            "applaud",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ...",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise",
            "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to"
        ],
        "answer": "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain down",
        "options": [
            "repeatedly criticise someone verbally",
            "same as rain",
            "used for telling someone to stop talking or to make less noise",
            "to expect something to happen and plan for it"
        ],
        "answer": "same as rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain down on",
        "options": [
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like",
            "fall in large numbers",
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "to prevent an amount or number from passing a limit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fall in large numbers"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain off",
        "options": [
            "if a sports game or other outside event is rained off, it does not happen because of rain",
            "move in a place making a lot of noise",
            "if people sit in, they take part in a sit-in",
            "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous"
        ],
        "answer": "if a sports game or other outside event is rained off, it does not happen because of rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain out",
        "options": [
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ...",
            "same as rain",
            "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake in",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to tell someone in authority about something bad that another person has done",
            "to earn a lot of money",
            "if a situation is looking up, it is getting better, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to earn a lot of money"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake it in",
        "options": [
            "make a lot of money",
            "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you",
            "to depend on something such as luck or chance to help you to achieve something, usually because you have no other choice",
            "to turn and face in the opposite direction"
        ],
        "answer": "make a lot of money"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake off",
        "options": [
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "to finish a drawing of something using ink",
            "to take a part of the profits from something, especially in an unfair or dishonest way",
            "same as tuck in"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a part of the profits from something, especially in an unfair or dishonest way"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake over",
        "options": [
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people",
            "to continue to talk about something unpleasant that someone else no longer wants to talk or think about"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to talk about something unpleasant that someone else no longer wants to talk or think about"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake through",
        "options": [
            "if a machine or computer shuts down, or if someone shuts it down, it stops operating, ...",
            "to take someone away to a place they do not want to go",
            "to search a place quickly for something",
            "same as rifle"
        ],
        "answer": "to search a place quickly for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "rake up",
        "options": [
            "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about",
            "mess up, ruin",
            "same as tape",
            "to start to play or sing a piece of music, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about"
    },
    {
        "question": "rally round",
        "options": [
            "to work with other people in order to help someone in a difficult situation",
            "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom",
            "to enter a room suddenly and noisily, usually interrupting someone in a rude way",
            "to keep asking someone questions, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to work with other people in order to help someone in a difficult situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "ramble on",
        "options": [
            "to happen suddenly or unexpectedly, ...",
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation",
            "to talk or write about something for a long time in a way that is boring, annoying, or confusing",
            "to cost a particular amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk or write about something for a long time in a way that is boring, annoying, or confusing"
    },
    {
        "question": "ramp up",
        "options": [
            "equalize one\ufffds competitive position",
            "same as go around, ...",
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "to increase something such as a rate or level, especially the rate at which goods are produced"
        ],
        "answer": "to increase something such as a rate or level, especially the rate at which goods are produced"
    },
    {
        "question": "rap out",
        "options": [
            "to say something loudly and quickly",
            "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something",
            "to stop working, ...",
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say something loudly and quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "rat on",
        "options": [
            "if someone is shut out of something, they are not allowed to do it or be involved in it",
            "to change your position or opinion and start supporting someone you were arguing or fighting with",
            "to not do something that you promised to do, ...",
            "to invite someone to go somewhere such as a restaurant or cinema with you, often because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to not do something that you promised to do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rat out",
        "options": [
            "inform the authorities about someone",
            "to begin an attack in boxing with a particular hand or hit, ...",
            "to masturbate",
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use"
        ],
        "answer": "inform the authorities about someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "rat through",
        "options": [
            "open a particular computer program that requires a name and password",
            "look for something hurriedly",
            "to make something better than it was before, or to do something better than you did before",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you"
        ],
        "answer": "look for something hurriedly"
    },
    {
        "question": "ratchet up",
        "options": [
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ...",
            "same as tuck in",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "increase"
        ],
        "answer": "increase"
    },
    {
        "question": "ration out",
        "options": [
            "to divide something among people so that each one gets a small amount",
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to divide something among people so that each one gets a small amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle around",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a later time for something, ...",
            "to live or work in a place in which you have a lot more space than you need",
            "criticise, find fault",
            "say something quickly without thinking, especially if you shouldn't"
        ],
        "answer": "to live or work in a place in which you have a lot more space than you need"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle off",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to say something quickly, especially something that you have learned by memory",
            "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ...",
            "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say something quickly, especially something that you have learned by memory"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle on",
        "options": [
            "get so emotional that you lose control",
            "to take a young plant that is growing in a container and put it in the ground to grow",
            "sit and do nothing, especially when you should be working",
            "to talk quickly and for a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk quickly and for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle out",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ...",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other",
            "to produce a series of quick loud noises or words",
            "to put money into your bank account"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a series of quick loud noises or words"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle through",
        "options": [
            "to do or say something quickly because you want to finish it as soon as you can",
            "travel somewhere to visit",
            "to admit that something is true or that you have done something wrong",
            "to not take advantage of an opportunity"
        ],
        "answer": "to do or say something quickly because you want to finish it as soon as you can"
    },
    {
        "question": "rattle up",
        "options": [
            "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition",
            "to put a document away in a file",
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "escape notice and be approved"
        ],
        "answer": "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition"
    },
    {
        "question": "reach out",
        "options": [
            "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something",
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ...",
            "to use something as a way of preventing people from discovering information about you",
            "same as gulp"
        ],
        "answer": "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "reach out for",
        "options": [
            "to give people a particular opinion of someone or something",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "try to achieve something difficult",
            "to read or deal with a lot of boring information"
        ],
        "answer": "try to achieve something difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "reach out to",
        "options": [
            "fasten something to the ground",
            "to ask someone for help, ...",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them"
        ],
        "answer": "to ask someone for help, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "react against",
        "options": [
            "to do the opposite of what a person, set of rules etc says you should do, because you disagree with them",
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ...",
            "to force someone to leave a place or organization, ...",
            "to gradually stop using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to do the opposite of what a person, set of rules etc says you should do, because you disagree with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "read back",
        "options": [
            "to look at and speak words that you wrote earlier, usually so that someone can check that what you have written is correct",
            "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine",
            "keep something near you",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business"
        ],
        "answer": "to look at and speak words that you wrote earlier, usually so that someone can check that what you have written is correct"
    },
    {
        "question": "read for",
        "options": [
            "to study for a particular degree, ...",
            "to try hard to understand a difficult idea or to solve a difficult problem",
            "to find a successful way of dealing with something by thinking about it",
            "to choose one thing or person from a group, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to study for a particular degree, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "read into",
        "options": [
            "treat someone badly",
            "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist",
            "consume, take, buy something other people may want",
            "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea"
        ],
        "answer": "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist"
    },
    {
        "question": "read off",
        "options": [
            "to read the measurement on a piece of equipment or graph",
            "ignore, exclude, ...",
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly",
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier"
        ],
        "answer": "to read the measurement on a piece of equipment or graph"
    },
    {
        "question": "read out",
        "options": [
            "to deal with something such as a problem or a strong feeling by thinking and talking about it",
            "to call someone by telephone, ...",
            "to say the words that you are reading so that people can hear them",
            "to try to find something by looking everywhere, even in places that you would prefer not to look in"
        ],
        "answer": "to say the words that you are reading so that people can hear them"
    },
    {
        "question": "read through",
        "options": [
            "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it",
            "remove by biting",
            "same as heap",
            "to say that someone has achieved something because of a particular thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it"
    },
    {
        "question": "read up on",
        "options": [
            "to not leave a person or place",
            "to continue for longer than expected or planned, ...",
            "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ...",
            "to get information on a particular subject by reading a lot about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to get information on a particular subject by reading a lot about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "rear up",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear",
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times",
            "same as rear",
            "to connect something with something else"
        ],
        "answer": "same as rear"
    },
    {
        "question": "reason out",
        "options": [
            "to become covered with ice",
            "to talk quickly and for a long time",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to find a successful way of dealing with something by thinking about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to find a successful way of dealing with something by thinking about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "reason with",
        "options": [
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "to get a lot of pleasure or enjoyment from something",
            "to try to persuade someone to do something by explaining why you think it is sensible",
            "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to persuade someone to do something by explaining why you think it is sensible"
    },
    {
        "question": "reckon on",
        "options": [
            "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ...",
            "to expect something to happen and plan for it",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to expect something to happen and plan for it"
    },
    {
        "question": "reckon with",
        "options": [
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to take the total of a column of numbers from the bottom of one page to the top of the next, ...",
            "be in the correct or appropriate location with other items",
            "to be forced to deal with someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be forced to deal with someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "reckon without",
        "options": [
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to not consider or include something in your plans and so not be prepared for it",
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not consider or include something in your plans and so not be prepared for it"
    },
    {
        "question": "reduce to",
        "options": [
            "to force someone into an unpleasant state or situation, ...",
            "to suddenly stop working correctly, ...",
            "prepare for something that will require a great effort",
            "same as slow, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone into an unpleasant state or situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "reel in",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone, or to find something by chance, ...",
            "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod",
            "to give power or control to someone else, ...",
            "to guard, protect, or be in charge of someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to bring a fish towards you by turning the reel of a fishing rod"
    },
    {
        "question": "reel off",
        "options": [
            "to emphasize something",
            "to give something to a person in authority, ...",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort"
        ],
        "answer": "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort"
    },
    {
        "question": "reel out",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as rope become straighter by removing it from an object shaped like a wheel that it was put around",
            "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ...",
            "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm",
            "to write exactly what someone has written or said"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something such as rope become straighter by removing it from an object shaped like a wheel that it was put around"
    },
    {
        "question": "reflect on",
        "options": [
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "to give people a particular opinion of someone or something",
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language",
            "leave a place in a hurry"
        ],
        "answer": "to give people a particular opinion of someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "rein in",
        "options": [
            "to make something explode, ...",
            "sit and do nothing, especially when you should be working",
            "to be very sad because you want to be with someone who you love, or want something that you do not have",
            "to make a horse stop or go more slowly by pulling its reins, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a horse stop or go more slowly by pulling its reins, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rejoice in",
        "options": [
            "to make someone or something different and special, ...",
            "to be very happy about something, ...",
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something",
            "to not go to bed"
        ],
        "answer": "to be very happy about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "relate to",
        "options": [
            "to appear very quickly or suddenly",
            "to move to a particular room or place",
            "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ...",
            "to be about something, or to be connected with something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be about something, or to be connected with something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "relieve of",
        "options": [
            "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead",
            "same as stoop",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to steal something from someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to steal something from someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "remind of",
        "options": [
            "same as lift",
            "to babysit, ...",
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ...",
            "to make someone remember something that happened in the past, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone remember something that happened in the past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rent out",
        "options": [
            "to make special conditions for something so that you do not have to follow the usual rules",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly",
            "let, grant a service or allow usage for a fee",
            "to get something again that you had lost such as power, especially gradually and with difficulty, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "let, grant a service or allow usage for a fee"
    },
    {
        "question": "repair to",
        "options": [
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to move to a particular room or place",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "to be given to someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move to a particular room or place"
    },
    {
        "question": "repeat on",
        "options": [
            "if food repeats on you, it makes you burp (=causes air to come up from your stomach and out through your mouth) for a long time after you have eaten it",
            "to have existed since or for a particular time, ...",
            "to change your position or opinion and start supporting someone you were arguing or fighting with",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "if food repeats on you, it makes you burp (=causes air to come up from your stomach and out through your mouth) for a long time after you have eaten it"
    },
    {
        "question": "report back",
        "options": [
            "to tell or send someone information that you have discovered, ...",
            "to make someone become very excited, ...",
            "leave suddenly",
            "if information goes in, you understand it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to tell or send someone information that you have discovered, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "report in",
        "options": [
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to go somewhere or to talk to someone by telephone in order to let them know that you are ready to start working or that you are in a particular place",
            "to be suitable or right for something, ...",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc. (often passive)"
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere or to talk to someone by telephone in order to let them know that you are ready to start working or that you are in a particular place"
    },
    {
        "question": "report to",
        "options": [
            "to send a letter or document to an organization, ...",
            "if people sit in, they take part in a sit-in",
            "let, grant a service or allow usage for a fee",
            "if you report to someone at work, they are in charge of you and responsible for telling you what to do"
        ],
        "answer": "if you report to someone at work, they are in charge of you and responsible for telling you what to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "reside in",
        "options": [
            "to exist in or belong to someone or something",
            "to reach a result, decision, or solution to a problem",
            "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly",
            "to continue doing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to exist in or belong to someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "rest on",
        "options": [
            "to have to deal with problems or difficulties, especially in order to achieve something",
            "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective",
            "to be based on something",
            "to try to hide a problem or disagreement instead of finding a satisfactory solution to it"
        ],
        "answer": "to be based on something"
    },
    {
        "question": "rest up",
        "options": [
            "to spend a period of time relaxing or sleeping after doing something tiring",
            "if a regular event comes round, it happens again, ...",
            "to return to a place, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a period of time relaxing or sleeping after doing something tiring"
    },
    {
        "question": "rest with",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it",
            "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility",
            "if you sign for a sports club, you join it by signing a contract, ...",
            "to tell someone to move away from a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a decision or responsibility rests with someone, they have the duty or authority to take that decision or responsibility"
    },
    {
        "question": "result in",
        "options": [
            "remove someone secretly of discreetly",
            "to cause something, or to produce something",
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ...",
            "to do something that will cause problems in the future, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to cause something, or to produce something"
    },
    {
        "question": "return to",
        "options": [
            "to go back to an activity after an interruption, ...",
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard",
            "to quickly look through a magazine or book, or to quickly look at several different television programmes",
            "to cause something, or to produce something"
        ],
        "answer": "to go back to an activity after an interruption, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "revel in",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "to enjoy something very much",
            "to practise or learn something in a slow patient way, or to show someone how to do something",
            "to continue trying to achieve something despite opposition or difficulties"
        ],
        "answer": "to enjoy something very much"
    },
    {
        "question": "revolve around",
        "options": [
            "try to keep something",
            "to give someone a lot of drugs or medicine with the result that they cannot behave normally",
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction",
            "to have something as a very important part or purpose, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have something as a very important part or purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ride off",
        "options": [
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ...",
            "go away on a bike, horse, etc",
            "to examine or deal with something such as a problem in a particular way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "go away on a bike, horse, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "ride on",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something for success",
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "to give someone something such as a look, smile, or answer to a question",
            "study something quickly, revise"
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on something for success"
    },
    {
        "question": "ride out",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with someone, ...",
            "to start to sleep, especially during the day and without intending to",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems"
        ],
        "answer": "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "ride up",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ...",
            "if a piece of clothing rides up, it gradually moves upwards on your body",
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "used about things that suddenly arrive or appear, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a piece of clothing rides up, it gradually moves upwards on your body"
    },
    {
        "question": "rifle through",
        "options": [
            "same as rifle",
            "to find and arrest people, ...",
            "to take out, ...",
            "to refuse to listen to someone, or to accept that something might be true or important"
        ],
        "answer": "same as rifle"
    },
    {
        "question": "rig out",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "to write something somewhere, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear"
    },
    {
        "question": "rig up",
        "options": [
            "if you report to someone at work, they are in charge of you and responsible for telling you what to do",
            "move quickly",
            "to make something quickly out of whatever you can find",
            "same as finish, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something quickly out of whatever you can find"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring around",
        "options": [
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "same as ring",
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked"
        ],
        "answer": "same as ring"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring back",
        "options": [
            "same as tap, ...",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth",
            "if you have someone over, they come to your house to visit you or to stay with you",
            "to phone someone again, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to phone someone again, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ring in",
        "options": [
            "same as polish",
            "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "to ring bells to celebrate the beginning of a new year, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to ring bells to celebrate the beginning of a new year, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ring off",
        "options": [
            "to finish a phone call",
            "same as cut down, ...",
            "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist",
            "try to achieve something difficult"
        ],
        "answer": "to finish a phone call"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring out",
        "options": [
            "to produce a loud clear sound",
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce a loud clear sound"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring round",
        "options": [
            "to sit or lie with your body against someone else\u2019s because you want to feel warm, protected, or loved",
            "to have only a few things left to use or deal with, ...",
            "to phone several people or companies etc in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone several people or companies etc in order to arrange something or to get information"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring through",
        "options": [
            "to knock someone over, because you are hurrying somewhere, ...",
            "to phone from one part of a building to another",
            "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ...",
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone from one part of a building to another"
    },
    {
        "question": "ring up",
        "options": [
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to phone someone, ...",
            "to be easy to notice, ...",
            "to stop doing or using one thing and start doing or using something else"
        ],
        "answer": "to phone someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "ring with",
        "options": [
            "to do the same activity for a very long time",
            "to call someone by telephone, ...",
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to call someone by telephone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rinse out",
        "options": [
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ...",
            "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ...",
            "eat something",
            "to use your power or influence to get involved in a situation in which you are not needed or wanted"
        ],
        "answer": "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rip off",
        "options": [
            "same as rifle",
            "to formally state that something is true, especially in a court of law",
            "to be connected to an electricity supply or to another piece of equipment, ...",
            "to steal something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to steal something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rip on",
        "options": [
            "to arrive at work or school, ...",
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to live or stay in a place for a short time, ...",
            "criticise or insult"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise or insult"
    },
    {
        "question": "rise above",
        "options": [
            "to be better than other things of the same type, ...",
            "remove dirt or something dirty",
            "to think about a time or event in the past, ...",
            "to find someone or something by looking for them in a determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to be better than other things of the same type, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rise to",
        "options": [
            "to spend time thinking about someone who you are attracted to rather than doing anything useful",
            "to deal successfully with a problem or situation that is especially difficult, ...",
            "to arrange a group of things into a series",
            "visit for a short time"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal successfully with a problem or situation that is especially difficult, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rise up",
        "options": [
            "to pretend that someone or something is a person or thing that they are not in order to trick someone else",
            "to suddenly notice or think of something",
            "same as rise",
            "keep afloat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as rise"
    },
    {
        "question": "rock up",
        "options": [
            "to ignore or avoid unpleasant facts",
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is less expensive",
            "to put something in a place where no one can find it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly"
    },
    {
        "question": "roll back",
        "options": [
            "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ...",
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll by",
        "options": [
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "pass (time)",
            "be upset",
            "to be the result of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pass (time)"
    },
    {
        "question": "roll down",
        "options": [
            "focus less closely",
            "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ...",
            "to believe that something is true when it is not, ...",
            "used for telling someone to move away from a person or place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll in",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ...",
            "same as let, ...",
            "short circuit",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll off",
        "options": [
            "if two people square up, one pays what they owe so that both people are equal, ...",
            "produce or issue, usually from a machine",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well",
            "if children act up, they behave badly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "produce or issue, usually from a machine"
    },
    {
        "question": "roll on",
        "options": [
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "to become thinner by losing weight, ...",
            "to start a new activity, ...",
            "when something continues to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "when something continues to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "roll on!",
        "options": [
            "join a teleconference",
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future",
            "to decide not to take part in something or to stop taking part in it",
            "spend time doing little things for pleasure"
        ],
        "answer": "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future"
    },
    {
        "question": "roll out",
        "options": [
            "be suitable, have the necessary qualities",
            "to prevent people from entering a place, using a road etc",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other"
        ],
        "answer": "same as roll, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll over",
        "options": [
            "form a pair with someone",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to meet someone or to find something without planning to",
            "abuse someone because you're angry"
        ],
        "answer": "same as roll, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll up",
        "options": [
            "to hunt another creature in order to eat it, ...",
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something",
            "same as roll, ...",
            "to make someone angry, or to argue with them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as roll, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "roll up!",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to take the place of someone temporarily",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "same as roll, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as roll, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "romp ahead",
        "options": [
            "if you screw up your eyes, you close them tightly, ...",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ...",
            "to start to win or increase quickly and easily",
            "to say the words that you are reading so that people can hear them"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to win or increase quickly and easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "romp in",
        "options": [
            "win easily",
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly",
            "to make a price or amount rise to a higher level, ...",
            "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "win easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "romp through",
        "options": [
            "to do something quickly and easily",
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with",
            "stop working or functioning, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something quickly and easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "room in",
        "options": [
            "if a person or animal is cooped up in a place, they have to stay there without being able to move around much",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone",
            "to try to take hold of something, ...",
            "to keep a mother and baby together after the birth"
        ],
        "answer": "to keep a mother and baby together after the birth"
    },
    {
        "question": "root about",
        "options": [
            "to make people understand something",
            "look in a place to try to find something",
            "to start to do something in a different way, ...",
            "same as split, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "look in a place to try to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "root around",
        "options": [
            "to search a person or a place very carefully, ...",
            "look in a place to try to find something",
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it",
            "if something such as a sound or smell issues from a place, it comes out from there"
        ],
        "answer": "look in a place to try to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "root for",
        "options": [
            "to support someone in a game, competition etc",
            "to have another use or job as something",
            "same as post",
            "to teach someone something by repeating it many times"
        ],
        "answer": "to support someone in a game, competition etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "root out",
        "options": [
            "to make strong steady progress, ...",
            "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it",
            "to bring someone into a team or group of people in order to help them do something",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "root up",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots",
            "to go somewhere where no one can find you",
            "to be easy to see or notice because of being different, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots"
    },
    {
        "question": "rope in",
        "options": [
            "to persuade someone to do something that they do not really want to do",
            "talk until you have nothing left to say",
            "to leave a place, usually suddenly",
            "to show that something is possible"
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to do something that they do not really want to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "rope into",
        "options": [
            "to pay money into a bank",
            "try to keep something",
            "when an aircraft or space vehicle lifts off, it goes up from the ground into the air",
            "get someone to help or become involved, usually when they don't want to"
        ],
        "answer": "get someone to help or become involved, usually when they don't want to"
    },
    {
        "question": "rope off",
        "options": [
            "to shoot someone and kill them or injure them badly, especially someone who is not guilty of anything, or who is not carrying a gun",
            "to enclose an area using ropes, usually because of danger",
            "if you lay a ship to, or if it lays to, it stops",
            "to succeed in keeping a job, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to enclose an area using ropes, usually because of danger"
    },
    {
        "question": "rope up",
        "options": [
            "to tie people together with ropes, especially people who are climbing",
            "to continue to talk for a long time",
            "to make information publicly known, ...",
            "persuade someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to tie people together with ropes, especially people who are climbing"
    },
    {
        "question": "rough up",
        "options": [
            "to physically attack someone",
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something",
            "to babysit, ...",
            "to become quieter or weaker and finally stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to physically attack someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "round down",
        "options": [
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "to sit down carelessly but gently",
            "to reduce a number to the nearest whole number, or the nearest number ending in zero",
            "avoid doing something in a way other people don't like"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce a number to the nearest whole number, or the nearest number ending in zero"
    },
    {
        "question": "round off",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone who is trying to attack you, ...",
            "to not become involved with something",
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "to end something in a satisfactory way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to end something in a satisfactory way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "round on",
        "options": [
            "to say publicly that you oppose someone or something",
            "hold a grudge",
            "to react angrily towards someone",
            "make electrical connections"
        ],
        "answer": "to react angrily towards someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "round out",
        "options": [
            "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature",
            "to discuss ideas or plans in an informal way",
            "to attack someone physically or with cruel words because you are angry with them",
            "turn around quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature"
    },
    {
        "question": "round up",
        "options": [
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "to find and arrest people, ...",
            "same as top up, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time relaxing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to find and arrest people, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "row back",
        "options": [
            "to slightly change something that you previously said, or to slightly change your opinion on an issue",
            "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ...",
            "to arrive or appear somewhere",
            "a way of saying \u2018lie down\u2019 that many people think is incorrect, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to slightly change something that you previously said, or to slightly change your opinion on an issue"
    },
    {
        "question": "rub along",
        "options": [
            "to try to discover in a careful or indirect way what a situation is like or what someone\u2019s attitude is",
            "to tick off something",
            "to live or work with someone in a friendly way",
            "if words or pictures jump off the page, they are the first thing that you notice"
        ],
        "answer": "to live or work with someone in a friendly way"
    },
    {
        "question": "rub down",
        "options": [
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "to rub a surface to make it smooth or dry, ...",
            "to murder someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to rub a surface to make it smooth or dry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rub in",
        "options": [
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to tell someone something, ...",
            "to examine or search something very carefully, ...",
            "relax, do nothing"
        ],
        "answer": "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rub it in",
        "options": [
            "to make someone heavy and unable to move easily, ...",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination"
        ],
        "answer": "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rub off",
        "options": [
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to leave a place suddenly, ...",
            "to do something immediately, and often with enthusiasm, as soon as you have the chance to do it",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too"
        ],
        "answer": "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too"
    },
    {
        "question": "rub off on",
        "options": [
            "become nervous, tense or unable to relax",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too",
            "to spend time in a place without any particular purpose",
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you"
        ],
        "answer": "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too"
    },
    {
        "question": "rub out",
        "options": [
            "to quickly jump or dive into water, ...",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to seem to prove that something exists or is true"
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rub up against",
        "options": [
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone"
        ],
        "answer": "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way"
    },
    {
        "question": "rub up on",
        "options": [
            "to remove something by burning it, ...",
            "revise",
            "to gradually become less involved in something, ...",
            "to start driving in a lower gear"
        ],
        "answer": "revise"
    },
    {
        "question": "ruck up",
        "options": [
            "to make something larger in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to not do something immediately because you are not confident or you do not feel certain about it",
            "to invest a lot of money in something in order to improve it or make it successful, ...",
            "if a piece of cloth or clothing rucks up, or if you ruck it up, it forms untidy folds"
        ],
        "answer": "if a piece of cloth or clothing rucks up, or if you ruck it up, it forms untidy folds"
    },
    {
        "question": "rule in",
        "options": [
            "arrive",
            "persuade someone to do something",
            "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen",
            "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide that something is a possibility or that it will definitely happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "rule out",
        "options": [
            "to stop considering something as a possibility",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "pay attention after not doing so",
            "to discover something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop considering something as a possibility"
    },
    {
        "question": "rule out of",
        "options": [
            "to oppose someone or something, especially in a brave or determined way, ...",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ...",
            "to make it impossible for a player to take part in a game or competition",
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere"
        ],
        "answer": "to make it impossible for a player to take part in a game or competition"
    },
    {
        "question": "rumble on",
        "options": [
            "to not use the usual way of doing something",
            "to give something back to someone, ...",
            "become involved, often against one\ufffds will",
            "to continue to cause trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to cause trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "run across",
        "options": [
            "look in different places for something",
            "to find something or to meet someone by chance",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ...",
            "to deal with official or legal business more quickly than usual"
        ],
        "answer": "to find something or to meet someone by chance"
    },
    {
        "question": "run after",
        "options": [
            "to develop, ...",
            "to chase someone or something, ...",
            "to become sober after being drunk, ...",
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": "to chase someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run against",
        "options": [
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing, ...",
            "same as post",
            "to move smoothly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move smoothly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run along",
        "options": [
            "leave a place angrily",
            "talk too much",
            "to expect something to happen",
            "used for telling children to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "used for telling children to go away"
    },
    {
        "question": "run around",
        "options": [
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "to be very busy doing a lot of different things",
            "to steal something or to take it without permission, ...",
            "to cause a government or politician to lose power, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be very busy doing a lot of different things"
    },
    {
        "question": "run around after",
        "options": [
            "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly",
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping",
            "to wait, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things"
    },
    {
        "question": "run around with",
        "options": [
            "to search for someone or something, ...",
            "to try to start a conversation with someone because you are sexually attracted to them",
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ...",
            "to spend a lot of time with someone, especially someone who other people do not approve of"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of time with someone, especially someone who other people do not approve of"
    },
    {
        "question": "run away",
        "options": [
            "to try to avoid dealing with a difficult or unpleasant situation, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ...",
            "to get information on a particular subject by reading a lot about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to avoid dealing with a difficult or unpleasant situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run away with",
        "options": [
            "to believe that something is true when it is not, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to make someone feel so worried or frightened that they do something",
            "to be the reason why something exists or happens, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to believe that something is true when it is not, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run by",
        "options": [
            "come to nothing, produce no results",
            "to become friends with someone, ...",
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "used for asking someone to repeat what they have just said, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used for asking someone to repeat what they have just said, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run down",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to waste time or money on things that are not necessary or important",
            "to quickly read everything on a list, ...",
            "behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly read everything on a list, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run for",
        "options": [
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "turn around quickly, ...",
            "to move smoothly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move smoothly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run in",
        "options": [
            "same as go around, ...",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station.",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad"
        ],
        "answer": "to find a criminal and take them to a police station."
    },
    {
        "question": "run into",
        "options": [
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "to reach a particular amount, ...",
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reach a particular amount, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run off",
        "options": [
            "to talk too much, ...",
            "to remove the dirt from something, especially from an upright surface",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to want something very much, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to talk too much, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run off with",
        "options": [
            "to steal something or to take it without permission, ...",
            "to catch fish in a particular area of water, ...",
            "same as hang",
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to steal something or to take it without permission, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run on",
        "options": [
            "if something boring or unpleasant grinds on, it continues happening for a long period of time",
            "same as bundle, ...",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to continue for longer than expected or planned, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue for longer than expected or planned, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run out",
        "options": [
            "if two people who ended their sexual or romantic relationship get back together, they start having a relationship with each other again",
            "to use all of something and not have any left, ...",
            "to suddenly start doing something, ...",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use all of something and not have any left, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run out of",
        "options": [
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ...",
            "to give someone a lot of drugs or medicine with the result that they cannot behave normally",
            "to use all of something and not have any left, ...",
            "to remain under water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use all of something and not have any left, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run out on",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly leave your wife, husband, or partner",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to avoid going to a place",
            "to go away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly leave your wife, husband, or partner"
    },
    {
        "question": "run over",
        "options": [
            "to relax and stop making the effort to do something",
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ...",
            "to continue for longer than planned, ...",
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue for longer than planned, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run through",
        "options": [
            "to push a sword through someone\u2019s body, ...",
            "put something in a liquid for a short time",
            "re-invest money you have made into a business",
            "introduce a new product; launch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to push a sword through someone\u2019s body, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run to",
        "options": [
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ...",
            "pass or succeed easily",
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "think of someone or something in a particular way"
        ],
        "answer": "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run up",
        "options": [
            "to raise a flag to the top of a pole, ...",
            "to move so that there is space for someone else",
            "same as flip",
            "to leave with something that belongs to someone else, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to raise a flag to the top of a pole, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "run up against",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone with a gun, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them",
            "to support an idea, project etc, or help someone in what they are trying to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them"
    },
    {
        "question": "run up on",
        "options": [
            "to start doing something as a habit, ...",
            "to make someone or something disappear very quickly and easily",
            "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose",
            "approach someone without their knowing"
        ],
        "answer": "approach someone without their knowing"
    },
    {
        "question": "run with",
        "options": [
            "be as good as something",
            "to go or travel to different places, ...",
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "to start doing something with energy and enthusiasm"
        ],
        "answer": "to move smoothly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rush around",
        "options": [
            "improve your knowledge quickly",
            "to have a particular name, ...",
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to stop doing something that is annoying someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "rush away",
        "options": [
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "same as lock away, ...",
            "same as hang, ...",
            "to compare one thing with another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place in a hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "rush in",
        "options": [
            "spend time with",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "hold tight"
        ],
        "answer": "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "rush into",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in large numbers or amounts, ...",
            "to do something without first thinking carefully about it",
            "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection",
            "to make something flat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something without first thinking carefully about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "rush off",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "win easily",
            "depart in a hurry",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair"
        ],
        "answer": "depart in a hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "rush out",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as an edge or corner straight",
            "to kill yourself, ...",
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "rush through",
        "options": [
            "to accelerate rapidly in a vehicle, ...",
            "to use something in an enthusiastic way in order to gain an advantage",
            "to deal with official or legal business more quickly than usual",
            "same as spit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with official or legal business more quickly than usual"
    },
    {
        "question": "rustle up",
        "options": [
            "to take a particular amount of something from a larger amount",
            "if a quality or feature tells against someone, it makes them less likely to succeed in achieving something",
            "to quickly produce something such as a meal using whatever is available",
            "to make someone compete or fight against someone or something else, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly produce something such as a meal using whatever is available"
    },
    {
        "question": "sack out",
        "options": [
            "to go to sleep",
            "to reduce an amount, ...",
            "leave suddenly",
            "to understand, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go to sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "saddle up",
        "options": [
            "to put a saddle on a horse",
            "to have sex with someone, ...",
            "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home",
            "if the sea casts something up, the sea carries it somewhere and leaves it there"
        ],
        "answer": "to put a saddle on a horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "saddle with",
        "options": [
            "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with",
            "to suddenly attack someone violently, ...",
            "to have something as a final result, ...",
            "to formally offer an idea or proposal to someone for them to consider or accept"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone something that is difficult to deal with"
    },
    {
        "question": "sag off",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation",
            "not go to school or work, or leave early when you shouldn't",
            "to telephone someone, ...",
            "to develop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "not go to school or work, or leave early when you shouldn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "sail into",
        "options": [
            "criticise angrily",
            "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ...",
            "to be connected to an electricity supply or to another piece of equipment, ...",
            "come to understand"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "sail through",
        "options": [
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something",
            "to gradually start to talk or write about a particular subject in a conversation or piece of writing, especially because it is embarrassing",
            "to do something, or to deal with something, very easily",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something, or to deal with something, very easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "sally forth",
        "options": [
            "if a situation calms down, there is less activity and people are less busy, ...",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to criticize someone angrily for doing something wrong",
            "to start to make progress faster than someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "sally out",
        "options": [
            "same as haul, ...",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "salt away",
        "options": [
            "same as put about",
            "to save money for the future, often hiding it illegally",
            "to try to avoid dealing with a difficult or unpleasant situation, ...",
            "pay attention after not doing so"
        ],
        "answer": "to save money for the future, often hiding it illegally"
    },
    {
        "question": "save on",
        "options": [
            "to start a new activity, ...",
            "to avoid using something, or to use less of it, ...",
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car",
            "to operate steadily but not very well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid using something, or to use less of it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "save up",
        "options": [
            "to achieve a particular level or number, ...",
            "if you sign with a sports club, you join it by signing a contract",
            "same as save",
            "if a quality that someone has rubs off, it starts to affect another person so that they start to have that quality too"
        ],
        "answer": "same as save"
    },
    {
        "question": "savour of",
        "options": [
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to seem to have a small amount of an unpleasant quality",
            "to give something back to someone, ...",
            "turn quickly and face in the opposite direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to seem to have a small amount of an unpleasant quality"
    },
    {
        "question": "saw at",
        "options": [
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad",
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "to move a knife or other object backwards and forwards several times across something, especially in order to cut it"
        ],
        "answer": "to move a knife or other object backwards and forwards several times across something, especially in order to cut it"
    },
    {
        "question": "saw down",
        "options": [
            "be less successful",
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ...",
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more",
            "to cut through something such as a tree with a saw so that it falls to the ground"
        ],
        "answer": "to cut through something such as a tree with a saw so that it falls to the ground"
    },
    {
        "question": "saw off",
        "options": [
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball",
            "to remove something by cutting through it with a saw or a knife",
            "same as stack, ...",
            "to not choose someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something by cutting through it with a saw or a knife"
    },
    {
        "question": "saw up",
        "options": [
            "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife",
            "leave the top deck of a ship",
            "to attack someone or something",
            "same as gulp"
        ],
        "answer": "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife"
    },
    {
        "question": "scale back",
        "options": [
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "intend, plan"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "scale down",
        "options": [
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair",
            "mess up, ruin",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "scale up",
        "options": [
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug",
            "to make something larger in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to leave quickly, especially after doing something wrong",
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something larger in size, amount etc than it used to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "scar over",
        "options": [
            "to make something fairer or more equal",
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "if an injury scars over, it forms a scar as it becomes better",
            "to enjoy yourself in a social situation, often by spending a lot of money, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if an injury scars over, it forms a scar as it becomes better"
    },
    {
        "question": "scare away",
        "options": [
            "to exist in or belong to someone or something",
            "to fix something to a wall with a nail or nails, ...",
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "same as invite"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "scare into",
        "options": [
            "if something hangs together, the different parts of it combine well so that it seems well planned and organized",
            "get something by chance",
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "to make someone feel so worried or frightened that they do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel so worried or frightened that they do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "scare off",
        "options": [
            "be unacceptable",
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people",
            "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "scare up",
        "options": [
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ...",
            "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it",
            "same as lap, ...",
            "to make something using the few things that are available"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something using the few things that are available"
    },
    {
        "question": "scoop up",
        "options": [
            "to stop something from happening",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health",
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "scoot over",
        "options": [
            "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket",
            "if someone sitting down scoots over, they move to a different position, for example to make space for someone else to sit down",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to join a conversation or activity without being asked to"
        ],
        "answer": "if someone sitting down scoots over, they move to a different position, for example to make space for someone else to sit down"
    },
    {
        "question": "score off",
        "options": [
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to do something or move somewhere more quickly, ...",
            "to gain an advantage over someone",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something"
        ],
        "answer": "to gain an advantage over someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "score out",
        "options": [
            "wipe, remove with a brush, ...",
            "to pull very strongly at something",
            "to draw a line through written words",
            "if a computer program falls over, it stops working, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to draw a line through written words"
    },
    {
        "question": "scout about",
        "options": [
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business",
            "get the energy or courage to do something",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to treat someone badly and to make them do what you want without respect for their feelings"
        ],
        "answer": "look in different places for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "scout around",
        "options": [
            "to be unwilling to do or accept something",
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ...",
            "look in different places for something"
        ],
        "answer": "look in different places for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "scout out",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something",
            "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death",
            "work hard doing something",
            "to move smoothly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "scout round",
        "options": [
            "to be very happy about something, ...",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "to keep something"
        ],
        "answer": "look in different places for something"
    },
    {
        "question": "scout up",
        "options": [
            "try to find someone for a task or requirement",
            "same as stop",
            "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from",
            "to succeed after great difficulty"
        ],
        "answer": "try to find someone for a task or requirement"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape along",
        "options": [
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them",
            "manage with little money",
            "to start driving in a lower gear",
            "to not keep a secret, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "manage with little money"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape back",
        "options": [
            "to tie your hair tightly so that it does not touch your face",
            "if an injury heals up, the skin or bone grows back together and becomes healthy again",
            "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ...",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to tie your hair tightly so that it does not touch your face"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape by",
        "options": [
            "to have enough money to pay for the things that you really need in order to live, but no more",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "same as buy, ...",
            "to turn and face in the opposite direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to have enough money to pay for the things that you really need in order to live, but no more"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape in",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing",
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "same as roll, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape into",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly say or shout something, ...",
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points",
            "to look at and speak words that you wrote earlier, usually so that someone can check that what you have written is correct"
        ],
        "answer": "to achieve a position by a very small number of votes or points"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape through",
        "options": [
            "to improve, ...",
            "to be part of a particular group, or to include someone or something among a particular group",
            "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way",
            "to decide not to do something you agreed to do"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in doing something, but not in a very impressive way"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape together",
        "options": [
            "if time creeps by, it passes very slowly",
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to cover an area of ground with grass",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrape up",
        "options": [
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ...",
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "to be shocked by something"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
    },
    {
        "question": "scratch around for",
        "options": [
            "if two or more people drift apart, their relationship gradually ends",
            "to try to find something by looking everywhere, even in places that you would prefer not to look in",
            "to suddenly have an idea, ...",
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find something by looking everywhere, even in places that you would prefer not to look in"
    },
    {
        "question": "scratch out",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to accept or to use something any longer",
            "same as heat, ...",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to remove a word from a sentence or something from a list by drawing a line through it"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a word from a sentence or something from a list by drawing a line through it"
    },
    {
        "question": "screen off",
        "options": [
            "behave without courage or conviction",
            "to invent a story, excuse, or plan",
            "to start a game of hockey by hitting another player\u2019s stick and then the ground before trying to hit the ball",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private"
    },
    {
        "question": "screen out",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to give something back to someone, ...",
            "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ...",
            "approach quietly or secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "screw around",
        "options": [
            "to phone several people or companies etc in order to arrange something or to get information",
            "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit",
            "do a lot to try to help or please someone",
            "to waste time in silly or useless activities, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to waste time in silly or useless activities, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "screw over",
        "options": [
            "to include someone in your plans",
            "to deliberately put someone in an unfavorable situation",
            "to be important, or to have influence, ...",
            "to try to persuade someone to do something by explaining why you think it is sensible"
        ],
        "answer": "to deliberately put someone in an unfavorable situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "screw up",
        "options": [
            "to arrive somewhere, especially unexpectedly",
            "if you screw up your eyes, you close them tightly, ...",
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "to avoid going to a place"
        ],
        "answer": "if you screw up your eyes, you close them tightly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "scrub out",
        "options": [
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ...",
            "pursue, be aware of someone's true nature",
            "to clean the inside of something thoroughly",
            "to make two things fit or match each other, or to fit or match in this way"
        ],
        "answer": "to clean the inside of something thoroughly"
    },
    {
        "question": "scrub up",
        "options": [
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ...",
            "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force",
            "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening"
        ],
        "answer": "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "scuzz up",
        "options": [
            "be elsewhere; on holiday, etc.",
            "to make people come together to form a group",
            "confuse, deceive",
            "spiil, ruin, contaminate"
        ],
        "answer": "spiil, ruin, contaminate"
    },
    {
        "question": "seal in",
        "options": [
            "same as spit, ...",
            "have food delivered",
            "to prevent the flavour, smell, or juice of a food from getting out",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child"
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent the flavour, smell, or juice of a food from getting out"
    },
    {
        "question": "seal off",
        "options": [
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ...",
            "like someone from the first time you meet them",
            "to prevent people from entering an area or a building",
            "same as slough, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent people from entering an area or a building"
    },
    {
        "question": "seal up",
        "options": [
            "progress, ...",
            "withdraw from company",
            "same as seal",
            "same as mop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "search out",
        "options": [
            "same as pull, ...",
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to escape from a person, place, or situation, ...",
            "to work hard in order to find something"
        ],
        "answer": "to work hard in order to find something"
    },
    {
        "question": "section off",
        "options": [
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas",
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word",
            "to separate something into different parts or areas",
            "approach quietly or secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate something into different parts or areas"
    },
    {
        "question": "see about",
        "options": [
            "to make someone do or experience something difficult or unpleasant, ...",
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "to deal with or organize something, ...",
            "pay attention after not doing so"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with or organize something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see around",
        "options": [
            "to examine a place by walking around it, ...",
            "to enjoy a particular thing or activity, ...",
            "to suddenly stop talking or explaining something, because you are embarrassed, unhappy, or want to keep a secret",
            "same as heap"
        ],
        "answer": "to examine a place by walking around it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see in",
        "options": [
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended",
            "to live or work with someone in a friendly way",
            "to recognize a particular quality in someone or something, ...",
            "do something slowly, with difficulty, unwillingly or considerable effort"
        ],
        "answer": "to recognize a particular quality in someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see into",
        "options": [
            "accompany someone into an office",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off your clothes, ...",
            "to hang a piece of clothing on something, ...",
            "to arrive at home or at work, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "accompany someone into an office"
    },
    {
        "question": "see off",
        "options": [
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary",
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to make someone go away or leave a place, especially by chasing them, ...",
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone go away or leave a place, especially by chasing them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see out",
        "options": [
            "to leave a job or position, especially an important one, ...",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move",
            "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them",
            "to celebrate the end of a year, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to celebrate the end of a year, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see over",
        "options": [
            "to listen to a radio programme, ...",
            "to walk around a place or building and look at what is there",
            "if you are loaded down with a lot of heavy things, you are carrying them, ...",
            "same as lead to"
        ],
        "answer": "to walk around a place or building and look at what is there"
    },
    {
        "question": "see through",
        "options": [
            "to write down information or a statement, ...",
            "to make a person or animal so afraid that they run away, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "to recognize that something is not true and not be tricked by it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to recognize that something is not true and not be tricked by it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "see to",
        "options": [
            "to spend time relaxing or doing nothing when you should be doing something",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to deal with or take responsibility for someone or something",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with or take responsibility for someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "seek out",
        "options": [
            "same as cut, ...",
            "to whistle to show that you think someone is sexually attractive",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "to find someone or something by looking for them in a determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to find someone or something by looking for them in a determined way"
    },
    {
        "question": "seep away",
        "options": [
            "to make a price or amount fall to a lower level",
            "same as get along, ...",
            "to gradually become weaker or to disappear",
            "if a missile or a vehicle carrying missiles locks onto something, it finds out its position and prepares to destroy it"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually become weaker or to disappear"
    },
    {
        "question": "seize on",
        "options": [
            "to use something in an enthusiastic way in order to gain an advantage",
            "to make someone or something more attractive or interesting, especially in a way that is intended to impress people but is not useful or necessary",
            "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition",
            "same as shade"
        ],
        "answer": "to use something in an enthusiastic way in order to gain an advantage"
    },
    {
        "question": "seize up",
        "options": [
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "to prevent something that is dangerous or unsuitable from coming in, ...",
            "to spend time with someone",
            "to suddenly stop moving or working properly"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly stop moving or working properly"
    },
    {
        "question": "sell off",
        "options": [
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "to sell something quickly and for a low price, usually because you need money",
            "persuade or pressure to accept something",
            "to make a place clean and tidy, especially after someone else has used it"
        ],
        "answer": "to sell something quickly and for a low price, usually because you need money"
    },
    {
        "question": "sell on",
        "options": [
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them",
            "to sell something after buying it from someone else",
            "to look at someone for so long that they have to look away"
        ],
        "answer": "to sell something after buying it from someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "sell out",
        "options": [
            "to start working hard, especially when you should have done this earlier",
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to end a letter, ...",
            "used about goods, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "used about goods, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sell up",
        "options": [
            "to write something again exactly as it has been written",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to behave badly, or to do things that other people do not approve of",
            "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different"
        ],
        "answer": "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different"
    },
    {
        "question": "send away",
        "options": [
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to order someone to leave a place",
            "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ...",
            "to be full of a strong emotion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to order someone to leave a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "send away for",
        "options": [
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document",
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want",
            "to tell someone something that is unpleasant or surprising, ...",
            "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "send back",
        "options": [
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "surrender to the police or authorities",
            "to return something that is not satisfactory",
            "to use something in an enthusiastic way in order to gain an advantage"
        ],
        "answer": "to return something that is not satisfactory"
    },
    {
        "question": "send down",
        "options": [
            "to start to sleep",
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "to destroy something completely by violently breaking it into many pieces",
            "to send someone to prison, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone to prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "send for",
        "options": [
            "to reach a particular number or amount",
            "to ask for someone to come to you, ...",
            "to spread objects or parts out, often in the shape of a semi-circle, ...",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to ask for someone to come to you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "send in",
        "options": [
            "to be suitable or right for something, ...",
            "to feel happy and excited about something that is going to happen",
            "to consider all the important facts in a situation before deciding or doing something",
            "to send a letter or document to an organization, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to send a letter or document to an organization, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "send off",
        "options": [
            "consider, regard",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "to remove someone from a position on something such as a committee by voting"
        ],
        "answer": "to post something to someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "send off for",
        "options": [
            "order something by post",
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation",
            "eat something",
            "to do something very badly and make a lot of mistakes"
        ],
        "answer": "order something by post"
    },
    {
        "question": "send out",
        "options": [
            "same as go around, ...",
            "waste time",
            "to send someone to a place for a particular purpose, ...",
            "sell something in an auction"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone to a place for a particular purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "send out for",
        "options": [
            "same as light, ...",
            "to behave in a stupid way, ...",
            "to order something and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a very boring way"
        ],
        "answer": "to order something and ask for it to be delivered to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "send up",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to prison, ...",
            "to tie your hair tightly so that it does not touch your face",
            "to make a lot of noise as you move around in a place",
            "favour one viewpoint, bias"
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone to prison, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "separate out",
        "options": [
            "to take off all your clothes, ...",
            "same as separate",
            "to put your foot very suddenly and hard on the brake of a vehicle because you want to stop quickly",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as separate"
    },
    {
        "question": "serve out",
        "options": [
            "try to find something",
            "to spend time experiencing and enjoying the mood or feeling in a place, ...",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard"
        ],
        "answer": "same as serve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "serve up",
        "options": [
            "to want something very much, ...",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands"
        ],
        "answer": "same as serve, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set about",
        "options": [
            "to begin doing something, especially in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to not live at the place where you work or study, ...",
            "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before",
            "try to maintain beliefs, hopes, etc."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin doing something, especially in a determined or enthusiastic way"
    },
    {
        "question": "set against",
        "options": [
            "become rigid, ...",
            "to start to employ someone, ...",
            "change tv channels quickly",
            "to compare one thing with another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to compare one thing with another, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set apart",
        "options": [
            "accept or get money without doing any work",
            "to make someone or something different and special, ...",
            "to gradually start to talk or write about a particular subject in a conversation or piece of writing, especially because it is embarrassing",
            "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone or something different and special, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set aside",
        "options": [
            "to talk or behave very confidently in order to make someone who you are competing against feel nervous and less likely to succeed",
            "to make someone feel very tired",
            "used for asking what has happened to someone or something, because you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to them, because you are worried about them",
            "to officially state that a particular legal decision will no longer be followed, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to officially state that a particular legal decision will no longer be followed, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set back",
        "options": [
            "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone",
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ...",
            "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death"
        ],
        "answer": "to delay the progress of someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set down",
        "options": [
            "to consider something in a particular way, ...",
            "to continue encouraging and persuading someone to do something",
            "to remove something from a surface using steam",
            "to move so that you are behind someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to consider something in a particular way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set forth",
        "options": [
            "invest in something",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ...",
            "to start a journey, especially one that is long or difficult, ...",
            "to do something quickly and easily"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a journey, especially one that is long or difficult, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set in",
        "options": [
            "to use or do something else after other things have failed",
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you",
            "if something unpleasant sets in, it starts to happen and have an effect, and is not likely to stop for a long time",
            "finally manage to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "if something unpleasant sets in, it starts to happen and have an effect, and is not likely to stop for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "set off",
        "options": [
            "to invite somebody into your house",
            "same as tease, ...",
            "to make something explode, ...",
            "same as flatten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something explode, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set off against",
        "options": [
            "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly",
            "to shout something",
            "to become involved in something by accident",
            "same as set against, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as set against, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set on",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone or something, ...",
            "come to understand",
            "same as wrap, ...",
            "to drink all of something, especially quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set out",
        "options": [
            "to start a journey, ...",
            "same as tidy, ...",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a room with a partition",
            "to produce a particular reaction"
        ],
        "answer": "to start a journey, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set to",
        "options": [
            "visit a lot of different places for pleasure",
            "same as mark out, ...",
            "to start doing something in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "share accommodation with a number of people because of the high rent"
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something in a determined or enthusiastic way"
    },
    {
        "question": "set up",
        "options": [
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "increase commitment to something, especially when this is risky",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "to prepare someone for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prepare someone for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "set upon",
        "options": [
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "to attack someone or something",
            "to eat an extremely large amount of food",
            "become involved in something despite opposition to your involvement"
        ],
        "answer": "to attack someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "settle down",
        "options": [
            "same as settle, ...",
            "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you",
            "to leave, ...",
            "to do something quickly, easily, and without much effort, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as settle, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "settle for",
        "options": [
            "to accept someone or something that is not exactly what you wanted because you cannot have what you wanted",
            "same as double",
            "to search very hard for something, ...",
            "to count and check all the money that a shop has received in a day"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept someone or something that is not exactly what you wanted because you cannot have what you wanted"
    },
    {
        "question": "settle in",
        "options": [
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to arrive, especially late or in an unusual way",
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "settle into",
        "options": [
            "same as heap",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ...",
            "to use or finish something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "settle on",
        "options": [
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money",
            "to break a door or gate in order to get through it",
            "to give someone money or property in a legal and official way, ...",
            "if a rate or an amount tops out, it reaches its highest level"
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone money or property in a legal and official way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "settle up",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to fix a picture to a wall, ...",
            "to come from a particular place, family, or situation, ...",
            "to agree how much each person or group should pay, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree how much each person or group should pay, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sew up",
        "options": [
            "to pull very strongly at something",
            "to wait, ...",
            "same as border, ...",
            "to repair something such as a hole in a piece of cloth by sewing it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to repair something such as a hole in a piece of cloth by sewing it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sex up",
        "options": [
            "avoid doing something because you lack confidence",
            "to consider the good and bad aspects of something in order to reach a decision about it",
            "study something quickly, revise",
            "to change something in order to make it seem more interesting, exciting, or important"
        ],
        "answer": "to change something in order to make it seem more interesting, exciting, or important"
    },
    {
        "question": "shack up",
        "options": [
            "look in a place to try to find something",
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "to live or stay in a place for a short time, ...",
            "approach quietly or secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "to live or stay in a place for a short time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shade in",
        "options": [
            "same as shade",
            "to give something back to someone, ...",
            "go into the pits (car racing)",
            "criticise"
        ],
        "answer": "same as shade"
    },
    {
        "question": "shade into",
        "options": [
            "if one thing shades into another thing, it is difficult to know where one ends and the other begins",
            "an imperative used to tell someone to go faster, especially when driving",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "to drink alcoholic drinks quickly, one after another"
        ],
        "answer": "if one thing shades into another thing, it is difficult to know where one ends and the other begins"
    },
    {
        "question": "shake down",
        "options": [
            "to search a person or a place very carefully, ...",
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "to do something, especially something that you should not do",
            "to take an opportunity that is offered to you in a very enthusiastic way"
        ],
        "answer": "to search a person or a place very carefully, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shake off",
        "options": [
            "waste (money, time, resources, etc)",
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ...",
            "to belong to a particular group or class, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shake out",
        "options": [
            "same as stow, ...",
            "same as press, ...",
            "to make something seem less good, attractive, or important, ...",
            "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off"
        ],
        "answer": "to shake a cloth, sheet, piece of clothing etc so that dust and dirt fall off"
    },
    {
        "question": "shake up",
        "options": [
            "same as heap",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "fight or argue",
            "to upset or frighten someone by shocking or surprising them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to upset or frighten someone by shocking or surprising them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shame into",
        "options": [
            "to stop something from having any effect",
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want",
            "to find out whether information is accurate or useful by comparing it with other information",
            "waste time"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want"
    },
    {
        "question": "shape up",
        "options": [
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk",
            "same as gobble",
            "to have something as the final part, ...",
            "to develop, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to develop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "share in",
        "options": [
            "to search for something among a lot of other things, ...",
            "be assertive and ready to initiate action. (related to the meaning 'attack')",
            "have a part in a project, activity, etc",
            "change tv channels quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "have a part in a project, activity, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "share out",
        "options": [
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to take the place of someone temporarily",
            "same as share"
        ],
        "answer": "same as share"
    },
    {
        "question": "shave off",
        "options": [
            "turn around quickly, ...",
            "to say something loudly and quickly",
            "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ...",
            "to reduce an amount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce an amount, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shell out",
        "options": [
            "to start a journey by ship, ...",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to spend a lot of money on something",
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a lot of money on something"
    },
    {
        "question": "shine through",
        "options": [
            "if a good feeling or quality shines through, it is very noticeable",
            "to go away, ...",
            "to make something larger in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to invite someone to your house, for example for a meal"
        ],
        "answer": "if a good feeling or quality shines through, it is very noticeable"
    },
    {
        "question": "ship off",
        "options": [
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "to send someone somewhere, usually when they do not want to go",
            "to wipe dust or dirt off the surface of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to send someone somewhere, usually when they do not want to go"
    },
    {
        "question": "ship out",
        "options": [
            "to spoil something or do something badly",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to join with other people in doing a job, ...",
            "to think about something carefully or discuss it carefully with other people before making a decision about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shit on",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place or an organization",
            "to treat someone in an extremely unfair way",
            "to be nice to someone so that they will help or support you",
            "to make a careless mistake"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone in an extremely unfair way"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot away",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past",
            "leave somewhere quickly",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "to be completely certain of something"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot back",
        "options": [
            "to play in a very lively or rough way",
            "if a market or price bounces back, it rises again after falling, ...",
            "to make something fall down and break into pieces by hitting it very hard",
            "return quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "return quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot down",
        "options": [
            "look for something hurriedly",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "to kill someone with a gun, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone with a gun, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot for",
        "options": [
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "used for talking about things that you did a lot, or things that you had a lot of, when you were a child",
            "to criticize someone regularly or for a long time",
            "to try to achieve a particular thing"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to achieve a particular thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot off",
        "options": [
            "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way",
            "to leave a place quickly or suddenly",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job, ...",
            "to divide something among people so that each one gets a small amount"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place quickly or suddenly"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot out",
        "options": [
            "go out for a short time",
            "to make people understand something",
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "if two people stay together, they continue to live together or to have a relationship with each other"
        ],
        "answer": "go out for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot through",
        "options": [
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "to go to a place for only a short period of time before continuing a journey",
            "to rub a surface to make it smooth or dry, ...",
            "to leave a place, usually suddenly"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, usually suddenly"
    },
    {
        "question": "shoot up",
        "options": [
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something",
            "get into trouble",
            "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly",
            "to grow taller very quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to grow taller very quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shop around",
        "options": [
            "to go to several shops before you decide what particular thing to buy, ...",
            "join or enter a competition",
            "make reasonable progress without any serious problems",
            "to refuse to accept or continue something"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to several shops before you decide what particular thing to buy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shore up",
        "options": [
            "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ...",
            "to refuse to accept that something is important or true",
            "same as gulp",
            "to leave or go away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to support something such as a wall to prevent it from falling, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "short out",
        "options": [
            "short circuit",
            "if you dissolve into something such as tears or laughter, you begin to cry or laugh in an uncontrolled way",
            "to get a large amount of sales or profits, ...",
            "to want to cause trouble for someone because you dislike them"
        ],
        "answer": "short circuit"
    },
    {
        "question": "shout down",
        "options": [
            "move or travel towards",
            "to make it difficult to hear what someone says by shouting while they are speaking",
            "to find a husband or wife for someone",
            "to put a saddle on a horse"
        ],
        "answer": "to make it difficult to hear what someone says by shouting while they are speaking"
    },
    {
        "question": "shout out",
        "options": [
            "to write down information or a statement, ...",
            "visit for a short time",
            "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ...",
            "same as block"
        ],
        "answer": "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shove around",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone badly and in an unfair way, especially by giving them orders",
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way",
            "to damage the surface of the ground by walking or driving over it too much, ...",
            "to take the place of someone temporarily"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone badly and in an unfair way, especially by giving them orders"
    },
    {
        "question": "shove off",
        "options": [
            "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ...",
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ...",
            "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ...",
            "to let yourself feel or show an emotion that you would normally not feel or show"
        ],
        "answer": "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shove over",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "write something short like a phone number for future reference.",
            "to agree with or go along with an idea or suggestion, ...",
            "to move in order to make more room for someone else"
        ],
        "answer": "to move in order to make more room for someone else"
    },
    {
        "question": "show around",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a group of things into a series",
            "to write exactly what someone has written or said",
            "to lead someone around a place for the first time, so that they can see all parts of it",
            "used about goods, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to lead someone around a place for the first time, so that they can see all parts of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "show in",
        "options": [
            "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is",
            "criticise or insult",
            "to lead someone into a room where they are going to meet other people",
            "if you colour up, your face becomes red"
        ],
        "answer": "to lead someone into a room where they are going to meet other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "show off",
        "options": [
            "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ...",
            "to give a baby the same name as someone else, especially a member of your family",
            "if you run up against problems, difficulties etc, you have to deal with them",
            "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something look very impressive or attractive, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "show out",
        "options": [
            "to not go to bed",
            "to lead someone to the door by which they leave a place",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to not approve of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to lead someone to the door by which they leave a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "show over",
        "options": [
            "make or persuade someone to accept something of lower quality than they wanted",
            "stop doing something (used as an imperative)",
            "manage with little money",
            "to lead someone around a place in order to show them how interesting or attractive it is"
        ],
        "answer": "to lead someone around a place in order to show them how interesting or attractive it is"
    },
    {
        "question": "show round",
        "options": [
            "same as show",
            "to start working hard and seriously",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to start a conversation with someone because you want to have a sexual or romantic relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "same as show"
    },
    {
        "question": "show through",
        "options": [
            "to consider something when making a plan or calculation",
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something",
            "to have space for someone or something, ...",
            "when a feeling can be seen despite attempts to conceal it"
        ],
        "answer": "when a feeling can be seen despite attempts to conceal it"
    },
    {
        "question": "show up",
        "options": [
            "same as show, ...",
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something",
            "pass (time)"
        ],
        "answer": "same as show, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shrink from",
        "options": [
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people",
            "to be very busy doing a lot of different things",
            "to not be willing to do something difficult, or to not deal with something unpleasant",
            "exploit, use to your advantage"
        ],
        "answer": "to not be willing to do something difficult, or to not deal with something unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "shrug off",
        "options": [
            "treat badly or defeat",
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ...",
            "to deal with something easily and successfully, ...",
            "same as straighten, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with something easily and successfully, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shuck off",
        "options": [
            "to get things from different places or people after people have finished with them",
            "to give something old as part of the payment for something new",
            "invest in something",
            "to take a piece of clothing off"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a piece of clothing off"
    },
    {
        "question": "shudder at",
        "options": [
            "same as key",
            "make yourself popular with someone",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "to be shocked by something"
        ],
        "answer": "to be shocked by something"
    },
    {
        "question": "shuffle through",
        "options": [
            "to look for something in a group of things, in a container, or in your pockets",
            "be upset",
            "if words pop out, you say them suddenly without thinking about it first",
            "if you fit things together, you join them in the right way to make something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to look for something in a group of things, in a container, or in your pockets"
    },
    {
        "question": "shut away",
        "options": [
            "put something in a place without taking care",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people"
        ],
        "answer": "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "shut down",
        "options": [
            "if a machine or computer shuts down, or if someone shuts it down, it stops operating, ...",
            "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ...",
            "if you dine out on an event or experience, people invite you to meals so that you can tell them about it",
            "to produce something such as heat, light, or a smell"
        ],
        "answer": "if a machine or computer shuts down, or if someone shuts it down, it stops operating, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shut in",
        "options": [
            "to put a person or animal in a place that they cannot leave",
            "visit different places for pleasure",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ...",
            "to go and see someone again, usually for a short time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put a person or animal in a place that they cannot leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "shut off",
        "options": [
            "to try to find or get something in a relaxed way",
            "if a group of people forms up, they move together in order to create a group that is correctly or tidily arranged",
            "to stop the flow of something, usually water or electricity, ...",
            "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop the flow of something, usually water or electricity, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shut out",
        "options": [
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen",
            "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ...",
            "to not allow someone to enter a particular place, ...",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to not allow someone to enter a particular place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shut out of",
        "options": [
            "add a keyword link or bookmark to a blog entry or webpage",
            "remove clothing to a certain level",
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "if someone is shut out of something, they are not allowed to do it or be involved in it"
        ],
        "answer": "if someone is shut out of something, they are not allowed to do it or be involved in it"
    },
    {
        "question": "shut up",
        "options": [
            "talk too much",
            "to stop talking or making a noise, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver pulls up, they stop, ...",
            "to study something very hard, especially for an examination"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop talking or making a noise, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "shut yourself away",
        "options": [
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ...",
            "reduce, decrease",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ...",
            "withdraw from company"
        ],
        "answer": "withdraw from company"
    },
    {
        "question": "shy away",
        "options": [
            "to try to do a lot of things or to go to a lot of places in a short period of time",
            "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident",
            "when something continues to happen",
            "to point a weapon at someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid someone, or to be unwilling to do something, because you are nervous, afraid, or not confident"
    },
    {
        "question": "shy away from",
        "options": [
            "avoid doing something because you lack confidence",
            "to take no action when something bad is happening",
            "blush",
            "to heat food until it is warm in all parts"
        ],
        "answer": "avoid doing something because you lack confidence"
    },
    {
        "question": "side with",
        "options": [
            "argue with someone about a specific subject",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair",
            "to give power or control to someone else, ...",
            "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument"
        ],
        "answer": "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument"
    },
    {
        "question": "sidle up to",
        "options": [
            "to tick off something",
            "if it is peeing down, a lot of rain is falling",
            "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried",
            "approach someone discreetly"
        ],
        "answer": "approach someone discreetly"
    },
    {
        "question": "sift out",
        "options": [
            "forward a film or tape to a certain point",
            "to gradually start using something",
            "to remove one part of something",
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove one part of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sift through",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone badly, especially because they have less power or importance than you",
            "to remove something from a list or record, ...",
            "same as sift",
            "to stop doing one thing and start doing another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as sift"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign away",
        "options": [
            "obtain information someone is unwilling to give up",
            "try to compensate for doing something wrong",
            "same as bag",
            "if you sign away property or a right to something, you agree that it no longer belongs to you by writing your name on a document"
        ],
        "answer": "if you sign away property or a right to something, you agree that it no longer belongs to you by writing your name on a document"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign for",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to tell you something",
            "if you sign for a sports club, you join it by signing a contract, ...",
            "to make a photograph bigger, ...",
            "to cheat by not obeying the rules on something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you sign for a sports club, you join it by signing a contract, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign in",
        "options": [
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to try to make someone or something leave a place, ...",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "to remain under water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign into",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home",
            "to masturbate",
            "open a particular computer program that requires a name and password"
        ],
        "answer": "open a particular computer program that requires a name and password"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign off",
        "options": [
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "same as hire, ...",
            "a phrase that was used a greeting",
            "to end a letter, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to end a letter, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign off on",
        "options": [
            "to do something, or to deal with something, very easily",
            "to shoot with a gun or other weapon, ...",
            "to officially agree to something",
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to officially agree to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign on",
        "options": [
            "if something lies ahead, especially something difficult or unpleasant, it is going to happen in the future and you will have to deal with it",
            "to employ someone to do a job, ...",
            "criticise angrily",
            "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection"
        ],
        "answer": "to employ someone to do a job, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign on with",
        "options": [
            "sign a document joining or agreeing to something",
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ...",
            "to behave in a very friendly or polite way to someone because you want them to like you or to do something for you"
        ],
        "answer": "sign a document joining or agreeing to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign out",
        "options": [
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to be very obvious or noticeable, ...",
            "to write your name on an official list when you leave a place, ...",
            "to visit a place for a short time on your way to another place"
        ],
        "answer": "to write your name on an official list when you leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign out of",
        "options": [
            "close a particular computer program that requires a name and password",
            "to increase something, ...",
            "to be a person or company that hides an illegal or secret activity for another person or organization",
            "inform the authorities about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "close a particular computer program that requires a name and password"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign over",
        "options": [
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document",
            "to become bigger and heavier",
            "to make something be successful, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document"
    },
    {
        "question": "sign up",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the total amount of something by gradually using small amounts of it",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "to continue to work hard on something",
            "same as sign, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as sign, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sign with",
        "options": [
            "to tick off something",
            "if you sign with a sports club, you join it by signing a contract",
            "to make a room look tidy after someone else has made it untidy",
            "to not allow yourself to be treated badly, especially by someone in authority"
        ],
        "answer": "if you sign with a sports club, you join it by signing a contract"
    },
    {
        "question": "simmer down",
        "options": [
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "to give something or someone a particular quality, ...",
            "press or twist something hard into something else",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry"
        ],
        "answer": "to become calm after being excited or angry"
    },
    {
        "question": "sing along",
        "options": [
            "same as bag",
            "if two people double up, they share something, especially a bedroom",
            "to sing a song with someone who is already singing",
            "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to sing a song with someone who is already singing"
    },
    {
        "question": "sing out",
        "options": [
            "to call out loudly, ...",
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "to try to find every member of a group, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to call out loudly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sing up",
        "options": [
            "in science fiction stories, to bring someone back to their spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "to sing with a louder voice",
            "same as finish, ...",
            "to become covered in a thin layer of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to sing with a louder voice"
    },
    {
        "question": "single out",
        "options": [
            "same as bust, ...",
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ...",
            "to choose one person from a group for special attention"
        ],
        "answer": "to choose one person from a group for special attention"
    },
    {
        "question": "sink in",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to deal again with something that you were dealing with earlier",
            "if something bad or unpleasant lets up, it slows down or stops, ...",
            "to become completely understood"
        ],
        "answer": "to become completely understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit about",
        "options": [
            "sit and do nothing, especially when you should be working",
            "same as blot",
            "to come to a particular place without planning to",
            "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home"
        ],
        "answer": "sit and do nothing, especially when you should be working"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit around",
        "options": [
            "to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself, doing no work",
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "to form a solid mass, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time doing nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit back",
        "options": [
            "to relax and stop making the effort to do something",
            "go to someone",
            "reduce, decrease",
            "to increase something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to relax and stop making the effort to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit by",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly",
            "same as fade, ...",
            "to take no action when something bad is happening",
            "short circuit"
        ],
        "answer": "to take no action when something bad is happening"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit down",
        "options": [
            "entertain someone in your home",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair",
            "to annoy someone or make them disappointed",
            "perform surgery"
        ],
        "answer": "to make yourself comfortable in a chair"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit for",
        "options": [
            "sell something cheaply to get rid of it",
            "to give someone money or property in a legal and official way, ...",
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to babysit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to babysit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sit in",
        "options": [
            "to find someone or something by looking for them in a determined way",
            "if people sit in, they take part in a sit-in",
            "to take air into your lungs through your nose or mouth, ...",
            "same as toss, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if people sit in, they take part in a sit-in"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit in for",
        "options": [
            "argue about a problem to find a solution",
            "to take the place of someone temporarily",
            "to ask someone a question, ...",
            "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it"
        ],
        "answer": "to take the place of someone temporarily"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit in on",
        "options": [
            "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ...",
            "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it",
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use",
            "same as cut, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit on",
        "options": [
            "close a door or window that has been left open",
            "to delay dealing with something",
            "to want something to happen very much, ...",
            "to avoid mentioning something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to delay dealing with something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit out",
        "options": [
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems",
            "to stop doing something for a period of time, ...",
            "to come to a particular place without planning to",
            "to get a large amount of sales or profits, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing something for a period of time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sit over",
        "options": [
            "get something by chance",
            "eat or drink slowly",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "same as lay, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "eat or drink slowly"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit through",
        "options": [
            "beat someone in a debate, discussion or argument, ...",
            "enter or go indoors in a hurry, ...",
            "to stay until the end of something, especially if you are not enjoying it",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stay until the end of something, especially if you are not enjoying it"
    },
    {
        "question": "sit up",
        "options": [
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "not think or consider",
            "make someone feel worried or uneasy"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to bed later than usual, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sit with",
        "options": [
            "same as double",
            "to treat something carefully so that it stays in good condition, ...",
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something",
            "reconcile different positions"
        ],
        "answer": "reconcile different positions"
    },
    {
        "question": "size up",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to wait, ...",
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ...",
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "skate around",
        "options": [
            "to make a profit, ...",
            "to officially ask for something, ...",
            "to decorate a person or object with something, usually for a special occasion",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid a difficult subject or situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "skate over",
        "options": [
            "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ...",
            "same as muddle",
            "to avoid a difficult subject or situation",
            "if people are flooded out, their home becomes filled with water and they are forced to leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid a difficult subject or situation"
    },
    {
        "question": "sketch in",
        "options": [
            "to add more information",
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number",
            "discuss something in great detail, ...",
            "to keep asking someone questions, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to add more information"
    },
    {
        "question": "sketch out",
        "options": [
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them",
            "relax, do nothing",
            "same as sketch",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as sketch"
    },
    {
        "question": "skin up",
        "options": [
            "to rain very hard",
            "to live or work with someone in a friendly way",
            "to begin a new career or way of life, ...",
            "make a cannabis joint"
        ],
        "answer": "make a cannabis joint"
    },
    {
        "question": "skive off",
        "options": [
            "touch someone in a sensual or sexual way",
            "to suddenly enter a room where someone is doing something",
            "to avoid going to school or work when you should go",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid going to school or work when you should go"
    },
    {
        "question": "slack off",
        "options": [
            "visit a lot of different places for pleasure",
            "same as stop",
            "to slow down, or to become less",
            "same as trip, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to slow down, or to become less"
    },
    {
        "question": "slacken off",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone more than once. This word is used especially about men who hit their wives or girlfriends.",
            "to make someone have to deal with something",
            "same as slacken",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as slacken"
    },
    {
        "question": "slag off",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone or something",
            "spend time doing very little or being unproductive",
            "to separate something into different parts or areas",
            "to not show what you are thinking or feeling, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "slam out",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "same as flare, ...",
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "end in an unsuccessful way"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place quickly and angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "slant toward",
        "options": [
            "to show that something is possible",
            "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly",
            "favour one viewpoint, bias",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "favour one viewpoint, bias"
    },
    {
        "question": "slap around",
        "options": [
            "to be defeated by someone in a competition, ...",
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to hit someone more than once. This word is used especially about men who hit their wives or girlfriends."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit someone more than once. This word is used especially about men who hit their wives or girlfriends."
    },
    {
        "question": "slap down",
        "options": [
            "to beat an opponent very easily, ...",
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "if someone\u2019s voice or words trail away or trail off, they gradually become silent",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous"
        ],
        "answer": "to beat an opponent very easily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slap on",
        "options": [
            "to do a lot of activities in a short time",
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ...",
            "circulate (rumours, etc)",
            "to add something as an extra cost, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to add something as an extra cost, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep around",
        "options": [
            "same as push, ...",
            "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people",
            "to eat a particular type of food, especially an expensive one",
            "same as block"
        ],
        "answer": "to have sexual relations with a lot of different people"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep away",
        "options": [
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "to spend a period of time in sleeping, ...",
            "in science fiction stories, to bring someone back to their spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "to spend a period of time in sleeping, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep in",
        "options": [
            "same as broaden",
            "to offer help or information",
            "to continue sleeping after the time that you usually wake up",
            "to heat food that has already been cooked, until every part of it is very hot"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue sleeping after the time that you usually wake up"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep off",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly become unconscious, ...",
            "yield, surrender, retreat, ...",
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to get rid of an unpleasant or uncomfortable feeling by sleeping, especially after eating or drinking too much"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of an unpleasant or uncomfortable feeling by sleeping, especially after eating or drinking too much"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep on",
        "options": [
            "to invite someone to go somewhere such as a restaurant or cinema with you, often because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them",
            "to wait to make a decision until the next day, after you have rested and had more time to think",
            "join a teleconference",
            "to change the date or time of an event so that it happens earlier, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wait to make a decision until the next day, after you have rested and had more time to think"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep out",
        "options": [
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air",
            "try to find something",
            "talk just for the point of talking rather than having anything to say",
            "to sleep outside"
        ],
        "answer": "to sleep outside"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep over",
        "options": [
            "to ask for someone to come to you, ...",
            "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night",
            "to begin to have more of a particular quality",
            "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit"
        ],
        "answer": "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep through",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something",
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction",
            "to make a drink of tea, ...",
            "to continue sleeping for a long time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue sleeping for a long time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep together",
        "options": [
            "to make a profit from something, ...",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "eat something enthusiastically",
            "start to have a negative feeling"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married"
    },
    {
        "question": "sleep with",
        "options": [
            "to have a particular name, ...",
            "to tell a player officially to leave the sports field because they have done something that is not allowed by the rules",
            "to have sex with someone, especially someone who you are not married to",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
        ],
        "answer": "to have sex with someone, especially someone who you are not married to"
    },
    {
        "question": "slice off",
        "options": [
            "to remove something by cutting it",
            "to make something possible",
            "to make a short visit somewhere",
            "to wish to enter a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something by cutting it"
    },
    {
        "question": "slice up",
        "options": [
            "cut completely into pieces or slices",
            "same as sign, ...",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ...",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station."
        ],
        "answer": "cut completely into pieces or slices"
    },
    {
        "question": "slim down",
        "options": [
            "same as camp, ...",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "to continue to talk about something unpleasant that someone else no longer wants to talk or think about",
            "to lose weight, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to lose weight, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sling off",
        "options": [
            "to deal with something easily and successfully, ...",
            "to blame or criticize someone in an unpleasant, unkind way",
            "to send a letter or document to an organization, ...",
            "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly"
        ],
        "answer": "to blame or criticize someone in an unpleasant, unkind way"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip away",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly make a car start moving very quickly so that it makes a lot of noise",
            "to leave secretly, ...",
            "to form a row, or to put people or things in a row, ...",
            "same as lead to"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave secretly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slip by",
        "options": [
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way",
            "to take a vehicle away from a place by towing it, especially because it is parked illegally",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
        ],
        "answer": "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip down",
        "options": [
            "if a situation or feeling boils up, people start to feel angry, ...",
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "if something such as a sound or smell issues from a place, it comes out from there",
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat"
        ],
        "answer": "be enjoyable to drink or eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip in",
        "options": [
            "to slightly change something that you previously said, or to slightly change your opinion on an issue",
            "eat or drink slowly",
            "if you slip in a remark, you make sure that you say it in a conversation in a way that is not too obvious",
            "same as mount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you slip in a remark, you make sure that you say it in a conversation in a way that is not too obvious"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip into",
        "options": [
            "same as pass, ...",
            "stop doing something annoying",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly put on a piece of clothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slip off",
        "options": [
            "same as hang",
            "to have happened previously, ...",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly",
            "to take someone or something with you when you go somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a piece of clothing off quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip off to",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere discreetly",
            "do something quickly",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you"
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere discreetly"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip on",
        "options": [
            "to keep one area separate from another",
            "understand something, often after a long time",
            "same as bung, ...",
            "to put clothes on"
        ],
        "answer": "to put clothes on"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip out",
        "options": [
            "to reduce an amount of money by using it",
            "if something, especially a secret, slips out, you say it without intending to",
            "to stop doing something",
            "to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "if something, especially a secret, slips out, you say it without intending to"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip out of",
        "options": [
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number",
            "phone back",
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way",
            "to take clothes off"
        ],
        "answer": "to take clothes off"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip through",
        "options": [
            "to pay for something",
            "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you",
            "to think someone or something is wrong",
            "escape notice and be approved"
        ],
        "answer": "escape notice and be approved"
    },
    {
        "question": "slip up",
        "options": [
            "to make a careless mistake",
            "to try to influence someone, ...",
            "to have something as a very important part or purpose, ...",
            "if someone scrubs up well, they look good when they have made an effort when getting ready to go out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a careless mistake"
    },
    {
        "question": "slob about",
        "options": [
            "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it",
            "same as flare, ...",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions"
        ],
        "answer": "be lazy, do nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "slob around",
        "options": [
            "to gradually become smaller or weaker before coming to an end or disappearing completely",
            "same as bundle, ...",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "if you play two people off against each other, you try to cause an argument between them because you think that this will give you more power or control in a situation"
        ],
        "answer": "be lazy, do nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "slobber over",
        "options": [
            "to burn someone\u2019s home so that they have to leave it, ...",
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "if a ship heaves to, it stops moving. The past tense and past participle is hove to.",
            "to be ready to do something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing"
    },
    {
        "question": "slope off",
        "options": [
            "if something unpleasant sets in, it starts to happen and have an effect, and is not likely to stop for a long time",
            "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ...",
            "to deal with or take responsibility for someone or something",
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed"
    },
    {
        "question": "slosh around",
        "options": [
            "to admire and respect someone",
            "to pay no attention to something, ...",
            "if money is sloshing around, a lot of it is available or people are spending a lot of it",
            "to progress at a very slow steady rate"
        ],
        "answer": "if money is sloshing around, a lot of it is available or people are spending a lot of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "slough off",
        "options": [
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "do something without help",
            "same as slough, ...",
            "same as watch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as slough, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slow down",
        "options": [
            "same as write off",
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "same as slow, ...",
            "if time goes by, it passes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as slow, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slow up",
        "options": [
            "same as slow, ...",
            "to think about a time or event in the past, ...",
            "to leave an official position or job, especially so that someone else can take your place",
            "same as stow, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as slow, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "slug it out",
        "options": [
            "if memories or feelings flood back, you suddenly remember them very clearly",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm",
            "same as mail",
            "fight or argue"
        ],
        "answer": "fight or argue"
    },
    {
        "question": "smack of",
        "options": [
            "same as wrap, ...",
            "to connect one thing or person to another, ...",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy"
        ],
        "answer": "to be a sign of something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "smash down",
        "options": [
            "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose",
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to make something fall down and break into pieces by hitting it very hard",
            "to find something or to meet someone by chance"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something fall down and break into pieces by hitting it very hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "smash in",
        "options": [
            "criticise",
            "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ...",
            "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ...",
            "to hit someone hard in the face, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit someone hard in the face, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "smash into",
        "options": [
            "to aim at something and move quickly and directly to it, ...",
            "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult",
            "to agree to be responsible for something, ...",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "smash up",
        "options": [
            "same as bring round",
            "not pay attention, ...",
            "to steal something, ...",
            "to destroy something completely by violently breaking it into many pieces"
        ],
        "answer": "to destroy something completely by violently breaking it into many pieces"
    },
    {
        "question": "smoke out",
        "options": [
            "to make information publicly known, ...",
            "to begin something or begin to take part in something",
            "to become covered with a layer of ice",
            "to admire and respect someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to make information publicly known, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "smooth over",
        "options": [
            "be jealous, abuse or have an active hatred of someone",
            "join a teleconference",
            "to make a problem seem less serious",
            "to become involved in something by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a problem seem less serious"
    },
    {
        "question": "snaffle up",
        "options": [
            "consume, take, buy something other people may want",
            "same as cloud, ...",
            "avoid doing something because you lack confidence",
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth"
        ],
        "answer": "consume, take, buy something other people may want"
    },
    {
        "question": "snap off",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ...",
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question",
            "break a piece off something",
            "same as chill"
        ],
        "answer": "break a piece off something"
    },
    {
        "question": "snap out of",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, machine etc",
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question",
            "control negative emotions",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you have arrived at work"
        ],
        "answer": "control negative emotions"
    },
    {
        "question": "snap to it!",
        "options": [
            "to explain to someone in detail how something should be done, what something is about etc",
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "do something quickly",
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more"
        ],
        "answer": "do something quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "snap up",
        "options": [
            "to immediately take advantage of an opportunity, ...",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "to attack someone violently, ...",
            "to send air out of your lungs through your nose or mouth, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to immediately take advantage of an opportunity, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "snarl up",
        "options": [
            "same as snarl",
            "to encourage someone to do something or to expect something, especially by lying to them or promising them something that they cannot have",
            "to rub a surface to make it smooth or dry, ...",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as snarl"
    },
    {
        "question": "sneak out",
        "options": [
            "to take out, ...",
            "depart furtively",
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "same as warm, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "depart furtively"
    },
    {
        "question": "sneak up",
        "options": [
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "to begin doing something, especially in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get very near someone before they notice you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sneak up on",
        "options": [
            "if you fling clothes on, you put them on quickly",
            "to agree with or be the same as something else",
            "control negative emotions",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get very near someone before they notice you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sniff around",
        "options": [
            "eat something",
            "to try to find out information, ...",
            "to send someone a copy of an email or letter that you are sending to another person",
            "to support someone in a game, competition etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out information, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sniff at",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to let someone come into a place",
            "to do something or move somewhere more quickly, ...",
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "to smell something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to smell something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sniff out",
        "options": [
            "become rigid, ...",
            "to discover something, ...",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ...",
            "to have oral sex with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to discover something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "snitch on",
        "options": [
            "persuade or pressure to accept something",
            "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "divulge secrets, inform authorities about someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "snuff out",
        "options": [
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "to make people understand something",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private",
            "to make something end quickly, especially by using force, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something end quickly, especially by using force, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "soak in",
        "options": [
            "to spend time experiencing and enjoying the mood or feeling in a place, ...",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "make very secure",
            "collapse, break, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time experiencing and enjoying the mood or feeling in a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "soak up",
        "options": [
            "dedicate time, energy, etc, to something",
            "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ...",
            "to continue doing something as quickly as possible",
            "leave ('moggie off' is also used.)"
        ],
        "answer": "to use a lot of something such as money or time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sober up",
        "options": [
            "to become sober after being drunk, ...",
            "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times",
            "to make certain about something by checking it",
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed"
        ],
        "answer": "to become sober after being drunk, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sock away",
        "options": [
            "save money in a bank account, investment, etc",
            "to keep one area separate from another",
            "become rigid, ...",
            "to pay no attention to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "save money in a bank account, investment, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "sock in",
        "options": [
            "include someone or something in a group, category, etc",
            "close access to a place because of bad weather",
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "to avoid mentioning something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "close access to a place because of bad weather"
    },
    {
        "question": "sod off",
        "options": [
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "sleep, take a nap",
            "to go away, ...",
            "to have an erection, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to go away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "soften up",
        "options": [
            "to lift something or someone quickly with your hands or arms, ...",
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ...",
            "lower the top half of your body"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "soldier on",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "not pay attention, ...",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "to continue to do something even though it is difficult or unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do something even though it is difficult or unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "sort out",
        "options": [
            "to formally offer an idea or proposal to someone for them to consider or accept",
            "treat someone badly",
            "to provide something for someone, ...",
            "to die. This word is used to avoid saying \u2018die\u2019 when you think this might upset someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to provide something for someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sort through",
        "options": [
            "to repair something, often quickly and not very well, ...",
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need",
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "to talk about something for a long time in a very boring way"
        ],
        "answer": "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need"
    },
    {
        "question": "sound off",
        "options": [
            "enter a place quickly",
            "to express your opinions loudly, especially in an unreasonable way",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "to consider a problem or decision carefully"
        ],
        "answer": "to express your opinions loudly, especially in an unreasonable way"
    },
    {
        "question": "sound out",
        "options": [
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound",
            "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling",
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them",
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "spaff away",
        "options": [
            "same as face",
            "waste (money, time, resources, etc)",
            "same as draw on",
            "be funny, or try to"
        ],
        "answer": "waste (money, time, resources, etc)"
    },
    {
        "question": "spark off",
        "options": [
            "charge more for something",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well",
            "same as open, ...",
            "cause something, usually unpleasant, to happen"
        ],
        "answer": "cause something, usually unpleasant, to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "spark up",
        "options": [
            "to use all of a supply of something",
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "light a cigarette or joint",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal"
        ],
        "answer": "light a cigarette or joint"
    },
    {
        "question": "speak for",
        "options": [
            "to consider something in a particular way, ...",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "to represent the feelings or opinions of another person or group of people",
            "to remove all or most of your clothes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to represent the feelings or opinions of another person or group of people"
    },
    {
        "question": "speak of",
        "options": [
            "to spread to other areas",
            "to reduce something, ...",
            "to start a piece of knitting by making the first row of stitches",
            "to seem to prove that something exists or is true"
        ],
        "answer": "to seem to prove that something exists or is true"
    },
    {
        "question": "speak out",
        "options": [
            "to physically attack someone or something, ...",
            "arrive or get a result",
            "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something",
            "to phone someone again, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to state your opinion firmly and publicly about something, especially in order to protest against or defend something"
    },
    {
        "question": "speak to",
        "options": [
            "approach someone without their knowing",
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to discuss a plan or a situation in a detailed way, ...",
            "to talk to someone who has done something wrong in an effort to persuade them to improve their behaviour"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk to someone who has done something wrong in an effort to persuade them to improve their behaviour"
    },
    {
        "question": "speak up",
        "options": [
            "to talk louder, ...",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to make something smaller in size, amount etc than it used to be",
            "to stop something from happening"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk louder, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "speak up for",
        "options": [
            "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time",
            "to say something in support of someone or something",
            "sleep somewhere temporarily because you don't go home",
            "to help someone to get rid of feelings of sadness, worry, or anger by kissing them to show that you are sympathetic"
        ],
        "answer": "to say something in support of someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "speed up",
        "options": [
            "to have oral sex with someone",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to hold something above someone or something, ...",
            "to move or happen faster, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to move or happen faster, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spell out",
        "options": [
            "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife",
            "to think about what is likely to happen, or to plan what you are going to do in the future",
            "take care of yourself or someone with help from other people",
            "to say or write the letters of a word in the correct order, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say or write the letters of a word in the correct order, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spew out",
        "options": [
            "expel, throw out",
            "relax, unwind",
            "gradually become attached, united or close",
            "to heat food that has already been cooked, until every part of it is very hot"
        ],
        "answer": "expel, throw out"
    },
    {
        "question": "spew up",
        "options": [
            "if a bell peals out, it makes a loud sound",
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer",
            "keep quiet, say nothing",
            "vomit"
        ],
        "answer": "vomit"
    },
    {
        "question": "spice up",
        "options": [
            "to officially ask for something, ...",
            "to make something more interesting or exciting, ...",
            "to do something good that helps someone to feel better after you did something bad to them, ...",
            "to suddenly say or shout something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something more interesting or exciting, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spiff up",
        "options": [
            "to make a problem seem less serious",
            "to hit something lightly and then move away in a different direction",
            "make something smart or more presentable",
            "to take control of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "make something smart or more presentable"
    },
    {
        "question": "spike up",
        "options": [
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ...",
            "to stand somewhere and do nothing, often when you should be doing something",
            "increase sharply"
        ],
        "answer": "increase sharply"
    },
    {
        "question": "spill out",
        "options": [
            "criticise",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "pressure someone to accept something offered",
            "express or display emotions openly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "express or display emotions openly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spill over",
        "options": [
            "to spread to other areas",
            "praise someone in an excessive way to get their favour or something from them",
            "to give all your attention to something",
            "same as bust, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spread to other areas"
    },
    {
        "question": "spin off",
        "options": [
            "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ...",
            "to try to achieve a particular thing",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "to help someone, especially by doing a particular job or by giving them money"
        ],
        "answer": "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spin out",
        "options": [
            "to be owned by someone, ...",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "to spend a lot of money on something, ...",
            "to make something last for a long time, usually longer than is good or necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something last for a long time, usually longer than is good or necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "spin round",
        "options": [
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to decide that you want to do something or be involved in something",
            "same as spin, ...",
            "to be an aspect of a situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as spin, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spirit away",
        "options": [
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to go past, ...",
            "to be the most important aspect of a situation or problem, ...",
            "leave a place angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "remove someone secretly from a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "spirit off",
        "options": [
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ...",
            "to clean the inside of something thoroughly"
        ],
        "answer": "remove someone secretly from a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "spit at",
        "options": [
            "to not approve of something",
            "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth",
            "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult",
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult"
    },
    {
        "question": "spit it out",
        "options": [
            "same as spit, ...",
            "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime",
            "to sit down carelessly but gently",
            "to completely fill a container that is already partly full, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as spit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spit out",
        "options": [
            "enter a parking area in reverse gear",
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "mean, try to say",
            "same as spit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as spit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spit up",
        "options": [
            "to be a disadvantage in a particular situation",
            "calculate how expensive some work is going to be",
            "if a baby or animal spits up, or if it spits something up, it brings a small amount of food back up from its stomach and out of its mouth",
            "to spend time relaxing and doing nothing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a baby or animal spits up, or if it spits something up, it brings a small amount of food back up from its stomach and out of its mouth"
    },
    {
        "question": "splash around",
        "options": [
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "to copy someone or something\u2019s style",
            "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger",
            "to move around noisily in water"
        ],
        "answer": "to move around noisily in water"
    },
    {
        "question": "splash down",
        "options": [
            "when a space vehicle splashes down, it lands in the sea after being in space",
            "same as come across, ...",
            "to continue for longer than expected or planned, ...",
            "to move away from someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "when a space vehicle splashes down, it lands in the sea after being in space"
    },
    {
        "question": "splash out",
        "options": [
            "to buy something expensive",
            "to increase or improve something in order to make it the same as other things of its type",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left"
        ],
        "answer": "to buy something expensive"
    },
    {
        "question": "splash out on",
        "options": [
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "to buy something expensive",
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)"
        ],
        "answer": "to buy something expensive"
    },
    {
        "question": "split up",
        "options": [
            "used for warning someone to be careful, especially because they are likely to have an accident",
            "to not approach someone or something",
            "same as split, ...",
            "to complete something that was planned, often despite difficulties or opposition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as split, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spoil for",
        "options": [
            "to discuss a plan or a situation in a detailed way, ...",
            "to be better than other things of the same type, ...",
            "really want something",
            "to start to fight an enemy in battle, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "really want something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sponge down",
        "options": [
            "same as tail off",
            "to consider a problem or decision carefully",
            "clean something with a sponge",
            "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you"
        ],
        "answer": "clean something with a sponge"
    },
    {
        "question": "sponge off",
        "options": [
            "to consider something as separate from other things, ...",
            "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed",
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself",
            "to manage to reach or touch something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself"
    },
    {
        "question": "sponge on",
        "options": [
            "accept or get money without doing any work",
            "criticise",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction",
            "to listen to someone who is speaking about a particular thing, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "accept or get money without doing any work"
    },
    {
        "question": "spread out",
        "options": [
            "same as spread, ...",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "mess up, ruin",
            "to get rid of someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as spread, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spring back",
        "options": [
            "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed",
            "to gradually become weaker or to disappear",
            "to say something while you are breathing with difficulty, for example because you need more air, or are in pain",
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them"
        ],
        "answer": "return to original position after being bent, forced or when pressure is removed"
    },
    {
        "question": "spring for",
        "options": [
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to pay for someone else\u2019s share of something",
            "to persuade someone to buy or accept something that you do not want, especially something of low quality",
            "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay for someone else\u2019s share of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "spring from",
        "options": [
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to come from a particular place, family, or situation, ...",
            "to move information or users of a computer system to a new place or to new equipment at the same time or in an order that causes as few problems as possible",
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to come from a particular place, family, or situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spring on",
        "options": [
            "same as cloud, ...",
            "to tell someone something that they do not expect",
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone something that they do not expect"
    },
    {
        "question": "spring up",
        "options": [
            "fall, ...",
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "to remain in a place for longer than you originally intended, especially in order to wait for something to happen",
            "remove a title, award or position"
        ],
        "answer": "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "spruce up",
        "options": [
            "to handle or use something in a stupid or careless way",
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ...",
            "to improve the appearance of someone or something",
            "to make a sound at a particular level, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to improve the appearance of someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "spur on",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly stop working, ...",
            "same as join, ...",
            "encourage someone to continue",
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "encourage someone to continue"
    },
    {
        "question": "spy on",
        "options": [
            "reserve",
            "to develop something, ...",
            "to watch someone secretly so that you know everything that they do, ...",
            "to make someone get used to something when they are young"
        ],
        "answer": "to watch someone secretly so that you know everything that they do, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "spy out",
        "options": [
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "criticise or nag",
            "tie something so that it doesn't move",
            "same as spy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as spy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "square away",
        "options": [
            "same as cut down, ...",
            "to listen to a radio programme, ...",
            "to do the things necessary to complete something",
            "to not approve of something because you think that it is dishonest or immoral, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do the things necessary to complete something"
    },
    {
        "question": "square off",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as an edge or corner straight",
            "to happen or exist immediately before something, ...",
            "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ...",
            "same as broaden"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something such as an edge or corner straight"
    },
    {
        "question": "square off against",
        "options": [
            "to have a good result, ...",
            "to pay for someone else\u2019s share of something",
            "same as hire, ...",
            "confront someone or prepare to fight them"
        ],
        "answer": "confront someone or prepare to fight them"
    },
    {
        "question": "square up",
        "options": [
            "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to",
            "if two people square up, one pays what they owe so that both people are equal, ...",
            "to discuss something with someone in order to get their opinion and make a decision, ...",
            "to suddenly remember something that happened in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people square up, one pays what they owe so that both people are equal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "square up to",
        "options": [
            "to put someone in a room and lock the door so they cannot leave, ...",
            "to take someone somewhere, especially to a prison or hospital",
            "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
    },
    {
        "question": "square with",
        "options": [
            "to get permission from someone to do something, ...",
            "to go away, ...",
            "to continue encouraging and persuading someone to do something",
            "to separate something into different parts or areas"
        ],
        "answer": "to get permission from someone to do something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "squeeze in",
        "options": [
            "marry someone of the same ethnicity, religion, etc",
            "to develop and become a particular thing or person, ...",
            "to behave in a silly way for fun, ...",
            "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time"
        ],
        "answer": "to be able to do something, even though you do not have much time"
    },
    {
        "question": "squeeze out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ...",
            "to sit down carelessly but gently",
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "to be full of a strong emotion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone tell you something even though they do not want to, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "squeeze up",
        "options": [
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number",
            "same as brighten, ...",
            "make someone feel worried or uneasy",
            "get more people into a space than normal or comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "get more people into a space than normal or comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "stack up",
        "options": [
            "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night",
            "persuade someone to do something",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence",
            "same as stack, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as stack, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stack up against",
        "options": [
            "be as good as something",
            "to suddenly put someone in a new job when people do not expect it",
            "enter in a dramatic or attention-seeking manner",
            "to tie people together with ropes, especially people who are climbing"
        ],
        "answer": "be as good as something"
    },
    {
        "question": "staff up",
        "options": [
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "confuse, deceive",
            "get so emotional that you lose control",
            "employ someone for something specific"
        ],
        "answer": "employ someone for something specific"
    },
    {
        "question": "stake out",
        "options": [
            "to have sex with someone, especially someone who you are not married to",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to apply to buy shares in a company",
            "to explain your opinion clearly and defend it in a determined way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to explain your opinion clearly and defend it in a determined way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stammer out",
        "options": [
            "to leave or go away, ...",
            "to be the result of something",
            "to say something while stammering",
            "to go and see someone again, usually for a short time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say something while stammering"
    },
    {
        "question": "stamp on",
        "options": [
            "to keep criticizing someone or something",
            "to combine with something, ...",
            "leave to meet someone after they have left the place you're at, ...",
            "to stop something by taking determined action, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop something by taking determined action, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stamp out",
        "options": [
            "to gradually make something weaker, smaller, or less effective, ...",
            "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different",
            "to make a fire stop burning by putting your feet down hard on it, ...",
            "to discover something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a fire stop burning by putting your feet down hard on it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand about",
        "options": [
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "if information goes in, you understand it, ...",
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ...",
            "same as stand"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stand"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand against",
        "options": [
            "to try to take hold of something, ...",
            "to oppose someone or something, especially in a brave or determined way, ...",
            "to find out information about someone, especially secretly",
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "to oppose someone or something, especially in a brave or determined way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand around",
        "options": [
            "ruin or spoil something",
            "to stand somewhere and do nothing, often when you should be doing something",
            "same as choke, ...",
            "to be opposed to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stand somewhere and do nothing, often when you should be doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand aside",
        "options": [
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ...",
            "to become fatter",
            "not think or consider",
            "same as mark out, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to let someone else have your job or position, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand at",
        "options": [
            "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health",
            "to grow taller very quickly, ...",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "to receive something such as criticism"
        ],
        "answer": "to reach a particular level, amount etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand back",
        "options": [
            "invite",
            "if coloured, cut, or permed hair grows out, it grows so that it no longer has the colour or style that it had",
            "to try to avoid dealing with a difficult or unpleasant situation, ...",
            "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a building stands back from a road, it is a short distance away from it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand between",
        "options": [
            "escape notice and be approved",
            "to try to find out information about something",
            "to prevent someone from gaining or achieving something",
            "to have a tooth removed from your mouth or an organ removed from your body, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prevent someone from gaining or achieving something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand by",
        "options": [
            "to stop something by taking determined action, ...",
            "to begin to have more of a particular quality",
            "to be ready to do something, ...",
            "to ignore or avoid unpleasant facts"
        ],
        "answer": "to be ready to do something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand down",
        "options": [
            "same as join, ...",
            "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from",
            "remove someone secretly from a place",
            "to leave a job or position, especially an important one, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a job or position, especially an important one, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand for",
        "options": [
            "to visit someone, usually for a short time, ...",
            "make yourself comfortable",
            "if a court finds for someone, it makes a decision in their favour",
            "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be willing to accept something that someone does, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand in",
        "options": [
            "to make a short visit somewhere",
            "same as stop",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked"
        ],
        "answer": "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand in for",
        "options": [
            "to switch a computer off in the correct way",
            "to do things that help you to make progress towards something that you want to achieve",
            "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it",
            "to want something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do someone else\u2019s job temporarily while they are not available to do it"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand out",
        "options": [
            "to form a long line of traffic that is not moving",
            "re-invest money you have made into a business",
            "return",
            "to be easy to see or notice because of being different, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be easy to see or notice because of being different, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand out against",
        "options": [
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it",
            "if you have someone over, they come to your house to visit you or to stay with you",
            "to cover an area of ground with grass",
            "to state or show publicly that you oppose something"
        ],
        "answer": "to state or show publicly that you oppose something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand out for",
        "options": [
            "drink quickly",
            "same as deal, ...",
            "to say or believe that someone has a particular quality, ...",
            "to refuse to accept less than what you are asking for"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to accept less than what you are asking for"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand over",
        "options": [
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly",
            "to get into a place or something such as a car, especially in large numbers or in a way that is not organized",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ...",
            "to stop for a moment in order to consider something"
        ],
        "answer": "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand up",
        "options": [
            "to increase or improve something, or to make it more interesting",
            "mistreat physically",
            "to leave a place, situation, or person",
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stand up for",
        "options": [
            "to reach out and try to get hold of something",
            "if someone fills out, their body becomes less thin, ...",
            "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked",
            "to invite someone to go with you to a cinema, restaurant etc because you want to start a romantic or sexual relationship with them"
        ],
        "answer": "to defend someone or something that is being criticized or attacked"
    },
    {
        "question": "stand up to",
        "options": [
            "to not allow yourself to be treated badly, especially by someone in authority",
            "to deal with something or someone, ...",
            "expect something to happen (usually negative)",
            "to stop paying attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not allow yourself to be treated badly, especially by someone in authority"
    },
    {
        "question": "stare down",
        "options": [
            "to want something or someone very much",
            "to look at someone for so long that they have to look away",
            "exploit, use to your advantage",
            "to make a place clean and tidy, especially after someone else has used it"
        ],
        "answer": "to look at someone for so long that they have to look away"
    },
    {
        "question": "start back",
        "options": [
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to refuse to accept less than what you are asking for",
            "to begin returning to a place, ...",
            "to be owned by someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin returning to a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start in",
        "options": [
            "to win something, or to achieve something",
            "to have some success but not yet be extremely successful and famous",
            "to begin talking in a boring or annoying way, usually complaining or criticizing someone or something",
            "join a teleconference"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin talking in a boring or annoying way, usually complaining or criticizing someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "start off",
        "options": [
            "eat a big meal, ...",
            "if something such as a proposal gets past someone, or if you get it past someone, it is accepted by someone who has the power to stop it happening",
            "to make something begin, ...",
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something begin, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start off on",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something in a determined way, despite difficulties, opposition, or interruptions",
            "to look for something in a group of things, in a container, or in your pockets",
            "help someone to start a piece or work or activity",
            "to make a noise, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "help someone to start a piece or work or activity"
    },
    {
        "question": "start on",
        "options": [
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special",
            "to waste time doing things that are not important or necessary",
            "to quickly jump or dive into water, ...",
            "to begin working on something or dealing with something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin working on something or dealing with something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start on at",
        "options": [
            "to make something more interesting and exciting",
            "if it is peeing down, a lot of rain is falling",
            "to force saliva out of your mouth in the direction of someone else as an insult",
            "criticise or nag"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise or nag"
    },
    {
        "question": "start out",
        "options": [
            "be bored, upset or sick of something",
            "to begin a journey, ...",
            "same as rise",
            "make electrical connections"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a journey, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start out as",
        "options": [
            "deliver, ...",
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "same as spin, ...",
            "to begin a journey, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a journey, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start out to",
        "options": [
            "to become covered in a thin layer of something",
            "to suddenly have an idea, ...",
            "intend, plan",
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "intend, plan"
    },
    {
        "question": "start over",
        "options": [
            "to continue to be enough or continue to exist, ...",
            "to begin a new career or way of life, ...",
            "to criticize someone in an unkind or unfair way",
            "improve your knowledge quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin a new career or way of life, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "start up",
        "options": [
            "to bring a business, organization, or project into existence, ...",
            "drink quickly",
            "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad",
            "to start doing something new or different"
        ],
        "answer": "to bring a business, organization, or project into existence, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "starve out",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place by preventing them from getting enough food",
            "to make something happen later than it should happen, ...",
            "to annoy someone or make them disappointed",
            "to be closed by means of a zip, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to leave a place by preventing them from getting enough food"
    },
    {
        "question": "stash away",
        "options": [
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "store or hide something in a safe place",
            "to move or happen faster, ...",
            "to follow someone wherever they go, especially in a way that annoys them"
        ],
        "answer": "store or hide something in a safe place"
    },
    {
        "question": "stave in",
        "options": [
            "to build a new room or part onto the outside of a building, ...",
            "join a teleconference",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to break something inwards"
        ],
        "answer": "to break something inwards"
    },
    {
        "question": "stave off",
        "options": [
            "to give something to someone although you would prefer to keep it",
            "to think of something such as an idea or a plan, ...",
            "to stop something from happening",
            "to reduce the size of a group of people or things so that you only keep the best or most useful ones"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop something from happening"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay around",
        "options": [
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something",
            "to not leave a person or place",
            "to go back to an activity after an interruption, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not leave a person or place"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay away",
        "options": [
            "to not approach someone or something",
            "to start doing something, ...",
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ...",
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to not approach someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay away from",
        "options": [
            "to go in the direction of someone or something",
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ...",
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid mentioning something or avoid becoming involved in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay back",
        "options": [
            "invest in something",
            "to sell something after buying it from someone else",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "same as stay, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as stay, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stay behind",
        "options": [
            "if someone or something blends in, they are similar to the other people, objects, buildings etc around them, and so they seem appropriate or you do not notice them",
            "to share or divide something equally, or to be shared or divided equally, ...",
            "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "same as flare"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain somewhere after everyone else has left"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay down",
        "options": [
            "to find an extra meaning in someone\u2019s words or actions that is not obvious or does not exist",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "to remain under water, ...",
            "not gain or have something advantageous"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain under water, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stay in",
        "options": [
            "to move away from a person or place",
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ...",
            "to remain in your home for a period of time",
            "to add a particular amount of money to an amount that is being collected in order to buy something"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain in your home for a period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay off",
        "options": [
            "start to have a negative feeling",
            "to discuss something in order to make a decision",
            "to avoid mentioning something, ...",
            "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid mentioning something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stay on",
        "options": [
            "criticise",
            "look in different places for something",
            "if you have someone round, especially someone who lives near you, they come to your house",
            "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay out",
        "options": [
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "same as turn",
            "to remain out of your home for a period of time",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remain out of your home for a period of time"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay out of",
        "options": [
            "to show that something is true or that someone is telling the truth",
            "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ...",
            "to remove something from a list or record, ...",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid becoming involved in something"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay over",
        "options": [
            "to sleep in someone\u2019s house as a guest for one night",
            "to provide people with something they want or need, especially something unusual or special",
            "work hard doing something",
            "to be given to someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to sleep in someone\u2019s house as a guest for one night"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay together",
        "options": [
            "cause something, usually unpleasant, to happen",
            "same as lock",
            "to cough loudly, ...",
            "if two people stay together, they continue to live together or to have a relationship with each other"
        ],
        "answer": "if two people stay together, they continue to live together or to have a relationship with each other"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay up",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to a place for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to deal with an unpleasant situation in a confident, patient, and determined way",
            "to not go to bed",
            "to find someone or something after a long search"
        ],
        "answer": "to not go to bed"
    },
    {
        "question": "stay with",
        "options": [
            "to stop doing something, especially a job, ...",
            "same as chuck, ...",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to continue doing something although it is difficult or although other people have stopped doing it"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue doing something although it is difficult or although other people have stopped doing it"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal away",
        "options": [
            "to finish your working day, ...",
            "leave a place quietly or secretly",
            "to remove something from your throat or lungs by coughing in a loud rough way, ...",
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place quietly or secretly"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal out",
        "options": [
            "to produce something very quickly and without working very hard",
            "to refuse to think about something unpleasant",
            "to have enough money to buy a particular thing, ...",
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner"
        ],
        "answer": "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal over",
        "options": [
            "to give someone an unpleasant job that no one else wants to do",
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling",
            "to stop yourself from showing negative emotions like anger and disappointment, especially over a long period, so that these feelings develop in a harmful way"
        ],
        "answer": "be gradually overcome by an emotion or feeling"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal up",
        "options": [
            "same as gobble",
            "move about a place",
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "approach quietly or secretly"
        ],
        "answer": "approach quietly or secretly"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal up on",
        "options": [
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something",
            "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before",
            "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly",
            "to leave one place and move to another"
        ],
        "answer": "approach a place or someone quietly or secretly"
    },
    {
        "question": "steam off",
        "options": [
            "if a market or price bounces back, it rises again after falling, ...",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something of lower quality than they wanted",
            "to remove something from a surface using steam",
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something from a surface using steam"
    },
    {
        "question": "steam open",
        "options": [
            "to use steam to separate two edges or pieces of paper that are stuck together",
            "to start attacking or criticizing someone, ...",
            "avoid doing something in a way other people don't like",
            "make a decision by throwing a coin and seeing which side lands face up"
        ],
        "answer": "to use steam to separate two edges or pieces of paper that are stuck together"
    },
    {
        "question": "steam up",
        "options": [
            "shake or pat a cushion so that it fills with air",
            "to kill someone with a gun, ...",
            "to cover something with steam, or to become covered with steam",
            "force a person to leave or go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to cover something with steam, or to become covered with steam"
    },
    {
        "question": "steer clear of",
        "options": [
            "exploit or harm, ...",
            "avoid",
            "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting"
        ],
        "answer": "avoid"
    },
    {
        "question": "stem from",
        "options": [
            "become involved, often against one\ufffds will",
            "to avoid doing something that you should do because it is difficult",
            "to be caused by something",
            "to leave a place, situation, or person"
        ],
        "answer": "to be caused by something"
    },
    {
        "question": "step aside",
        "options": [
            "to waste time, energy, or money",
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly",
            "get lost",
            "to leave an official position or job, especially so that someone else can take your place"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave an official position or job, especially so that someone else can take your place"
    },
    {
        "question": "step back",
        "options": [
            "to stop for a moment in order to consider something",
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work",
            "same as slow, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop for a moment in order to consider something"
    },
    {
        "question": "step down",
        "options": [
            "to do a lot of things for someone, such as cleaning or getting things",
            "same as step",
            "to force someone to leave an organization because they have done something bad",
            "same as pass, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as step"
    },
    {
        "question": "step forward",
        "options": [
            "to heat a metal until it becomes liquid, especially in order to make something new from it",
            "to start a romantic relationship with someone, or to bring two people together because you want them to have a relationship with each other",
            "to offer help to someone who needs it",
            "to suddenly stop working, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to offer help to someone who needs it"
    },
    {
        "question": "step in",
        "options": [
            "depart furtively",
            "when a sports team plays away, it plays at an opponent\u2019s ground, ...",
            "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop",
            "calculate how expensive some work is going to be"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "step on",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone badly, especially because they have less power or importance than you",
            "enjoy yourself noisily and exuberantly",
            "to gradually prepare yourself or someone else for something that you are going to say or do",
            "confront, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone badly, especially because they have less power or importance than you"
    },
    {
        "question": "step on it",
        "options": [
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "an imperative used to tell someone to go faster, especially when driving",
            "to keep attacking someone or something, ...",
            "to attack someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "an imperative used to tell someone to go faster, especially when driving"
    },
    {
        "question": "step out",
        "options": [
            "to say a list of things quickly and without much effort",
            "to leave a place for a short time",
            "to be a person or company that hides an illegal or secret activity for another person or organization",
            "to cover a hole or surface with plaster"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place for a short time"
    },
    {
        "question": "step to",
        "options": [
            "to call someone by telephone, ...",
            "to spend time experiencing and enjoying the mood or feeling in a place, ...",
            "fall in large numbers",
            "confront, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "confront, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "step up",
        "options": [
            "to serve food, ...",
            "in science fiction stories, to send someone down onto a planet from a spacecraft using special electronic equipment",
            "to hit someone hard in the face, ...",
            "to increase something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to increase something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick around",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to remain in a place for longer than you originally intended, especially in order to wait for something to happen",
            "same as camp, ...",
            "if you roll a car window down, you turn a handle or push a button so that the window goes down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remain in a place for longer than you originally intended, especially in order to wait for something to happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick at",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in something that other people are doing that is fun or interesting, or that makes money",
            "to take the total of a column of numbers from the bottom of one page to the top of the next, ...",
            "to behave in a noisy silly way, ...",
            "to continue to work at something difficult or unpleasant in a determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to work at something difficult or unpleasant in a determined way"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick by",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone from speaking or being heard by shouting loudly and angrily",
            "go to someone",
            "to pay money that you owe, especially when you are unwilling to pay",
            "to continue to support someone who is in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to support someone who is in a difficult situation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick down",
        "options": [
            "same as put about",
            "to write something quickly and without taking much care",
            "to intend to do something, or to expect something to happen",
            "same as heave"
        ],
        "answer": "to write something quickly and without taking much care"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick it to",
        "options": [
            "criticise someone, ...",
            "to beat an opponent very easily, ...",
            "to criticize someone regularly or for a long time",
            "to take air into your lungs through your nose or mouth, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "criticise someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick on",
        "options": [
            "to become connected or involved with someone or something and get some benefit from them, ...",
            "to consider or express something in a different way, ...",
            "to say that someone is responsible for something bad",
            "to behave in a stupid way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to say that someone is responsible for something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick out",
        "options": [
            "to waste time doing silly or unimportant things",
            "same as put about",
            "to be very obvious or noticeable, ...",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to be very obvious or noticeable, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick out for",
        "options": [
            "fairly old, ...",
            "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance",
            "same as trip, ...",
            "to be determined to get what you want or need, and not be willing to accept anything less"
        ],
        "answer": "to be determined to get what you want or need, and not be willing to accept anything less"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick to",
        "options": [
            "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ...",
            "to breathe in smoke from a cigarette, ...",
            "to start doing something by chance, ...",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk or write about one particular thing only, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick together",
        "options": [
            "same as separate",
            "to not approve of an activity or action",
            "be friendly and spend time with someone",
            "if people stick together, they remain close together and support one another"
        ],
        "answer": "if people stick together, they remain close together and support one another"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick up",
        "options": [
            "to raise something upwards, especially your arm or hand, ...",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly",
            "persuade, ...",
            "to give something to someone officially and formally"
        ],
        "answer": "to raise something upwards, especially your arm or hand, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stick up for",
        "options": [
            "to speak in support of a person or an idea, belief, or plan, especially when no one else will",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to write on a list that someone agrees to give or take something, ...",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it"
        ],
        "answer": "to speak in support of a person or an idea, belief, or plan, especially when no one else will"
    },
    {
        "question": "stick with",
        "options": [
            "to start to think only about yourself and your own problems and to forget about other people and their problems",
            "boost, increase or exaggerate",
            "to continue to do or use something, and not change it, ...",
            "to rain in large amounts and with a lot of force"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to do or use something, and not change it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stiffen up",
        "options": [
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "become rigid, ...",
            "to move along slowly and in a relaxed way, especially in a car",
            "to watch someone while they are doing something, usually in order to make sure that they are doing it correctly"
        ],
        "answer": "become rigid, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stink out",
        "options": [
            "to make a place smell very unpleasant",
            "to become covered with ice",
            "to treat someone in a cruel way over a long period and gradually destroy their confidence or strength",
            "to make a person or animal fatter"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a place smell very unpleasant"
    },
    {
        "question": "stir in",
        "options": [
            "to spend time with someone",
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "to have just enough of something such as money or knowledge so that you can do what you need to do",
            "to add something to a liquid or substance and mix it"
        ],
        "answer": "to add something to a liquid or substance and mix it"
    },
    {
        "question": "stir into",
        "options": [
            "if something centres around a place, or if you centre something around it, it happens mainly there, ...",
            "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ...",
            "to hit your hands together at the same speed and beat as a piece of music or poetry",
            "to force someone to leave a place or an organization"
        ],
        "answer": "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stir up",
        "options": [
            "same as stir, ...",
            "to make someone go somewhere, especially in order to get rid of them",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other",
            "permanently to leave the house or flat where you live or the place where you have your business"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stir, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stitch up",
        "options": [
            "to call someone by telephone, ...",
            "revise",
            "to arrange an agreement or deal, ...",
            "to make someone learn or understand something by telling them about it many times"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange an agreement or deal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stock up",
        "options": [
            "same as stock",
            "to suddenly notice or think of something",
            "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stock"
    },
    {
        "question": "stomp off",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere angrily",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing, ...",
            "to be opposed to a plan or suggestion for a particular reason, ...",
            "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "stomp on",
        "options": [
            "treat badly or defeat",
            "same as tune, ...",
            "to express your thoughts or feelings through your words or behaviour, ...",
            "clog or overwhelm"
        ],
        "answer": "treat badly or defeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "stoop down",
        "options": [
            "same as stoop",
            "to start using a computer system, for example by typing a particular word",
            "to make a determined attempt to stop people doing something bad or illegal",
            "to have a tooth removed from your mouth or an organ removed from your body, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as stoop"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop around",
        "options": [
            "visit someone for a short time.",
            "to invest a lot of money in something in order to improve it or make it successful, ...",
            "to make yourself comfortable in a chair",
            "to come from a particular place, family, or situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "visit someone for a short time."
    },
    {
        "question": "stop away",
        "options": [
            "to avoid going to a place",
            "sleep somewhere for the night",
            "to discuss something in order to make a decision",
            "to treat someone in a cruel way over a long period and gradually destroy their confidence or strength"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid going to a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop back",
        "options": [
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "return somewhere",
            "have sex with",
            "organise or arrange something for a particular purpose, audience, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "return somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop behind",
        "options": [
            "have sex",
            "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ...",
            "stay somewhere when other people leave",
            "to bring someone into a team or group of people in order to help them do something"
        ],
        "answer": "stay somewhere when other people leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop by",
        "options": [
            "to stand in front of people who have been waiting longer than you, in a way that is unfair",
            "same as light, ...",
            "if someone sitting down scoots over, they move to a different position, for example to make space for someone else to sit down",
            "same as stop"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop in",
        "options": [
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to make someone feel very enthusiastic",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "to stay at home"
        ],
        "answer": "to stay at home"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop off",
        "options": [
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "to visit somewhere before continuing to another place",
            "to feel that you can understand and share someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to think that something is the right thing to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to visit somewhere before continuing to another place"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop on",
        "options": [
            "to heat a metal until it becomes liquid, especially in order to make something new from it",
            "to wait for a difficult situation to end, ...",
            "to remain at a place longer than you had intended to",
            "to begin to notice something, or to make someone begin to notice something, especially danger"
        ],
        "answer": "to remain at a place longer than you had intended to"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop out",
        "options": [
            "to not come home at night",
            "to put money into your bank account, ...",
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "same as pile, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not come home at night"
    },
    {
        "question": "stop over",
        "options": [
            "approach someone without their knowing",
            "forward a film or tape to a certain point",
            "same as stop, ...",
            "used for saying that you strongly agree with what someone has said, or strongly hope that it is true, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as stop, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stop up",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "to make a simple copy of something that you will later make or do properly, in order to test it or show people what it will be like",
            "to manage to remember something that you learned or knew long ago, ...",
            "to have sex with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "store away",
        "options": [
            "to put something in a safe place until you need it",
            "include someone or something in a group, category, etc",
            "to become firmly attached to something, ...",
            "to prepare someone for something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put something in a safe place until you need it"
    },
    {
        "question": "store up",
        "options": [
            "to do something that will cause problems in the future, ...",
            "to join together with someone else in order to do something such as start a business",
            "to talk too much, ...",
            "same as pass, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something that will cause problems in the future, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "storm off",
        "options": [
            "leave a place angrily",
            "to continue without changing, in a way that is not interesting or exciting",
            "same as touch",
            "to be very happy about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "storm out",
        "options": [
            "to expect something to happen and plan for it",
            "same as border, ...",
            "to succeed after great difficulty",
            "leave a place angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "leave a place angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "stow away",
        "options": [
            "same as stow, ...",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place",
            "to prevent someone from taking part in something",
            "surrender to the police or authorities"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stow, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "straighten out",
        "options": [
            "same as straighten, ...",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other",
            "an extremely offensive expression that means to waste someone else\u2019s time or treat them in a bad way, ...",
            "same as border, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as straighten, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "straighten up",
        "options": [
            "to stand up straight, ...",
            "become involved even though there is opposition to your involvement",
            "to decide not to do something because you are frightened or not confident",
            "to put clothes on"
        ],
        "answer": "to stand up straight, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stretch out",
        "options": [
            "same as stretch, ...",
            "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit",
            "to start to do something in a different way, ...",
            "if something dries off, or if you dry it off, all the water dries or is wiped from its surface"
        ],
        "answer": "same as stretch, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stretch to",
        "options": [
            "be recognised as important, worthwhile or valuable",
            "same as box",
            "to look or behave like an older relative",
            "to no longer be reasonable, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to no longer be reasonable, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "stretcher off",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place suddenly, ...",
            "to chase someone or something, ...",
            "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc.",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug"
        ],
        "answer": "carry an injured player off the pitch, field, etc."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike at",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them",
            "to buy a large quantity of something",
            "to try to hit someone or something with your hand or a weapon, ...",
            "to have sex with a lot of different people, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to hit someone or something with your hand or a weapon, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike back",
        "options": [
            "to ask someone for something, especially money",
            "get so emotional that you lose control",
            "to attack, harm, or criticize someone who has attacked, harmed, or criticized you, ...",
            "to make it seem that someone is guilty of a crime when they are not, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to attack, harm, or criticize someone who has attacked, harmed, or criticized you, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike down",
        "options": [
            "same as stop",
            "to leave a place suddenly, ...",
            "to go to bed at night, ...",
            "to hit someone with enough force to make them fall down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to hit someone with enough force to make them fall down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike off",
        "options": [
            "to remove something from a list or record, ...",
            "to criticize or punish someone severely",
            "if a situation is looking up, it is getting better, ...",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something from a list or record, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike on",
        "options": [
            "to continue at around the same level, rising and falling only slightly",
            "if you are struck on someone or something, you like them, ...",
            "accuse somebody of a crime",
            "keep afloat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if you are struck on someone or something, you like them, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike out",
        "options": [
            "keep afloat, ...",
            "to stop the continuation of a court case, ...",
            "to waste time doing things that are not important or necessary",
            "same as throw away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop the continuation of a court case, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike up",
        "options": [
            "sleep, take a nap",
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ...",
            "to start to play or sing a piece of music, ...",
            "to be covered in insects, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to play or sing a piece of music, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strike upon",
        "options": [
            "to look at someone or something so that you are certain they are safe, satisfactory etc",
            "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract",
            "to enclose someone or something and prevent them from moving or leaving, ...",
            "same as strike on"
        ],
        "answer": "same as strike on"
    },
    {
        "question": "string along",
        "options": [
            "to buy and sell something, ...",
            "to keep something so that it can be used or taken away later, ...",
            "become calm or regain control of your emotions",
            "to agree with or go along with an idea or suggestion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to agree with or go along with an idea or suggestion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "string out",
        "options": [
            "to arrange something in a long line, ...",
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to physically attack someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange something in a long line, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "string together",
        "options": [
            "to arrange a group of things into a series",
            "look in different places for something",
            "to shout offensive words at someone because you are annoyed with them",
            "to accept something unpleasant that you cannot change, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to arrange a group of things into a series"
    },
    {
        "question": "string up",
        "options": [
            "to kill someone by hanging them",
            "to add something to a liquid or substance and mix it",
            "to refuse to accept or to use something any longer",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen"
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone by hanging them"
    },
    {
        "question": "strip away",
        "options": [
            "to remove something that covers something, ...",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ...",
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "break the surface of soil"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove something that covers something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strip down",
        "options": [
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "to stand somewhere and do nothing, often when you should be doing something",
            "to leave one place and move to another",
            "to remove all or most of your clothes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove all or most of your clothes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strip down to",
        "options": [
            "to hurt someone by hitting them a lot of times",
            "to reduce an amount of money by using it",
            "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to",
            "to remove all or most of your clothes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to remove all or most of your clothes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strip of",
        "options": [
            "to change to a new system or way of behaving, ...",
            "to operate steadily but not very well, ...",
            "remove a title, award or position",
            "to hurt someone by hitting or kicking them many times"
        ],
        "answer": "remove a title, award or position"
    },
    {
        "question": "strip off",
        "options": [
            "to fill something with air using a pump, ...",
            "to start something such as an explanation, project, or attack with a lot of enthusiasm",
            "to stand up straight, ...",
            "to take off all your clothes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take off all your clothes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strip out",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop",
            "remove, ...",
            "same as bundle, ...",
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter"
        ],
        "answer": "remove, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "strip to",
        "options": [
            "to take clothes off",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "confess, admit reluctantly to something",
            "remove clothing to a certain level"
        ],
        "answer": "remove clothing to a certain level"
    },
    {
        "question": "stub out",
        "options": [
            "to kill yourself, ...",
            "sleep away from your home, often without planning to",
            "to ask or tell someone many times about something in a way that they do not like",
            "to press a cigarette hard against a surface to make it stop burning"
        ],
        "answer": "to press a cigarette hard against a surface to make it stop burning"
    },
    {
        "question": "stuff up",
        "options": [
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil",
            "to shout something, especially when you are surprised or worried, ...",
            "to become quieter, weaker, or smaller",
            "have a good time when intoxicated"
        ],
        "answer": "make a mistake, do badly, spoil"
    },
    {
        "question": "stumble across",
        "options": [
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "to play a message or film that has been recorded in order to listen to or watch it",
            "to buy tickets for someone for a specific journey on a plane, train, or bus",
            "to be similar to something from the past, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
    },
    {
        "question": "stumble into",
        "options": [
            "criticise harshly or punish someone for something",
            "to stay at home",
            "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine",
            "to become involved in something by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in something by accident"
    },
    {
        "question": "stumble upon",
        "options": [
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "to be good enough, ...",
            "same as pen, ...",
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
    },
    {
        "question": "stump up",
        "options": [
            "to give money, often without wanting to give it",
            "same as polish",
            "to move from a sitting position into a position in which you are lying flat on a surface",
            "to cover an area of ground with grass"
        ],
        "answer": "to give money, often without wanting to give it"
    },
    {
        "question": "style after",
        "options": [
            "used as a polite way of asking someone to be patient while you do or finish something",
            "to copy someone or something\u2019s style",
            "ask how someone is doing, especially professionally and in terms of health",
            "to take care of someone and make sure that they are treated well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to copy someone or something\u2019s style"
    },
    {
        "question": "subscribe for",
        "options": [
            "to be correct, suitable, or sensible in relation to something else",
            "to apply to buy shares in a company",
            "to get very near someone before they notice you, ...",
            "same as hang"
        ],
        "answer": "to apply to buy shares in a company"
    },
    {
        "question": "subscribe to",
        "options": [
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing, ...",
            "same as get on, ...",
            "to agree with an idea",
            "same as balance"
        ],
        "answer": "to agree with an idea"
    },
    {
        "question": "suck in",
        "options": [
            "to be as good as what was expected or promised",
            "to make a particular aim or idea the main part of something",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "to try to make someone or something leave a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "suck into",
        "options": [
            "to waste time when you should be working",
            "to pretend to be a particular person or type of person in order to trick people",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad",
            "to give someone or something the same name as someone or something else, especially the same first name as a member of your family"
        ],
        "answer": "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "suck off",
        "options": [
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something",
            "same as lighten, ...",
            "to perform oral sex on a man",
            "to go to sleep"
        ],
        "answer": "to perform oral sex on a man"
    },
    {
        "question": "suck up",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "to prevent you from doing or getting something, ...",
            "win easily",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well"
        ],
        "answer": "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well"
    },
    {
        "question": "suck up to",
        "options": [
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well",
            "to play a tune very loudly, especially on the piano"
        ],
        "answer": "to be very nice to someone in authority so that they will treat you well"
    },
    {
        "question": "suit up",
        "options": [
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "get someone to help or become involved, usually when they don't want to",
            "to get ready for an activity by putting on a uniform or special clothes"
        ],
        "answer": "to get ready for an activity by putting on a uniform or special clothes"
    },
    {
        "question": "sum up",
        "options": [
            "to stay in bed in the morning for longer than usual",
            "to continue for longer than you want or think is necessary",
            "same as double, ...",
            "to give a summary of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give a summary of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "summon up",
        "options": [
            "to sleep at someone else\u2019s house for one night",
            "to avoid doing something that you were intending to do or had promised to do",
            "reconcile different positions",
            "get the energy or courage to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "get the energy or courage to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sup up",
        "options": [
            "to mention something unpleasant that happened in the past and that someone else does not want to talk about",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "to finish drinking something",
            "to start having a conversation with someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to finish drinking something"
    },
    {
        "question": "suss out",
        "options": [
            "persuade someone",
            "come to understand",
            "make something sticky",
            "same as blot"
        ],
        "answer": "come to understand"
    },
    {
        "question": "swallow up",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "to take control of a smaller company or country, ...",
            "to start doing something immediately, ...",
            "to point a weapon at someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to take control of a smaller company or country, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "swan about",
        "options": [
            "same as hike, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ...",
            "to add more details about something in order to make it easier to understand or imagine"
        ],
        "answer": "move in a dramatic or affected manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "swan around",
        "options": [
            "to inform someone about something, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "if you beaver away at something, you work very hard at it",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "move in a dramatic or affected manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "swan in",
        "options": [
            "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more",
            "to pull very strongly at something",
            "to remove one part of something",
            "enter in a dramatic or attention-seeking manner"
        ],
        "answer": "enter in a dramatic or attention-seeking manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "swan off",
        "options": [
            "exploit, use to your advantage",
            "think about something",
            "to move a plant into a larger container because it has grown bigger",
            "leave somewhere in a defiant or pompous manner"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere in a defiant or pompous manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "swarm with",
        "options": [
            "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them",
            "if time or an opportunity slips by, it passes and you fail to use it or to gain an advantage from it",
            "to cover a hole or surface with plaster",
            "to measure a distance by counting the number of steps that you need to walk from one end of something to the other"
        ],
        "answer": "if a place is swarming with people, insects, or animals, it is full of them"
    },
    {
        "question": "swear by",
        "options": [
            "to believe that something is effective",
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually",
            "same as stand",
            "to not tell someone something"
        ],
        "answer": "to believe that something is effective"
    },
    {
        "question": "swear down",
        "options": [
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "to get into a place or something such as a car, especially in large numbers or in a way that is not organized",
            "promise that something is true",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "promise that something is true"
    },
    {
        "question": "swear in",
        "options": [
            "become involved in something despite opposition to your involvement",
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "mistreat physically",
            "to make someone give a formal promise in a law court or at an official ceremony"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone give a formal promise in a law court or at an official ceremony"
    },
    {
        "question": "swear off",
        "options": [
            "to start driving in a higher gear",
            "to go with someone who does not want to be with you, ...",
            "to promise to stop doing or using something",
            "to send someone to a court of law because they have been accused of a crime"
        ],
        "answer": "to promise to stop doing or using something"
    },
    {
        "question": "swear to",
        "options": [
            "if a thought or idea occurs to you, you suddenly and unexpectedly start to think about it",
            "to be completely certain of something",
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "invent, maker up, improvise, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be completely certain of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweat off",
        "options": [
            "something that makes you feel very disappointed or upset, especially when you have been trying hard to achieve something",
            "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ...",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep along",
        "options": [
            "return quickly",
            "to stop doing something, especially a job or a course of study, ...",
            "if something sweeps you along, you become very involved in it because you are so excited about it",
            "to continue trying to achieve something despite opposition or difficulties"
        ],
        "answer": "if something sweeps you along, you become very involved in it because you are so excited about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep aside",
        "options": [
            "to get something, especially something that is hard to get",
            "to mix something into a liquid or substance, ...",
            "to ignore someone or something, or to refuse to consider them",
            "expel"
        ],
        "answer": "to ignore someone or something, or to refuse to consider them"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep away",
        "options": [
            "visit",
            "if money is sloshing around, a lot of it is available or people are spending a lot of it",
            "to destroy or to completely remove something, ...",
            "leave a place in a hurry"
        ],
        "answer": "to destroy or to completely remove something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep back",
        "options": [
            "to make someone or something different and special, ...",
            "to put your hair into a style that keeps it away from your face",
            "same as tone",
            "do something out of a car"
        ],
        "answer": "to put your hair into a style that keeps it away from your face"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep over",
        "options": [
            "to suddenly affect someone very strongly",
            "to be wearing particular clothes, shoes etc, ...",
            "to hold something so that someone else can reach it or see it, ...",
            "to start to deal with someone or something in a brave and determined way"
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly affect someone very strongly"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep through",
        "options": [
            "same as get around",
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use",
            "to win something easily, ...",
            "to finish drinking something"
        ],
        "answer": "to win something easily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "sweep up",
        "options": [
            "to organize data (=computer information) according to different levels of detail, each level more detailed than the previous one",
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to clean and remove dirt, glass, dust etc from a floor or the ground using a brush or broom",
            "to reduce a price or amount, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to clean and remove dirt, glass, dust etc from a floor or the ground using a brush or broom"
    },
    {
        "question": "sweeten up",
        "options": [
            "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to",
            "to write down information or a statement, ...",
            "sell something in an auction",
            "surprise or shock"
        ],
        "answer": "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to"
    },
    {
        "question": "swell up",
        "options": [
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ...",
            "to shout something",
            "same as swell",
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure"
        ],
        "answer": "same as swell"
    },
    {
        "question": "swing around",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else",
            "turn around quickly, ...",
            "to separate two people or animals that are fighting",
            "to kill yourself, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "turn around quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "swing at",
        "options": [
            "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ...",
            "target, focus on (sport)",
            "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad",
            "leave a group by moving in a different direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "swing by",
        "options": [
            "to make a short visit to a person or place",
            "to not tell someone something, ...",
            "support",
            "to pay money to your business partner so that you can control all of a business you previously owned together, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a short visit to a person or place"
    },
    {
        "question": "swing round",
        "options": [
            "turn around quickly, ...",
            "to be about something, or to be connected with something, ...",
            "to find a husband or wife for someone",
            "to avoid becoming involved in something"
        ],
        "answer": "turn around quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "swing through",
        "options": [
            "to give someone more food than usual in order to make them stronger or less thin",
            "to have a lot of something",
            "to visit a place for a short time on your way to another place",
            "to be the result of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to visit a place for a short time on your way to another place"
    },
    {
        "question": "switch off",
        "options": [
            "spoil or ruin something",
            "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ...",
            "to gradually get closer to someone or something that you are trying to catch",
            "to start a new sexual relationship with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop listening to someone, or to stop thinking about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "switch on",
        "options": [
            "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you",
            "to make a particular aim or idea the main part of something",
            "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ...",
            "if you switch on something such as a light or a machine, or if it switches on, you make it start working"
        ],
        "answer": "if you switch on something such as a light or a machine, or if it switches on, you make it start working"
    },
    {
        "question": "switch over",
        "options": [
            "to think about something that happened in the past",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to realize or remember something",
            "to stop doing one thing and start doing another, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop doing one thing and start doing another, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "swot up",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to leave, ...",
            "to study something very hard, especially for an examination",
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "to begin, or to begin something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to study something very hard, especially for an examination"
    },
    {
        "question": "syphon off",
        "options": [
            "divert money illegally, ...",
            "same as goof",
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed",
            "to not go onto a particular area of land, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "divert money illegally, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tack on",
        "options": [
            "to be the main reason for something or the most basic part of something",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "to upset or frighten someone by shocking or surprising them, ...",
            "same as pen"
        ],
        "answer": "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest"
    },
    {
        "question": "tack onto",
        "options": [
            "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something",
            "to not approve of something, ...",
            "to go away, ...",
            "become nervous, tense or unable to relax"
        ],
        "answer": "add or attach something that wasn't planned to something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tag along",
        "options": [
            "to go somewhere with someone else although you are not needed",
            "same as step",
            "to become calm after being excited or angry",
            "to annoy someone or make them disappointed"
        ],
        "answer": "to go somewhere with someone else although you are not needed"
    },
    {
        "question": "tag on",
        "options": [
            "persuade someone",
            "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest",
            "become controlled",
            "to continue for longer than you want or think is necessary"
        ],
        "answer": "to add something extra, especially something that does not seem to belong to the rest"
    },
    {
        "question": "tag onto",
        "options": [
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it",
            "to succeed in winning or gaining something from an opponent, ...",
            "add an additional point to something written or spoken",
            "to try in a determined way to achieve something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "add an additional point to something written or spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "tag with",
        "options": [
            "to make a horse stop or go more slowly by pulling its reins, ...",
            "to try hard to develop or improve something",
            "to travel by plane, ...",
            "add a keyword link or bookmark to a blog entry or webpage"
        ],
        "answer": "add a keyword link or bookmark to a blog entry or webpage"
    },
    {
        "question": "tail away",
        "options": [
            "to become familiar with a new way of life, place, or job, or to make someone do this, ...",
            "like something",
            "same as tail off",
            "to avoid mentioning something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as tail off"
    },
    {
        "question": "tail back",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ...",
            "to spend time experiencing and enjoying the mood or feeling in a place, ...",
            "to fasten something, ...",
            "to form a long line of traffic that is not moving"
        ],
        "answer": "to form a long line of traffic that is not moving"
    },
    {
        "question": "tail off",
        "options": [
            "same as border, ...",
            "to be owned by someone, ...",
            "to become quieter, weaker, or smaller",
            "look for something hurriedly"
        ],
        "answer": "to become quieter, weaker, or smaller"
    },
    {
        "question": "take aback",
        "options": [
            "surprise or shock",
            "same as drop",
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to offer something to someone to study, discuss, approve etc"
        ],
        "answer": "surprise or shock"
    },
    {
        "question": "take after",
        "options": [
            "to leave somewhere quietly or secretly, especially in order to avoid being noticed",
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something",
            "same as call on",
            "to look or behave like an older relative"
        ],
        "answer": "to look or behave like an older relative"
    },
    {
        "question": "take against",
        "options": [
            "to become ill with a particular illness",
            "to begin to dislike someone, often without having a good reason",
            "if someone with power or influence railroads something through, they make someone else accept it, although they do not really want to",
            "same as snarl"
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to dislike someone, often without having a good reason"
    },
    {
        "question": "take apart",
        "options": [
            "to make something fall down and break into pieces by hitting it very hard",
            "to say something quickly, especially something that you have learned by memory",
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you",
            "to separate an object into pieces, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to separate an object into pieces, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take aside",
        "options": [
            "to discuss something until you find a solution or reach an agreement",
            "to move through something with a lot of difficulty, ...",
            "to listen to someone until they have finished speaking, without interrupting them",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen"
        ],
        "answer": "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen"
    },
    {
        "question": "take away",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the positive effect or success of something",
            "vomit",
            "if the amount, level, or value of something falls off, it gets smaller",
            "to measure a particular length, width, height etc, often at a point where something is to be cut"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the positive effect or success of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "take away from",
        "options": [
            "to increase and become more obvious",
            "used to tell someone to go away because they're annoying you",
            "to reduce the positive effect or success of something",
            "to tell someone about something in a way that makes them think it is unimportant, so that they do not ask questions about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the positive effect or success of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "take back",
        "options": [
            "to take a particular amount of time, or to last for a particular amount of time",
            "to say unkind things about someone when they are not there, ...",
            "to remind someone of something in the past, ...",
            "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried"
        ],
        "answer": "to remind someone of something in the past, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take down",
        "options": [
            "to write down information or a statement, ...",
            "to take control of a smaller company or country, ...",
            "to increase or improve something, or to make it more interesting",
            "to tell someone something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write down information or a statement, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take for",
        "options": [
            "focus more closely",
            "to give information, reasons, or a list of things that you have given many times before",
            "to believe something, usually wrongly, about someone or something",
            "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance"
        ],
        "answer": "to believe something, usually wrongly, about someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "take in",
        "options": [
            "same as rain",
            "to be as good as someone or something, ...",
            "same as invite",
            "to include something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to include something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take it",
        "options": [
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something",
            "to stop thinking or believing something, ...",
            "visit a place to check something",
            "accept criticism"
        ],
        "answer": "accept criticism"
    },
    {
        "question": "take it out on",
        "options": [
            "produce or issue, usually from a machine",
            "to score a particular amount very quickly in a game or competition",
            "abuse someone because you're angry",
            "to manage to say something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "abuse someone because you're angry"
    },
    {
        "question": "take it upon yourself",
        "options": [
            "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are",
            "take responsibility, often without consulting other people",
            "to reduce the level of tension or intensity in a situation, ...",
            "stop paying attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "take responsibility, often without consulting other people"
    },
    {
        "question": "take off",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place suddenly, ...",
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it",
            "same as truss, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place suddenly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take on",
        "options": [
            "to count and check all the money that a shop has received in a day",
            "to start to employ someone, ...",
            "fight or argue",
            "to be given to someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to employ someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take out",
        "options": [
            "to make something last for a long time, usually longer than is good or necessary",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble",
            "to leave, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take over",
        "options": [
            "to be dressed in a particular way, ...",
            "to take control of something, ...",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way",
            "keep something near you"
        ],
        "answer": "to take control of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take through",
        "options": [
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended",
            "to try to find out someone\u2019s opinions, ideas, feelings etc by talking to them",
            "to explain to someone in detail how something should be done, what something is about etc",
            "to use something as a model for a film, piece of writing, or work of art, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to explain to someone in detail how something should be done, what something is about etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "take to",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone physically, ...",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ...",
            "to start doing something as a habit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start doing something as a habit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take up",
        "options": [
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to start living somewhere, ...",
            "to make something continue for longer than necessary",
            "face (of a building)"
        ],
        "answer": "to start living somewhere, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take up on",
        "options": [
            "said when you can't wait for something nice in the future",
            "increase sharply",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made"
    },
    {
        "question": "take up with",
        "options": [
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ...",
            "to begin talking in a boring or annoying way, usually complaining or criticizing someone or something",
            "to try hard to develop or improve something",
            "to turn and face in the opposite direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "take upon",
        "options": [
            "to do something without first thinking carefully about it",
            "to find something bad or illegal and get rid of it",
            "same as take on",
            "to lose weight, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as take on"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk around",
        "options": [
            "to work hard and in a determined way over a long period of time, often on something that is boring or difficult",
            "boost, increase or exaggerate",
            "to delay the progress of someone or something, ...",
            "persuade, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "persuade, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "talk at",
        "options": [
            "to stop yourself from saying what you think, ...",
            "to rain very hard",
            "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk a lot without letting anyone else say anything"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk away",
        "options": [
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ...",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things",
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question",
            "to continue to talk for a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue to talk for a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk back",
        "options": [
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ...",
            "to reach a particular amount, ...",
            "same as join, ...",
            "to reply quickly and often rudely to something that someone says. This expression is used especially to describe children being rude to their parents"
        ],
        "answer": "to reply quickly and often rudely to something that someone says. This expression is used especially to describe children being rude to their parents"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk down",
        "options": [
            "to reduce the speed of a vehicle by reducing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "to persuade someone to lower the price of something, ...",
            "to persuade someone to tell you a secret, with difficulty",
            "get into trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to lower the price of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "talk down to",
        "options": [
            "open an advertisement on the internet",
            "to be connected with something or to influence it",
            "to work with other people in order to help someone in a difficult situation",
            "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk to someone as if you think they are not as clever or important as you are"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk into",
        "options": [
            "to be related to a person or animal that lived long ago, ...",
            "same as stoop",
            "treat someone badly",
            "persuade someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "persuade someone to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk out",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as a piece of writing shorter by giving only the basic, most important facts, ...",
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you",
            "if someone\u2019s eyes bore into you, they look at you very hard and this makes you feel nervous",
            "to discuss a problem thoroughly with someone who disagrees with you about it"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss a problem thoroughly with someone who disagrees with you about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk out of",
        "options": [
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination",
            "persuade someone not to do something",
            "reconcile different positions",
            "if time goes by, it passes, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "persuade someone not to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk over",
        "options": [
            "to search through a collection of things in order to find something",
            "be bored, upset or sick of something",
            "leave a place in a hurry",
            "to discuss a problem or a plan"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss a problem or a plan"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk round",
        "options": [
            "accept something less satisfactory because there's no alternative",
            "same as beat up",
            "repeatedly criticise someone verbally",
            "to succeed in persuading someone to agree to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed in persuading someone to agree to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "talk through",
        "options": [
            "to remain at a job, school, or place for longer than you had intended to",
            "to discuss a plan or a situation in a detailed way, ...",
            "same as split, ...",
            "to have everything that you need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss a plan or a situation in a detailed way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "talk to",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone that they have done something wrong and that you are angry or dissatisfied about it",
            "to switch a computer off in the correct way",
            "to attack and cut someone with a knife, ...",
            "to feel that you are strong or healthy enough to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone that they have done something wrong and that you are angry or dissatisfied about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk up",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone to be quiet, ...",
            "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are",
            "to move smoothly, ...",
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are"
    },
    {
        "question": "talk yourself out",
        "options": [
            "same as catch, ...",
            "to treat someone in an unkind and unfair way, ...",
            "talk until you have nothing left to say",
            "same as mail"
        ],
        "answer": "talk until you have nothing left to say"
    },
    {
        "question": "tally up",
        "options": [
            "same as tally",
            "to give something to each member of a group, ...",
            "to finish drinking something",
            "to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tally"
    },
    {
        "question": "tangle up",
        "options": [
            "to do something without first thinking carefully about it",
            "same as tangle",
            "to let someone else have your job or position, ...",
            "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tangle"
    },
    {
        "question": "tangle with",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something when you would prefer to stop",
            "to become involved in a fight or an argument with someone",
            "to be the result of something, ...",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in a fight or an argument with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "tank up",
        "options": [
            "if two people sleep together, they have sex, especially when they are not married",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident",
            "to fill a vehicle with petrol",
            "same as curl, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fill a vehicle with petrol"
    },
    {
        "question": "tap for",
        "options": [
            "to not consider something because you want to consider something else instead",
            "to make something less strong, powerful, or confident, ...",
            "get money off someone",
            "if a good feeling or quality shines through, it is very noticeable"
        ],
        "answer": "get money off someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "tap into",
        "options": [
            "sleep on something other than a bed",
            "to talk quickly and for a long time",
            "to find a criminal and take them to a police station.",
            "same as tap, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as tap, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tap off with",
        "options": [
            "to aim at something and move quickly and directly to it, ...",
            "have sex with",
            "to stop hoping that you will find someone alive and stop looking for them, ...",
            "if a group dies off, the members die one by one until none exist"
        ],
        "answer": "have sex with"
    },
    {
        "question": "tap out",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in keeping a job, ...",
            "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ...",
            "if an idea is floating around, it has been suggested but not yet considered, ...",
            "to interrupt someone who is speaking, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to create a particular pattern of sounds by hitting a surface gently with your fingers, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tap up",
        "options": [
            "persuade someone to do something",
            "to put money into your bank account, ...",
            "to make something seem more impressive than it really is, ...",
            "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours"
        ],
        "answer": "to make an informal approach to a footballer who is contracted to another team to try and persuade them to come and play for yours"
    },
    {
        "question": "tape up",
        "options": [
            "to obey a rule, law, agreement etc, ...",
            "same as tape",
            "to remove something by cutting, especially a part of someone\u2019s body",
            "to try to take hold of something in a rough or rude way"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tape"
    },
    {
        "question": "taper off",
        "options": [
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away",
            "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping",
            "behave in a silly way",
            "to make someone leave a place, their job, or something that they are involved in"
        ],
        "answer": "gradually become smaller or weaker until stopping"
    },
    {
        "question": "tax with",
        "options": [
            "same as finish, ...",
            "enter in a dramatic or attention-seeking manner",
            "to order someone to do something, ...",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to order someone to do something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "team up",
        "options": [
            "work with someone or a group to achieve something",
            "leave the top deck of a ship",
            "if a sound or picture fades out, or if you fade it out, it gradually disappears",
            "clock in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "work with someone or a group to achieve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tear apart",
        "options": [
            "to produce a series of quick loud noises or words",
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "to give something to a person in authority, ...",
            "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone or something very strongly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tear at",
        "options": [
            "to drink something, usually alcohol, quickly, swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to pull very strongly at something",
            "to be covered in insects, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pull very strongly at something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tear away",
        "options": [
            "to send someone to prison, ...",
            "force someone out of a place, job, position, etc.",
            "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something",
            "if you are struck on someone or something, you like them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force yourself or someone else to leave or to stop doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tear down",
        "options": [
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure",
            "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death",
            "to cost a particular amount",
            "to be careful"
        ],
        "answer": "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure"
    },
    {
        "question": "tear into",
        "options": [
            "to remain out of your home for a period of time",
            "used for telling someone to leave, ...",
            "to physically attack someone or something, ...",
            "to lead someone into a room where they are going to meet other people"
        ],
        "answer": "to physically attack someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tear off",
        "options": [
            "to check something carefully, ...",
            "to make something sound more interesting or impressive than it is",
            "to connect one thing to another thing, for example as a way of understanding its meaning or structure",
            "to write something quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write something quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tear out",
        "options": [
            "depart rapidly",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to belong to a particular group or class, ...",
            "to joke about something in order to show that you think it is not important or serious"
        ],
        "answer": "depart rapidly"
    },
    {
        "question": "tear up",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in a situation very quickly, ...",
            "behave stupidly or waste time",
            "to make someone feel very unhappy or upset, ...",
            "to take control of something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel very unhappy or upset, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tease out",
        "options": [
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen",
            "to move a plant into a larger container because it has grown bigger",
            "to start behaving in a bad way",
            "same as tease, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as tease, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tee off",
        "options": [
            "progress",
            "to make someone unconscious before a medical operation by giving them a drug",
            "if someone or something blends in, they are similar to the other people, objects, buildings etc around them, and so they seem appropriate or you do not notice them",
            "to start a new activity, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start a new activity, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tee off on",
        "options": [
            "to achieve a particular level or number, ...",
            "if something or someone grows on you, you start to like them more",
            "criticise",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing"
        ],
        "answer": "criticise"
    },
    {
        "question": "tee up",
        "options": [
            "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ...",
            "to put a ball on a tee",
            "to draw a line through written words",
            "to become stronger or more successful than another group so that they fail or can no longer compete with you"
        ],
        "answer": "to put a ball on a tee"
    },
    {
        "question": "teem with",
        "options": [
            "to contain an extremely large number of people, animals, or objects that are all moving around",
            "to be in a position of power while important changes or events are happening",
            "to make a place clean and tidy, especially after someone else has used it",
            "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to"
        ],
        "answer": "to contain an extremely large number of people, animals, or objects that are all moving around"
    },
    {
        "question": "tell against",
        "options": [
            "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you",
            "if a quality or feature tells against someone, it makes them less likely to succeed in achieving something",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc"
        ],
        "answer": "if a quality or feature tells against someone, it makes them less likely to succeed in achieving something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tell apart",
        "options": [
            "same as straighten, ...",
            "to show that something is possible",
            "provide someone with necessary equipment",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things that are very similar"
        ],
        "answer": "to recognize the difference between two people or things that are very similar"
    },
    {
        "question": "tell of",
        "options": [
            "to receive something such as criticism",
            "same as tangle",
            "to inform someone about something, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner"
        ],
        "answer": "to inform someone about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tell off",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone angrily for doing something wrong",
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots",
            "to make someone so frightened that they run away, ...",
            "to eat a large quantity of food, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone angrily for doing something wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "tell on",
        "options": [
            "be good enough, ...",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "to not keep a secret, ...",
            "to put traffic cones across a road in order to prevent traffic from going along the road"
        ],
        "answer": "to not keep a secret, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tense up",
        "options": [
            "not allow yourself to do something",
            "to become friends with someone, ...",
            "same as toss, ...",
            "become nervous, tense or unable to relax"
        ],
        "answer": "become nervous, tense or unable to relax"
    },
    {
        "question": "test out",
        "options": [
            "same as settle, ...",
            "same as test, ...",
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "if people grow apart, their relationship gradually changes and they become less close"
        ],
        "answer": "same as test, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "text out",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in doing something despite having no clear plan, method, or suitable equipment",
            "to produce something quickly and easily, ...",
            "cancel an appointment by sending a text message",
            "to leave quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "cancel an appointment by sending a text message"
    },
    {
        "question": "think ahead",
        "options": [
            "to pull someone or something out of the water, ...",
            "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop",
            "to make plans about things that will or may happen in the future, so that you will be prepared for them",
            "same as lift"
        ],
        "answer": "to make plans about things that will or may happen in the future, so that you will be prepared for them"
    },
    {
        "question": "think back",
        "options": [
            "to get a large amount of sales or profits, ...",
            "to remove parts of a film, television, or radio programme that are not wanted before it is shown or broadcast",
            "to think about something that happened in the past",
            "to mix one substance completely into another one, usually using your hands, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to think about something that happened in the past"
    },
    {
        "question": "think out",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties",
            "to be immediately obvious to someone, or to immediately get their attention",
            "to tell someone a secret",
            "to consider all the important facts in a situation before deciding or doing something"
        ],
        "answer": "to consider all the important facts in a situation before deciding or doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "think over",
        "options": [
            "to consider a problem or decision carefully",
            "if something hangs over you, you worry about it or feel upset about it",
            "to kill a lot of people quickly and violently, especially by shooting them",
            "to plant young plants outdoors"
        ],
        "answer": "to consider a problem or decision carefully"
    },
    {
        "question": "think through",
        "options": [
            "to escape from a person or place, ...",
            "to consider the facts about something in an organized and thorough way",
            "to remove the dirt from something, especially from an upright surface",
            "to remove part of the original sound from a recording, especially a film"
        ],
        "answer": "to consider the facts about something in an organized and thorough way"
    },
    {
        "question": "think up",
        "options": [
            "if something such as an economy or price bottoms out, it reaches its lowest level before starting to improve again",
            "connect with someone or contact them",
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "break something with your feet"
        ],
        "answer": "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse"
    },
    {
        "question": "thirst for",
        "options": [
            "same as toss",
            "become rigid, ...",
            "to suddenly make a car start moving very quickly so that it makes a lot of noise",
            "to want something very much"
        ],
        "answer": "to want something very much"
    },
    {
        "question": "thrash out",
        "options": [
            "to discuss something until you find a solution or reach an agreement",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to separate an area by surrounding it with a fence",
            "visit someone for a short time."
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss something until you find a solution or reach an agreement"
    },
    {
        "question": "thrive on",
        "options": [
            "to be connected with someone or something, ...",
            "to become successful or happy in a particular situation, especially one that other people would not enjoy",
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "put something in a liquid for a short time"
        ],
        "answer": "to become successful or happy in a particular situation, especially one that other people would not enjoy"
    },
    {
        "question": "throttle back",
        "options": [
            "to be extremely nice to someone more important than you because you want them to like you or give you something",
            "to reduce the speed of a vehicle by reducing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "same as cut, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the speed of a vehicle by reducing the supply of fuel to the engine"
    },
    {
        "question": "throttle up",
        "options": [
            "to increase the speed of a vehicle by increasing the supply of fuel to the engine",
            "to spend time doing things that are not important",
            "to refuse to obey instructions, ...",
            "to spend a period of time relaxing or sleeping after doing something tiring"
        ],
        "answer": "to increase the speed of a vehicle by increasing the supply of fuel to the engine"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw aside",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in a fight or an argument with someone",
            "to think hard about someone or something for a long time and try to understand them",
            "to refuse to accept or continue something",
            "to gradually stop using something"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to accept or continue something"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw away",
        "options": [
            "collapse, break, ...",
            "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ...",
            "to consider something as separate from other things, ...",
            "to heat food until it is warm in all parts"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of something that you no longer want, for example by putting it in a dustbin, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw back",
        "options": [
            "to make someone go away or leave a place, especially by chasing them, ...",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to depend on someone or something for the money or food that you need",
            "to continue to do something even though it is difficult or unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw back on",
        "options": [
            "to do something that you have agreed or promised to do, ...",
            "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use",
            "to continue doing something although it is difficult or although other people have stopped doing it",
            "perform surgery"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to use their own abilities, powers etc because there is nothing else to use"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw in",
        "options": [
            "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ...",
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ...",
            "same as come at, ...",
            "stop supporting someone when they are in trouble"
        ],
        "answer": "to add a remark, question etc in a conversation, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw off",
        "options": [
            "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ...",
            "associate with, ...",
            "to talk to someone who has done something wrong in an effort to persuade them to improve their behaviour",
            "focus less closely"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly remove a piece of clothing, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw off at",
        "options": [
            "to ask or persuade someone to do something",
            "produce or issue, usually from a machine",
            "to criticize someone in an unkind or unfair way",
            "to suddenly understand or realize something"
        ],
        "answer": "to criticize someone in an unkind or unfair way"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw on",
        "options": [
            "give support, reinforce, strengthen",
            "associate with, ...",
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ...",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing"
        ],
        "answer": "to quickly put on a piece of clothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw out",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone in an unkind or unfair way",
            "to move in a circle, ...",
            "persuade someone",
            "same as throw away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as throw away, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw over",
        "options": [
            "to end a romantic or sexual relationship with someone",
            "to tell or send someone information that you have discovered, ...",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to ask someone to leave a place, usually by telephoning them or sending them a message"
        ],
        "answer": "to end a romantic or sexual relationship with someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw together",
        "options": [
            "to go to a better job, higher level etc, ...",
            "to be caused by something",
            "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ...",
            "to take someone or something with you when you go somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something quickly because you do not have much time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw up",
        "options": [
            "used for giving someone permission to ask a question",
            "to produce something new or unexpected, ...",
            "to have a particular name, ...",
            "be enjoyable to drink or eat"
        ],
        "answer": "to produce something new or unexpected, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "throw yourself at",
        "options": [
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to get rid of an illness by sweating a lot, ...",
            "make it clear you are sexually attracted to someone"
        ],
        "answer": "make it clear you are sexually attracted to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "throw yourself into",
        "options": [
            "to spend time doing nothing",
            "do something enthusiastically or energetically",
            "to break something inwards",
            "if the weather closes in, it becomes unpleasant, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "do something enthusiastically or energetically"
    },
    {
        "question": "thrust aside",
        "options": [
            "to put things together without any order, ...",
            "criticise something strongly",
            "if a roof or wall caves in, it falls down or inwards, ...",
            "to pay no attention to something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pay no attention to something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "thrust upon",
        "options": [
            "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them",
            "to put your hand into a container in order to get something, ...",
            "to talk about someone or something in a way that makes them seem more important or better than they really are",
            "to force someone to do or to accept something"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to do or to accept something"
    },
    {
        "question": "thump out",
        "options": [
            "to play a tune very loudly, especially on the piano",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "do something without making much effort or trying to improve",
            "to produce a copy of a computer document from a printer"
        ],
        "answer": "to play a tune very loudly, especially on the piano"
    },
    {
        "question": "tick along",
        "options": [
            "to make it possible for something to happen in the future, ...",
            "make reasonable progress without any serious problems",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ...",
            "to get rid of something unpleasant"
        ],
        "answer": "make reasonable progress without any serious problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "tick away",
        "options": [
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way",
            "to stop someone from moving their car out of a place, ...",
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "to be unable to stop yourself from getting involved in something bad"
        ],
        "answer": "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tick by",
        "options": [
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "if a train pulls out, it leaves a station, ...",
            "to make something necessary or suitable, ...",
            "to invest a lot of money in something"
        ],
        "answer": "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tick off",
        "options": [
            "break or damage, ...",
            "to go with someone who does not want to be with you, ...",
            "to appear strong and confident when someone is threatening or criticizing you",
            "to annoy someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to annoy someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tick over",
        "options": [
            "visit a place to check something",
            "provide someone with what they require, ...",
            "same as build on",
            "to operate steadily but not very well, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to operate steadily but not very well, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tickle up",
        "options": [
            "improve a document",
            "to criticize someone regularly or for a long time",
            "to buy something expensive",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way"
        ],
        "answer": "improve a document"
    },
    {
        "question": "tide over",
        "options": [
            "roll or form into a round shape, ...",
            "die",
            "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more",
            "to destroy something with an explosion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to help someone to get to the end of a difficult period of time, especially by giving them money until they can get some more"
    },
    {
        "question": "tidy away",
        "options": [
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "same as tone"
        ],
        "answer": "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them"
    },
    {
        "question": "tidy out",
        "options": [
            "not very attractive, ...",
            "to reduce something such as a price or salary, ...",
            "to admire and respect someone",
            "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a room or cupboard look better by removing things that you do not want"
    },
    {
        "question": "tidy up",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to turn and go back in the direction that you have come from",
            "to choose someone or something from a number of possible choices",
            "same as tidy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as tidy, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tidy up after",
        "options": [
            "to continue to do something even though it is difficult or unpleasant",
            "make an empty space inside in something, reduce power or authority",
            "to make a room look tidy after someone else has made it untidy",
            "behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a room look tidy after someone else has made it untidy"
    },
    {
        "question": "tie back",
        "options": [
            "fasten or secure so that it doesn't obstruct",
            "if you wash dirt off something, or if dirt washes off, you remove it by washing",
            "when a space vehicle splashes down, it lands in the sea after being in space",
            "to become involved in something that other people are doing that is fun or interesting, or that makes money"
        ],
        "answer": "fasten or secure so that it doesn't obstruct"
    },
    {
        "question": "tie down",
        "options": [
            "to include a particular amount or factor when you calculate something",
            "to cover something with wooden boards",
            "accuse somebody of a crime",
            "to force a group of soldiers to stay in one place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to force a group of soldiers to stay in one place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tie in",
        "options": [
            "change tv channels quickly",
            "to invest a lot of money in something",
            "to discuss a plan or a situation in a detailed way, ...",
            "associate with, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "associate with, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tie in with",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel more and more unhappy or worried",
            "to say something while you are breathing with difficulty, for example because you need more air, or are in pain",
            "to combine with something, ...",
            "to use steam to separate two edges or pieces of paper that are stuck together"
        ],
        "answer": "to combine with something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tie up",
        "options": [
            "to give a person or political party a position of power by voting",
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually",
            "to tie the ends of something together, ...",
            "to try to find something, especially by moving other things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to tie the ends of something together, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tie up with",
        "options": [
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots",
            "to fire a gun or bullet, ...",
            "to connect something with something else",
            "to take a piece of clothing off quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to connect something with something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "tighten up",
        "options": [
            "same as tighten, ...",
            "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ...",
            "same as jump, ...",
            "to remove something from a surface using steam"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tighten, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "time out",
        "options": [
            "clear a table in a restaurant",
            "end or close because of a time limit, ...",
            "same as mop, ...",
            "to post something to someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "end or close because of a time limit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tip off",
        "options": [
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "same as cool, ...",
            "to give someone a warning or secret information about something",
            "to move more slowly than other people so that you are behind them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give someone a warning or secret information about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tip over",
        "options": [
            "if something tips over, or if someone or something tips it over, it falls onto its side",
            "to try to make people support you or buy something from you",
            "to seem to have a small amount of an unpleasant quality",
            "to burn gas and let it go into the atmosphere"
        ],
        "answer": "if something tips over, or if someone or something tips it over, it falls onto its side"
    },
    {
        "question": "tip up",
        "options": [
            "to get rid of someone or something that you do not want, by persuading someone else to take or buy them from you, ...",
            "to turn a container upside down so that the things inside it come out, ...",
            "get to the bottom of something, get detailed data",
            "to remove something from a surface by cutting or digging with a sharp object"
        ],
        "answer": "to turn a container upside down so that the things inside it come out, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tiptoe around",
        "options": [
            "to continue to cause trouble",
            "to avoid dealing directly with a problem, ...",
            "to cause problems for someone, ...",
            "to manage to say something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid dealing directly with a problem, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tire of",
        "options": [
            "to always enjoy something, ...",
            "to make a photograph bigger, ...",
            "to think that something is the right thing to do, ...",
            "to put a person or animal in a place that they cannot leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to always enjoy something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tire out",
        "options": [
            "if you switch on something such as a light or a machine, or if it switches on, you make it start working",
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ...",
            "to make someone feel very tired",
            "to become completely understood"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel very tired"
    },
    {
        "question": "toddle off",
        "options": [
            "to increase in size, ...",
            "to stop asking for something, or to stop saying that you will do something, because a lot of people oppose you",
            "to leave in order to go somewhere",
            "to depend on someone to do what you want or expect them to do for you, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to leave in order to go somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "tone down",
        "options": [
            "consider, regard",
            "make a quick note",
            "to make something less severe, shocking, or offensive, ...",
            "to become sober after being drunk, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something less severe, shocking, or offensive, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tone in",
        "options": [
            "to attempt to get or achieve something difficult or something that you want very much",
            "to definitely decide, arrange, or complete something, ...",
            "to change part of the original sound of a recording, especially a film, by adding new sound to it",
            "same as tone"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tone"
    },
    {
        "question": "tone in with",
        "options": [
            "to solve a confusing or complicated problem by thinking carefully about it",
            "same as tone",
            "to allow someone or something to move to a lower position, ...",
            "to have an effect gradually or after a long time"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tone"
    },
    {
        "question": "tone up",
        "options": [
            "to hit someone a lot, ...",
            "try to keep something",
            "same as tone",
            "to be made at a particular time in the past"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tone"
    },
    {
        "question": "tool up",
        "options": [
            "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ...",
            "hold tight",
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "to become tired of something or bored with it"
        ],
        "answer": "to provide someone with a weapon, especially so that they can commit a crime, or to be provided with a weapon for this purpose, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tootle off",
        "options": [
            "to leave, ...",
            "same as beat up",
            "leave, depart",
            "to do someone\u2019s work while they are away or ill, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "leave, depart"
    },
    {
        "question": "top off",
        "options": [
            "make a mistake, do badly, spoil",
            "same as top up, ...",
            "to recognize that something is not true and not be tricked by it, ...",
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation"
        ],
        "answer": "same as top up, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "top out",
        "options": [
            "to give your opinions about something in a very annoying way, especially when you are complaining or criticizing something",
            "if a rate or an amount tops out, it reaches its highest level",
            "to become mentally ill, ...",
            "to make something part of a plan, system, calculation etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if a rate or an amount tops out, it reaches its highest level"
    },
    {
        "question": "top up",
        "options": [
            "same as camp, ...",
            "to completely fill a container that is already partly full, ...",
            "to stretch out your arm to try to touch or hold someone or something",
            "turn quickly and face in the opposite direction"
        ],
        "answer": "to completely fill a container that is already partly full, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "toss about",
        "options": [
            "to take someone or something from one place and have them with you when you arrive somewhere else",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way",
            "move quickly",
            "to send a letter or document to an organization, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
    },
    {
        "question": "toss around",
        "options": [
            "intend, plan",
            "if a building, garden etc backs onto a place, that place is directly behind it",
            "leave a place angrily",
            "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
        ],
        "answer": "to discuss something such as an idea, often in an informal way"
    },
    {
        "question": "toss aside",
        "options": [
            "if two people fight it out, they fight or argue until something is decided",
            "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you",
            "leave suddenly",
            "to arrive or appear somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop accepting or believing in something, especially when the situation makes this difficult for you"
    },
    {
        "question": "toss back",
        "options": [
            "to drink something, usually alcohol, quickly, swallowing it all at once, ...",
            "to not use the usual way of doing something",
            "roll or form into a round shape, ...",
            "visit for a short time"
        ],
        "answer": "to drink something, usually alcohol, quickly, swallowing it all at once, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "toss down",
        "options": [
            "to happen, especially by chance, ...",
            "drink quickly",
            "to remove part of the original sound from a recording, especially a film",
            "to produce a new product and start to sell it, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "drink quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "toss for",
        "options": [
            "to start to be good or effective because different parts are combining well, ...",
            "make a decision by throwing a coin and seeing which side lands face up",
            "criticise someone, ...",
            "save money in a bank account, investment, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "make a decision by throwing a coin and seeing which side lands face up"
    },
    {
        "question": "toss off",
        "options": [
            "to make strong steady progress, ...",
            "remove someone secretly of discreetly",
            "to do something quickly, easily, and without much effort, ...",
            "focus more closely"
        ],
        "answer": "to do something quickly, easily, and without much effort, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "toss out",
        "options": [
            "to make it seem that someone is guilty of a crime when they are not, ...",
            "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim",
            "put something in a liquid for a short time",
            "same as toss, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as toss, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "toss up",
        "options": [
            "same as toss",
            "to start to sleep, ...",
            "same as broaden",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as toss"
    },
    {
        "question": "touch down",
        "options": [
            "to begin a journey, ...",
            "be funny, or try to",
            "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands",
            "burn brightly"
        ],
        "answer": "if an aircraft or space vehicle touches down, it lands"
    },
    {
        "question": "touch for",
        "options": [
            "to get or borrow money from someone",
            "if something such as your hair or a tooth falls out, it comes out, ...",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "to think that a person or thing is someone or something else"
        ],
        "answer": "to get or borrow money from someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "touch off",
        "options": [
            "to make something unpleasant or dangerous happen",
            "to be very happy about something, ...",
            "do something enthusiastically or energetically",
            "be ill"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something unpleasant or dangerous happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "touch on",
        "options": [
            "make yourself comfortable",
            "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to",
            "to mention something when you are talking or writing",
            "to deal with or organize something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to mention something when you are talking or writing"
    },
    {
        "question": "touch up",
        "options": [
            "be recognised as important, worthwhile or valuable",
            "turn quickly and face in the opposite direction",
            "if something jumps out at you, you notice it immediately",
            "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a surface look better with small improvements, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "touch upon",
        "options": [
            "to stop supporting one group and start supporting another, ...",
            "same as touch",
            "to eat food, especially a lot of food, quickly or in an enthusiastic way",
            "make or persuade someone to accept something you don't want"
        ],
        "answer": "same as touch"
    },
    {
        "question": "tow away",
        "options": [
            "to clock off, ...",
            "to give something to someone officially and formally",
            "be shocked or surprised",
            "to take a vehicle away from a place by towing it, especially because it is parked illegally"
        ],
        "answer": "to take a vehicle away from a place by towing it, especially because it is parked illegally"
    },
    {
        "question": "toy at",
        "options": [
            "to suffer extreme poverty or deprivation, ...",
            "pretend to think about or think about in a casual way",
            "same as fill, ...",
            "to make something begin, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pretend to think about or think about in a casual way"
    },
    {
        "question": "toy over",
        "options": [
            "think about something",
            "to make someone leave a job or position without saying anything publicly",
            "to die, ...",
            "when there is too much moisture and a plant is affected by fungal parasites"
        ],
        "answer": "think about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "toy with",
        "options": [
            "to consider an idea in a way that is not serious or definite, ...",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to believe that a trick or a joke is true, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to consider an idea in a way that is not serious or definite, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "track down",
        "options": [
            "same as build, ...",
            "to find someone or something after a long search",
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them",
            "to become involved in a discussion or argument, especially in order to make it stop"
        ],
        "answer": "to find someone or something after a long search"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade down",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "to gradually start using something",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is less expensive",
            "to be the result of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is less expensive"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade in",
        "options": [
            "to give something old as part of the payment for something new",
            "to move away from someone or something, ...",
            "to persuade someone to lower the price of something, ...",
            "to limit someone\u2019s freedom to choose what to do, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give something old as part of the payment for something new"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade off",
        "options": [
            "stop doing or using something to change to something different",
            "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit",
            "wait or refuse to do something until you get what you want",
            "to buy a large quantity of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to accept a disadvantage so that you can have a benefit"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade on",
        "options": [
            "to get an advantage by making use of something",
            "if two people stay together, they continue to live together or to have a relationship with each other",
            "to take someone or something from one place to the place where someone else is, especially their home",
            "if a situation or feeling boils over, people cannot control their anger and start to fight or argue, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get an advantage by making use of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade up",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone a secret",
            "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive",
            "to include something, ...",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to sell something in order to buy something of the same kind that is more expensive"
    },
    {
        "question": "trade upon",
        "options": [
            "exploit, use to your advantage",
            "make electrical connections",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ...",
            "persuade someone to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "exploit, use to your advantage"
    },
    {
        "question": "trail away",
        "options": [
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "if someone\u2019s voice or words trail away or trail off, they gradually become silent",
            "to think about a time or event in the past, ...",
            "to arrange for a case to be discussed in a court, committee, or parliament, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if someone\u2019s voice or words trail away or trail off, they gradually become silent"
    },
    {
        "question": "train up",
        "options": [
            "teach someone the specific skills they will need to carry out a job or task",
            "same as buckle, ...",
            "to fix something to a wall with a nail or nails, ...",
            "burn brightly"
        ],
        "answer": "teach someone the specific skills they will need to carry out a job or task"
    },
    {
        "question": "treat with",
        "options": [
            "to have a formal discussion with someone in order to try to reach an agreement about something",
            "fairly old, ...",
            "arrive, end a journey in a place, often without planning",
            "to do a particular piece of work, research etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have a formal discussion with someone in order to try to reach an agreement about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "trespass on",
        "options": [
            "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ...",
            "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair",
            "pass without stopping",
            "to become smaller or lower in amount, level, value etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to use more of someone\u2019s time or to accept more of someone\u2019s kindness than is fair"
    },
    {
        "question": "trick out",
        "options": [
            "to blame or criticize yourself or someone else, ...",
            "to leave secretly, ...",
            "to begin a new career or way of life, ...",
            "to decorate something in a particular way, or to wear a particular set of clothes"
        ],
        "answer": "to decorate something in a particular way, or to wear a particular set of clothes"
    },
    {
        "question": "trickle down",
        "options": [
            "to have an effect gradually or after a long time",
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "to bring a plane down to the ground, ...",
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people"
        ],
        "answer": "to have an effect gradually or after a long time"
    },
    {
        "question": "trickle up",
        "options": [
            "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "to spend your time behaving in a silly way",
            "to be the real reason for a decision or action"
        ],
        "answer": "when financial benefits given to poor people or small businesses pass on to the wealthy"
    },
    {
        "question": "trigger off",
        "options": [
            "start, set off, ...",
            "to pick up things from several different places and put them together",
            "be near a time",
            "talk fast or incomprehensibly"
        ],
        "answer": "start, set off, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trim down",
        "options": [
            "same as goof",
            "to hit someone with enough force to make them fall down, ...",
            "to make a connection in an electric circuit, ...",
            "to become thinner by losing weight, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to become thinner by losing weight, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trip out",
        "options": [
            "same as trip, ...",
            "reduce, decrease",
            "same as fool, ...",
            "divert money illegally, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as trip, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trip over",
        "options": [
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need",
            "fall, ...",
            "to go to bed later than usual, ...",
            "to do something that should have been done before, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "fall, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trip up",
        "options": [
            "leave somewhere in a defiant or pompous manner",
            "to do a mathematical calculation to find out how many times a smaller number will fit into a larger number",
            "same as trip, ...",
            "to read the measurement on a piece of equipment or graph"
        ],
        "answer": "same as trip, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "troll for",
        "options": [
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "take to another place quickly",
            "to discover something, ...",
            "to try to find or get something in a relaxed way"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to find or get something in a relaxed way"
    },
    {
        "question": "trot off",
        "options": [
            "to tell someone to move away from a place, ...",
            "leave",
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ...",
            "fall asleep"
        ],
        "answer": "leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "trot off to",
        "options": [
            "go somewhere",
            "to agree with one particular person and support them in an argument",
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ...",
            "have or do something at the end or as the last of something"
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "trot out",
        "options": [
            "to phone, write, or speak to someone at a later time because you were busy or could not answer their question earlier",
            "face up to someone, withstand criticism",
            "same as serve, ...",
            "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone appear in public, usually to represent an organization or an opinion, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trudge through",
        "options": [
            "understand something",
            "do something slowly, with difficulty, unwillingly or considerable effort",
            "have sex with",
            "to talk about something in detail, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "do something slowly, with difficulty, unwillingly or considerable effort"
    },
    {
        "question": "trump up",
        "options": [
            "feel more confident or optimistic about something",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the next page of a document appear on the screen",
            "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime",
            "to combine with something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to deliberately make up information that connects someone with a crime"
    },
    {
        "question": "trundle out",
        "options": [
            "to include someone in your plans",
            "to happen, ...",
            "to spoil something or do something badly",
            "to give information, reasons, or a list of things that you have given many times before"
        ],
        "answer": "to give information, reasons, or a list of things that you have given many times before"
    },
    {
        "question": "truss up",
        "options": [
            "to stop competing or arguing and accept that you cannot win, ...",
            "same as truss, ...",
            "to eat your evening meal at home, or at a hotel when you are staying there, instead of at a restaurant",
            "to type something that someone has written with a pen or pencil"
        ],
        "answer": "same as truss, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "trust in",
        "options": [
            "to connect a piece of equipment such as a washing machine to the water pipes in a room so that water can flow to and from it",
            "to have confidence in someone or something",
            "to leave quickly, ...",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have confidence in someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "trust to",
        "options": [
            "to be dressed in a particular way, ...",
            "same as stop",
            "to depend on something such as luck or chance to help you to achieve something, usually because you have no other choice",
            "to read all of a document, book etc in order to check or correct it"
        ],
        "answer": "to depend on something such as luck or chance to help you to achieve something, usually because you have no other choice"
    },
    {
        "question": "try back",
        "options": [
            "same as knock down, ...",
            "to make something quickly and often carelessly by putting together various objects or ideas",
            "phone back",
            "to fail to do something that you have promised or agreed to do"
        ],
        "answer": "phone back"
    },
    {
        "question": "try for",
        "options": [
            "to focus on satisfying the people who are above you in an organization, more than on the people you are responsible for",
            "same as trip, ...",
            "to be easy to notice, ...",
            "to attempt to get or achieve something difficult or something that you want very much"
        ],
        "answer": "to attempt to get or achieve something difficult or something that you want very much"
    },
    {
        "question": "try it on",
        "options": [
            "to be used to help to pay for something",
            "to stop something from happening",
            "same as save",
            "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "provoke someone by being annoying or behaving badly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "try on",
        "options": [
            "to try on clothes to see if they fit, ...",
            "to make someone become involved in a situation when they do not want to, ...",
            "to reduce an amount of something, ...",
            "be the reason for something"
        ],
        "answer": "to try on clothes to see if they fit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "try out",
        "options": [
            "same as drop, ...",
            "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective",
            "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you",
            "yield, surrender, retreat, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to test someone or something to see what they are like or whether they are suitable or effective"
    },
    {
        "question": "try out for",
        "options": [
            "to try to become a member of a team or to get a part in a play or film by showing someone how well you can play or perform",
            "to stop yourself from showing a feeling or emotion",
            "work hard doing something",
            "wipe, remove with a brush, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to become a member of a team or to get a part in a play or film by showing someone how well you can play or perform"
    },
    {
        "question": "tuck away",
        "options": [
            "to rain very hard",
            "to prevent people from entering an area or a building",
            "to admit that you have done something bad or embarrassing",
            "to put money in a safe place so that you can use it later, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to put money in a safe place so that you can use it later, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tuck in",
        "options": [
            "to meet someone unexpectedly, ...",
            "to be correct, suitable, or sensible in relation to something else",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "face (of a building)"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tuck into",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out information about something",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to be more successful, or to progress more quickly than, other people",
            "arrive"
        ],
        "answer": "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tuck up",
        "options": [
            "join a teleconference",
            "to no longer use someone or something because you no longer want or need them",
            "same as tuck in",
            "to order something and ask for it to be delivered to you"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tuck in"
    },
    {
        "question": "tumble down",
        "options": [
            "relax, unwind",
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "have no more left",
            "in a factory, to pass a special card through a piece of equipment to record that you are leaving work"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tumble, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tumble to",
        "options": [
            "to realize or understand something",
            "to ask several people for information or advice",
            "approach someone discreetly",
            "used for telling someone in a rude way to go away"
        ],
        "answer": "to realize or understand something"
    },
    {
        "question": "tune in",
        "options": [
            "to stop a fight, ...",
            "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ...",
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them",
            "to start living somewhere, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to understand something such as a situation or someone else\u2019s feelings, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "tune in to",
        "options": [
            "to arrive at a place by accident or without intending to go there",
            "to officially give your property to someone by writing your name on a document",
            "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme",
            "to cough loudly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme"
    },
    {
        "question": "tune out",
        "options": [
            "used to tell someone to go away because they're annoying you",
            "to stop paying attention",
            "to suddenly choose someone or something after being unable to decide what to do",
            "to say that you want someone to give something, often money you have paid, back to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop paying attention"
    },
    {
        "question": "tune up",
        "options": [
            "to get to the end of a difficult or dangerous period or situation without any serious problems",
            "to challenge someone over something they have said or done, ...",
            "same as tune, ...",
            "remove quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "same as tune, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turf out",
        "options": [
            "tease, make fun of",
            "if a boat shoves off, it moves away from the land into the water, ...",
            "to change someone or something so that they become something else",
            "to force someone to leave a place or an organization"
        ],
        "answer": "to force someone to leave a place or an organization"
    },
    {
        "question": "turn against",
        "options": [
            "spend some time doing little things for pleasure",
            "to keep criticizing someone or something",
            "persuade, ...",
            "to make someone stop liking or supporting someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone stop liking or supporting someone or something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn around",
        "options": [
            "check in at a hotel, ...",
            "same as camp, ...",
            "to consider or express something in a different way, ...",
            "do something out of a car"
        ],
        "answer": "to consider or express something in a different way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn away",
        "options": [
            "to refuse to let someone come into a place",
            "invite someone",
            "end or close because of a time limit, ...",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to let someone come into a place"
    },
    {
        "question": "turn away from",
        "options": [
            "relax, do nothing",
            "to refuse to accept or to use something any longer",
            "to phone, write, or speak to someone at a later time because you were busy or could not answer their question earlier",
            "to know about someone or something, but not know any details, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to refuse to accept or to use something any longer"
    },
    {
        "question": "turn back",
        "options": [
            "to make someone unconscious, ...",
            "move to another side or place",
            "same as mop, ...",
            "same as turn down, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as turn down, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn down",
        "options": [
            "to fold the edge of something, ...",
            "to show respect to someone who is more powerful than you",
            "to avoid going to school or work when you should go",
            "same as toss, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to fold the edge of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn in",
        "options": [
            "to spoil something or do something badly",
            "to go to bed at night, ...",
            "to keep telling someone what to do as if you have authority over them, in a way that annoys people",
            "to put things back in their correct place after you have been using them"
        ],
        "answer": "to go to bed at night, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn in on",
        "options": [
            "to be especially nice to someone so that they will agree to something that you want them to agree to",
            "to start to think only about yourself and your own problems and to forget about other people and their problems",
            "to measure an exact amount of something",
            "to put yourself in a difficult situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to start to think only about yourself and your own problems and to forget about other people and their problems"
    },
    {
        "question": "turn into",
        "options": [
            "to change or develop into something different, ...",
            "to quickly look through a magazine or book, or to quickly look at several different television programmes",
            "to order food from a restaurant and ask for it to be delivered to you",
            "to use an opportunity to make a profit or gain an advantage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to change or develop into something different, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn off",
        "options": [
            "to stop paying attention, ...",
            "to visit someone for a short time on your way to another place, especially if they are ill or may need help",
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ...",
            "to give things to different people in a group, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stop paying attention, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn on",
        "options": [
            "to have something such as a good ability or quality, ...",
            "to make someone accept something that they do not want",
            "have sex with",
            "to suddenly attack someone violently, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to suddenly attack someone violently, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn out",
        "options": [
            "to be dressed in a particular way, ...",
            "to quickly read everything on a list, ...",
            "to find or see someone or something when you did not expect to",
            "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them"
        ],
        "answer": "to be dressed in a particular way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn over",
        "options": [
            "to continue to talk for a long time",
            "to put soil around a plant in order to protect it or to help it to grow",
            "to enter a place illegally and steal things from it, ...",
            "in science fiction stories, to bring someone back to their spacecraft using special electronic equipment"
        ],
        "answer": "to enter a place illegally and steal things from it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn round",
        "options": [
            "same as turn",
            "to begin talking in a boring or annoying way, usually complaining or criticizing someone or something",
            "to become ill with a particular disease, usually one that is not serious",
            "if a feeling or quality goes out of someone or something, they do not have it any longer"
        ],
        "answer": "same as turn"
    },
    {
        "question": "turn to",
        "options": [
            "to make a lot of money, ...",
            "to ask for news about someone",
            "to try to make a problem or difficult situation seem less important than it is",
            "same as turn, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as turn, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "turn up",
        "options": [
            "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ...",
            "same as finish, ...",
            "pass (time)",
            "to make something quickly and without a lot of care, using whatever is available"
        ],
        "answer": "to happen unexpectedly or by chance, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "type in",
        "options": [
            "to compare one thing with another, ...",
            "to continue a journey, especially after stopping for a period of time, ...",
            "to leave a place, especially in a way that is not noticed by other people",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen"
        ],
        "answer": "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen"
    },
    {
        "question": "type into",
        "options": [
            "to happen, ...",
            "to bail out of a plane, ...",
            "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen",
            "to enter a place in large numbers, especially in a way that is not organized"
        ],
        "answer": "to type information on a keyboard so that it is recorded by a computer and appears on its screen"
    },
    {
        "question": "type out",
        "options": [
            "to phone, write, or speak to someone at a later time because you were busy or could not answer their question earlier",
            "to recognize a particular quality in someone or something, ...",
            "to write the whole of something using a keyboard",
            "to continue doing something although it is difficult or although other people have stopped doing it"
        ],
        "answer": "to write the whole of something using a keyboard"
    },
    {
        "question": "type up",
        "options": [
            "to agree how much each person or group should pay, ...",
            "to type something that someone has written with a pen or pencil",
            "to take something that you earn or are given in one year or period of time into the next one, ...",
            "fall in large numbers"
        ],
        "answer": "to type something that someone has written with a pen or pencil"
    },
    {
        "question": "urge on",
        "options": [
            "to start a journey, ...",
            "to steal something, ...",
            "to encourage someone to put more effort into something or to not stop trying to do something",
            "make yourself popular with someone"
        ],
        "answer": "to encourage someone to put more effort into something or to not stop trying to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "urge upon",
        "options": [
            "to search very hard for something, ...",
            "to start doing something new or different",
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "persuade or pressure to accept something"
        ],
        "answer": "persuade or pressure to accept something"
    },
    {
        "question": "use up",
        "options": [
            "same as broaden",
            "to lead someone into a room where they are going to meet other people",
            "to go to sleep, especially when you do not intend to",
            "to use all of a supply of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to use all of a supply of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "usher in",
        "options": [
            "to make an activity or process begin",
            "to clean someone or something using your hands or a brush",
            "to post something to someone, ...",
            "to move towards someone quietly and slowly, especially because you want to surprise them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make an activity or process begin"
    },
    {
        "question": "vacuum up",
        "options": [
            "criticise",
            "to focus on being an effective manager for the people you are responsible for in an organization, more than on satisfying the people who are above you",
            "to solve a problem or a mystery, ...",
            "consume"
        ],
        "answer": "consume"
    },
    {
        "question": "vamp up",
        "options": [
            "to switch off a light, ...",
            "to deal with official or legal business more quickly than usual",
            "to improve something by making it more interesting, attractive, or powerful",
            "invent, maker up, improvise, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "invent, maker up, improvise, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "veg out",
        "options": [
            "to develop from something, or to exist as a result of it, ...",
            "to leave one place and move to another",
            "relax, do nothing",
            "same as hatch"
        ],
        "answer": "relax, do nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "venture forth",
        "options": [
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "pass a law, regulation, etc, without considering or debating it seriously",
            "same as come",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somewhere safe or comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "visit on",
        "options": [
            "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone",
            "fasten something to the ground",
            "to interrupt an activity or process, ...",
            "to try to find something"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something very unpleasant happen to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "vote down",
        "options": [
            "to offer money for something in order to increase its price, and not because you want to buy it",
            "to quickly look through a magazine or book, or to quickly look at several different television programmes",
            "avoid doing something",
            "to stop or end something as the result of a vote"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop or end something as the result of a vote"
    },
    {
        "question": "vote in",
        "options": [
            "to discover a fact or piece of information, ...",
            "to give a person or political party a position of power by voting",
            "escape notice and be approved",
            "stop doing something annoying"
        ],
        "answer": "to give a person or political party a position of power by voting"
    },
    {
        "question": "vote off",
        "options": [
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to remove someone from a position on something such as a committee by voting",
            "to discuss a plan or agreement in order to agree about the details",
            "to give someone a particular type of clothing to wear"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove someone from a position on something such as a committee by voting"
    },
    {
        "question": "vote out",
        "options": [
            "to remove a person or political party from a position by voting",
            "to rub a surface to make it smooth or dry, ...",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "if you grow away from someone, your relationship gradually changes and you become less close to them"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a person or political party from a position by voting"
    },
    {
        "question": "vote through",
        "options": [
            "same as hatch",
            "if a group of people crowd in on someone, they move close to them and then surround them, ...",
            "to make something accepted officially by voting",
            "to be similar to or agree with someone else\u2019s ideas, plans, feelings etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to make something accepted officially by voting"
    },
    {
        "question": "wade in",
        "options": [
            "to become involved in someone else\u2019s discussion, argument, or fight in a confident way that may not be very welcome",
            "to end a letter, ...",
            "to keep a mother and baby together after the birth",
            "to clean a place after someone has made it dirty or untidy"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in someone else\u2019s discussion, argument, or fight in a confident way that may not be very welcome"
    },
    {
        "question": "wade into",
        "options": [
            "to spend a lot of time thinking or talking about something unpleasant",
            "to break because of being old or badly made, ...",
            "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually",
            "to drink something quickly, usually swallowing it all at once, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "become embroiled or involved in a situation, without thinking or planning usually"
    },
    {
        "question": "wade through",
        "options": [
            "to read or deal with a lot of boring information",
            "to feel worried about someone or something because you think something bad may happen to them or has happened to them",
            "to go to sleep",
            "to get permission from someone to do something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to read or deal with a lot of boring information"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait about",
        "options": [
            "to say something suddenly in a very loud voice, ...",
            "to save money for the future, often hiding it illegally",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait around",
        "options": [
            "if the sea casts something up, the sea carries it somewhere and leaves it there",
            "to have a meal in a restaurant instead of at home",
            "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does",
            "to become involved in something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do nothing because you are expecting something to happen, and you cannot do anything until it does"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait behind",
        "options": [
            "leave the top deck of a ship",
            "to go somewhere where you can be alone, ...",
            "to stay somewhere after everyone else has left",
            "if you are loaded down with a lot of heavy things, you are carrying them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stay somewhere after everyone else has left"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait in",
        "options": [
            "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you",
            "move easily and quickly",
            "same as blank, ...",
            "same as pen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to stay at home because you expect someone to come or to telephone you"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait on",
        "options": [
            "to do something very quickly and not very carefully",
            "keep something near you",
            "to serve people in a restaurant, ...",
            "make a fire burn less, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to serve people in a restaurant, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wait out",
        "options": [
            "to stop criticizing someone or telling them what to do, ...",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad",
            "leave in a stealthy or quiet manner"
        ],
        "answer": "to stay where you are until something ends, usually something bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "wait up",
        "options": [
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "to start behaving in a bad way",
            "to decide or agree on something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wait up!",
        "options": [
            "to arrive at work or school, ...",
            "win easily",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to ask for money and other things from someone such as a friend or relative and make no effort to give them anything or to pay for anything yourself"
        ],
        "answer": "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wait upon",
        "options": [
            "to behave in a stupid way, ...",
            "same as blot",
            "provide someone with what they require, ...",
            "to shoot people, animals, or aircraft one by one by aiming at them carefully from a distance"
        ],
        "answer": "provide someone with what they require, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wake up",
        "options": [
            "to cause problems or delays for someone, ...",
            "same as slough, ...",
            "same as wake, ...",
            "break a piece off something"
        ],
        "answer": "same as wake, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wake up to",
        "options": [
            "same as get along, ...",
            "to make a tree or tall plant fall down by cutting through it, ...",
            "to start existing or being seen, ...",
            "to start to realize something"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to realize something"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk around",
        "options": [
            "to use something for a particular purpose, ...",
            "same as stock",
            "to dress or behave in public in a particular way, especially when this makes you look or seem silly",
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended"
        ],
        "answer": "to dress or behave in public in a particular way, especially when this makes you look or seem silly"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk away",
        "options": [
            "to become friends with someone, ...",
            "to leave a place, situation, or person",
            "break something with your feet",
            "to cut something into several pieces using a saw or a knife"
        ],
        "answer": "to leave a place, situation, or person"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk away from",
        "options": [
            "to pick up things from several different places and put them together",
            "to remove small pieces of something from a surface by hitting it",
            "stop your unfair or unreasonable behaviour",
            "leave something you don't like"
        ],
        "answer": "leave something you don't like"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk away with",
        "options": [
            "to steal something, ...",
            "to fail a test or a course at school, ...",
            "same as cut down, ...",
            "same as get across, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to steal something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "walk back from",
        "options": [
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly",
            "to collect crops from the field when they are ready",
            "to stop, get rid of, or destroy something, ...",
            "retract a statement"
        ],
        "answer": "retract a statement"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk in on",
        "options": [
            "to try to make someone understand how important something is",
            "to walk into a room where someone is doing something private or secret",
            "to involve someone or something in a system, plan etc in such a way that they cannot easily escape from it",
            "to obtain an amount of money that you need, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to walk into a room where someone is doing something private or secret"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk into",
        "options": [
            "to find a job easily, ...",
            "to lose an opportunity to do or have something, ...",
            "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature",
            "to form a long line of traffic that is not moving"
        ],
        "answer": "to find a job easily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "walk off",
        "options": [
            "to make a fire stop burning by putting your feet down hard on it, ...",
            "to get rid of a bad feeling or condition by going for a walk, ...",
            "do something enthusiastically or energetically",
            "to realize or understand something"
        ],
        "answer": "to get rid of a bad feeling or condition by going for a walk, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "walk off with",
        "options": [
            "if a shop has something in, it is available in the shop for you to buy, ...",
            "to start to have a sexual or romantic relationship with someone that you had a relationship with before",
            "want something a lot",
            "to steal something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to steal something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "walk on",
        "options": [
            "if someone or something blends in, they are similar to the other people, objects, buildings etc around them, and so they seem appropriate or you do not notice them",
            "to continue walking in your intended direction",
            "to do something so that a proposal is accepted or an issue is dealt with quickly",
            "to refuse to let someone come into a place"
        ],
        "answer": "to continue walking in your intended direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk out",
        "options": [
            "to not tell someone something",
            "if something jumps out at you, you notice it immediately",
            "to stop working as a way of protesting about something, ...",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things that are very similar"
        ],
        "answer": "to stop working as a way of protesting about something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "walk out on",
        "options": [
            "start being used",
            "return somewhere",
            "to be a person or company that hides an illegal or secret activity for another person or organization",
            "leave somebody angrily"
        ],
        "answer": "leave somebody angrily"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk over",
        "options": [
            "to do something so that a proposal is accepted or an issue is dealt with quickly",
            "go out for a short time",
            "to treat someone badly and to make them do what you want without respect for their feelings",
            "to cover something with steam, or to become covered with steam"
        ],
        "answer": "to treat someone badly and to make them do what you want without respect for their feelings"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk through",
        "options": [
            "to make something such as rope become straighter by removing it from an object shaped like a wheel that it was put around",
            "to behave in a noisy silly way, ...",
            "to practise or learn something in a slow patient way, or to show someone how to do something",
            "to kill someone by hanging them"
        ],
        "answer": "to practise or learn something in a slow patient way, or to show someone how to do something"
    },
    {
        "question": "walk up",
        "options": [
            "to try to make yourself or someone else feel mentally ready for something",
            "to gradually start to affect or change something, ...",
            "go to someone",
            "same as drop"
        ],
        "answer": "go to someone"
    },
    {
        "question": "waltz off with",
        "options": [
            "to force someone into an unpleasant state or situation, ...",
            "to take something without asking permission",
            "to write something quickly, ...",
            "leave somewhere quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to take something without asking permission"
    },
    {
        "question": "waltz through",
        "options": [
            "to use a situation or emotions such as fear or worry in order to get what you want, ...",
            "want something a lot, especially if you shouldn't want it or can't have it",
            "to walk or go somewhere in a relaxed and confident way, ...",
            "to stop working as a way of protesting about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to walk or go somewhere in a relaxed and confident way, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wander off",
        "options": [
            "to use all of something and not have any left, ...",
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "to seem to gradually change into something else",
            "stop paying attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "stop paying attention, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "want for",
        "options": [
            "to try to find out more about something, or to do something more to deal with it, ...",
            "to wait, ...",
            "to have everything that you need, ...",
            "to keep following or talking to someone and not let them go, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to have everything that you need, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "want in",
        "options": [
            "to live or work with someone in a friendly way",
            "to wish to enter a place, ...",
            "to not do something you were going to do because you are too frightened",
            "break something with your feet"
        ],
        "answer": "to wish to enter a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "want out",
        "options": [
            "to improve, ...",
            "to cut through something such as a tree with a saw so that it falls to the ground",
            "to wish to leave a place, ...",
            "to replace the original soundtrack of a film with one in a different language, so that the actors seem to be speaking the other language"
        ],
        "answer": "to wish to leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "warm through",
        "options": [
            "to sink below the surface of the water, ...",
            "to heat food until it is warm in all parts",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "if the sun breaks through the clouds, it appears from behind them, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to heat food until it is warm in all parts"
    },
    {
        "question": "warm to",
        "options": [
            "to try to find something that you want or need, ...",
            "to begin to like someone or something",
            "to stop for a moment in order to consider something",
            "to hit something very hard while moving fast, causing injury or damage, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to begin to like someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "warm up",
        "options": [
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ...",
            "sell a house or business to move somewhere or do something different",
            "same as tumble, ...",
            "same as warm, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as warm, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "warn away",
        "options": [
            "if time ticks away or ticks by, it passes, ...",
            "to warn someone not to come near, because of a possible problem or danger",
            "if a ship puts in, it stops at a port, ...",
            "to put a ball on a tee"
        ],
        "answer": "to warn someone not to come near, because of a possible problem or danger"
    },
    {
        "question": "warn off",
        "options": [
            "to remove the parts of something that you do not want by cutting them",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to tell someone that they must stop doing something and that if they do not something bad will happen to them",
            "to trick someone by pretending something or by behaving dishonestly"
        ],
        "answer": "to tell someone that they must stop doing something and that if they do not something bad will happen to them"
    },
    {
        "question": "wash away",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something, ...",
            "if something such as rain or a river washes something away, it carries it away",
            "to go to a meeting or a class although you are not directly involved in it",
            "to obey a rule, law, agreement etc, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "if something such as rain or a river washes something away, it carries it away"
    },
    {
        "question": "wash down",
        "options": [
            "to make a short visit to a person or place",
            "to have a good result, ...",
            "to wash the whole surface of something, ...",
            "if roads, streets etc meet up, they join or cross each other, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wash the whole surface of something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wash off",
        "options": [
            "if you wash dirt off something, or if dirt washes off, you remove it by washing",
            "to save money for the future, often hiding it illegally",
            "to target, ...",
            "to be extremely nice to someone more important than you because you want them to like you or give you something"
        ],
        "answer": "if you wash dirt off something, or if dirt washes off, you remove it by washing"
    },
    {
        "question": "wash out",
        "options": [
            "confuse, deceive",
            "to start a journey by ship, ...",
            "to wash something quickly, especially the inside of a container, ...",
            "to spend a period of time in sleeping, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wash something quickly, especially the inside of a container, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wash over",
        "options": [
            "suddenly experience a strong emotion",
            "to attack someone and hit and kick them, ...",
            "same as flip",
            "to come together as a group in order to achieve something"
        ],
        "answer": "suddenly experience a strong emotion"
    },
    {
        "question": "wash up",
        "options": [
            "to be immediately very interested in something or very keen to do or have something",
            "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ...",
            "if a happy or excited feeling bubbles over, you feel it very strongly and usually show that you are feeling it",
            "used to tell someone to go away, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to wash plates, cups, spoons etc after a meal, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "waste away",
        "options": [
            "to gradually become thinner and weaker over a period of time, usually because of an illness",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ...",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private",
            "to force someone into an unpleasant state or situation, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually become thinner and weaker over a period of time, usually because of an illness"
    },
    {
        "question": "watch for",
        "options": [
            "to fill a space in a wall with bricks",
            "to pay attention so that you will see something when it arrives or happens",
            "leave somewhere in a defiant or pompous manner",
            "if two people live together, they are not married but live in the same house and have a sexual relationship"
        ],
        "answer": "to pay attention so that you will see something when it arrives or happens"
    },
    {
        "question": "watch out",
        "options": [
            "to be careful",
            "to ask someone to come into your house, for example after you have been out with them",
            "to show the shape of something by drawing it on a surface, ...",
            "to create a situation in which people meet and do something together, especially when they would not usually do so"
        ],
        "answer": "to be careful"
    },
    {
        "question": "watch out for",
        "options": [
            "same as watch, ...",
            "to write something again exactly as it has been written",
            "to happen, ...",
            "end in an unsuccessful way"
        ],
        "answer": "same as watch, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "watch over",
        "options": [
            "same as grind",
            "to guard, protect, or be in charge of someone or something",
            "to be sent by post, ...",
            "to pull a plant out of the ground, including its roots"
        ],
        "answer": "to guard, protect, or be in charge of someone or something"
    },
    {
        "question": "water down",
        "options": [
            "arrive",
            "to add water to a drink or liquid in order to make it less strong, ...",
            "to masturbate",
            "get money from someone under false pretences"
        ],
        "answer": "to add water to a drink or liquid in order to make it less strong, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wave aside",
        "options": [
            "force someone",
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ...",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "to ignore someone\u2019s ideas, feelings, or opinions because you do not think they are important"
        ],
        "answer": "to ignore someone\u2019s ideas, feelings, or opinions because you do not think they are important"
    },
    {
        "question": "wave down",
        "options": [
            "to enjoy and become very excited about something, especially in a sexual way",
            "to buy large amounts of something or all of it that is available",
            "to keep doing something in a determined way, especially when it is boring or difficult",
            "to make a vehicle stop by waving your arm or hand at the driver"
        ],
        "answer": "to make a vehicle stop by waving your arm or hand at the driver"
    },
    {
        "question": "wave off",
        "options": [
            "to become known by the public",
            "to get nearer to a particular time or stage in a process, ...",
            "to leave quickly, ...",
            "to say goodbye to someone by waving as they leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to say goodbye to someone by waving as they leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "wave on",
        "options": [
            "to become covered in spots because you are ill or because your body reacts to a food or medicine",
            "hurry away, leave somewhere quickly",
            "make a hand signal to tell someone to keep moving",
            "to succeed in living or working without someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "make a hand signal to tell someone to keep moving"
    },
    {
        "question": "wave through",
        "options": [
            "to invent a story, poem etc, ...",
            "to enter a place illegally and steal things from it, ...",
            "to kill someone with a gun, ...",
            "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to give permission or approval for something immediately and often without checking or considering it properly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wean off",
        "options": [
            "to escape with something that you have stolen",
            "same as let, ...",
            "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit",
            "to destroy or remove a structure or part of a structure"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone gradually stop depending on something that they like and have become used to, especially a drug or a bad habit"
    },
    {
        "question": "wean on",
        "options": [
            "to still seem true or correct after being examined carefully, ...",
            "to put soil around a plant in order to protect it or to help it to grow",
            "to make someone get used to something when they are young",
            "to encourage someone to do something stupid or wrong"
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone get used to something when they are young"
    },
    {
        "question": "wear away",
        "options": [
            "to disappear, or to make something disappear, because it has been used or rubbed a lot",
            "to think that something is the right thing to do, ...",
            "used to remind someone of something stupid or bad that they did, ...",
            "to have an erection, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to disappear, or to make something disappear, because it has been used or rubbed a lot"
    },
    {
        "question": "wear down",
        "options": [
            "if you fall about or fall about laughing, you laugh a lot at something",
            "to take someone away from someone else they are with so that you can speak to them in a place where other people cannot watch or listen",
            "to decide not to do something you agreed to do",
            "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone gradually lose their energy or confidence, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wear in",
        "options": [
            "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable",
            "to pretend that something is true, ...",
            "to not approve of something",
            "to spend a lot of time with someone, especially someone who other people do not approve of"
        ],
        "answer": "if you wear in something such as a pair of shoes, you wear them until they fit your feet better and are more comfortable"
    },
    {
        "question": "wear off",
        "options": [
            "if a feeling wears off, it gradually disappears, ...",
            "write something quickly",
            "if people club together, each of them gives some money so that all the money collected can be used to buy something",
            "to start dealing with someone or something much more strictly"
        ],
        "answer": "if a feeling wears off, it gradually disappears, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wear on",
        "options": [
            "fire a gun repeatedly",
            "to stop yourself from showing tears or an emotion",
            "if time wears on, it passes, ...",
            "to continue to do something that may involve problems or that other people are opposing"
        ],
        "answer": "if time wears on, it passes, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wear out",
        "options": [
            "to make someone feel very tired, ...",
            "to change the time of a clock or watch to a later time, ...",
            "if an injury heals over, new skin forms over it and it becomes healthy again",
            "to add something as an extra cost, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel very tired, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "weary of",
        "options": [
            "to become tired of something or bored with it",
            "to reach a particular level, amount etc",
            "to make a dead person live again, ...",
            "if a vehicle moves off, it starts to move"
        ],
        "answer": "to become tired of something or bored with it"
    },
    {
        "question": "weasel out",
        "options": [
            "stop doing something annoying",
            "to collect money from people in a group for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to do something immediately, and often with enthusiasm, as soon as you have the chance to do it",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way"
        ],
        "answer": "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way"
    },
    {
        "question": "weasel out of",
        "options": [
            "same as put aside",
            "form a pair with someone",
            "to quickly put on a piece of clothing, ...",
            "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way"
        ],
        "answer": "to back out of a situation or a commitment, usually in a sneaky way"
    },
    {
        "question": "weed out",
        "options": [
            "inform the authorities about someone",
            "to look at a lot of things in order to find what you want or need",
            "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection",
            "to force someone or something to leave a place"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a person or thing that is not suitable or good enough, especially from a group or collection"
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh down",
        "options": [
            "to grow trees, plants, or seeds in a container or an area so that they fill it completely",
            "start to have a negative feeling",
            "keep something near you",
            "to make someone heavy and unable to move easily, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone heavy and unable to move easily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh down on",
        "options": [
            "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc",
            "same as empty",
            "to do an activity with people who are already doing it",
            "to try to find out information about someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "burden with responsibilities, duties, etc"
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh in",
        "options": [
            "to be caused by something",
            "to become involved in something, ...",
            "same as spread, ...",
            "to arrange for a person or animal to stay with someone who is paid to look after them for a period of time"
        ],
        "answer": "to become involved in something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh in on",
        "options": [
            "to get just enough money or food to be able to continue to exist, ...",
            "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea",
            "to have to deal with something difficult or unpleasant",
            "to persuade someone to buy or accept something that you do not want, especially something of low quality"
        ],
        "answer": "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea"
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh into",
        "options": [
            "same as pen, ...",
            "to start to criticize or blame someone angrily, ...",
            "to escape from a prison, ...",
            "to separate one part of a room from another, for example to make it more private"
        ],
        "answer": "to start to criticize or blame someone angrily, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh on",
        "options": [
            "to do something to hurt or upset someone after they have hurt or upset you",
            "same as land, ...",
            "try to achieve something difficult",
            "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried"
        ],
        "answer": "to cause problems for someone or something, or to make someone worried"
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh out",
        "options": [
            "be less successful",
            "to measure an exact amount of something",
            "to gain an advantage over someone",
            "to ask questions and examine the answers in order to find out the truth about something"
        ],
        "answer": "to measure an exact amount of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "weigh up",
        "options": [
            "to consider the good and bad aspects of something in order to reach a decision about it",
            "same as lay, ...",
            "to recognize the difference between two people or things",
            "to search for someone or something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to consider the good and bad aspects of something in order to reach a decision about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "weird out",
        "options": [
            "same as flip",
            "to make someone feel strange",
            "same as get",
            "to separate an object into pieces, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone feel strange"
    },
    {
        "question": "well up",
        "options": [
            "to die. This word is used to avoid saying \u2018die\u2019 when you think this might upset someone",
            "feel tears starting, ...",
            "to talk to someone who has done something wrong in an effort to persuade them to improve their behaviour",
            "to ask someone for help, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "feel tears starting, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "whack off",
        "options": [
            "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)",
            "to know about someone or something, but not know any details, ...",
            "same as stop",
            "if a spaceship blasts off, it leaves the ground"
        ],
        "answer": "if a man whacks off, he masturbates (=gets sexual pleasure from rubbing his penis)"
    },
    {
        "question": "wheel around",
        "options": [
            "delay or avoid doing something",
            "to arrive in a place, ...",
            "to turn around quickly where you are standing",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way"
        ],
        "answer": "to turn around quickly where you are standing"
    },
    {
        "question": "wheel out",
        "options": [
            "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ...",
            "to have a particular number or amount as an average, ...",
            "to make something increase",
            "to ask someone to go somewhere with you or do something with you"
        ],
        "answer": "to show people something new, or to make something new available, for the first time, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wheel round",
        "options": [
            "have sex",
            "turn quickly and face in the opposite direction",
            "depart in a hurry",
            "behave indecisively"
        ],
        "answer": "turn quickly and face in the opposite direction"
    },
    {
        "question": "while away",
        "options": [
            "to spend time in a relaxed way when you have nothing else to do",
            "same as beat up",
            "be submitted, arrive, ...",
            "to remain strong or in a fairly good condition, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to spend time in a relaxed way when you have nothing else to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "whip into",
        "options": [
            "provide someone with necessary equipment",
            "to accept an offer or invitation that someone has made",
            "to make someone become very excited, ...",
            "to make part of a company into a new independent company, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make someone become very excited, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "whip off",
        "options": [
            "remove quickly, ...",
            "make yourself popular with someone",
            "same as pine",
            "invite someone"
        ],
        "answer": "remove quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "whip out",
        "options": [
            "to attack someone violently",
            "if something, especially a secret, slips out, you say it without intending to",
            "if something lies ahead, especially something difficult or unpleasant, it is going to happen in the future and you will have to deal with it",
            "remove quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "remove quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "whip out of",
        "options": [
            "to replace a swearword in a television or radio broadcast with a short high sound, so that people are not offended",
            "to experience a dangerous or unpleasant situation and still be alive after it",
            "to go in the direction of someone or something",
            "exit rapidly"
        ],
        "answer": "exit rapidly"
    },
    {
        "question": "whip through",
        "options": [
            "to do something very quickly",
            "to agree to do what someone wants you to do, although you do not want to",
            "to think about what is likely to happen, or to plan what you are going to do in the future",
            "to have existed since or for a particular time, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "whip up",
        "options": [
            "used on signs to tell people not to go into a place, ...",
            "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ...",
            "to spend an amount of money, ...",
            "to prepare something to eat very quickly, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to prepare something to eat very quickly, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "whisk away",
        "options": [
            "to accept someone\u2019s opinion or decision, especially because you respect them",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement to be included in something",
            "to improve something, to get rid of imperfections from something, ...",
            "take to another place quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "take to another place quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "whisk off",
        "options": [
            "to agree with an idea",
            "wipe, remove with a brush, ...",
            "move or drive very fast, ...",
            "to find something, or to meet someone, by accident"
        ],
        "answer": "wipe, remove with a brush, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "whistle at",
        "options": [
            "to whistle to show that you think someone is sexually attractive",
            "to say goodbye to someone by waving as they leave",
            "to have sex with someone",
            "to start a new activity, especially one that involves some risk"
        ],
        "answer": "to whistle to show that you think someone is sexually attractive"
    },
    {
        "question": "white out",
        "options": [
            "to criticize someone or something",
            "to switch a computer on in the correct way",
            "use correction fluid to cover a mistake in a written text",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "use correction fluid to cover a mistake in a written text"
    },
    {
        "question": "whittle away",
        "options": [
            "to use something such as time or effort for a particular purpose, ...",
            "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need",
            "to be given to someone or something, ...",
            "to gradually reduce the amount or importance of something"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually reduce the amount or importance of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "whittle down",
        "options": [
            "to add more information",
            "lower the top part of your body",
            "to reduce the number of people or things, or the size of something",
            "same as spit, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the number of people or things, or the size of something"
    },
    {
        "question": "whizz through",
        "options": [
            "if something gnaws at you, you keep worrying about it or feeling upset about it",
            "to do something very quickly and not very carefully",
            "to become weaker or less common and then disappear completely",
            "to make someone feel unhappy or less hopeful, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to do something very quickly and not very carefully"
    },
    {
        "question": "wig out",
        "options": [
            "to appear or to be produced suddenly and quickly",
            "to start driving in a higher gear",
            "become excited and lose control",
            "give away secrets about someone"
        ],
        "answer": "become excited and lose control"
    },
    {
        "question": "wiggle out",
        "options": [
            "avoid doing",
            "to tell someone that they must stop doing something and that if they do not something bad will happen to them",
            "cause sufficient blood loss to result in death",
            "applaud"
        ],
        "answer": "avoid doing"
    },
    {
        "question": "wiggle out of",
        "options": [
            "avoid doing something",
            "to beat an opponent very easily, ...",
            "same as put forward, ...",
            "to catch fish in a particular area of water, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "avoid doing something"
    },
    {
        "question": "wimp out",
        "options": [
            "to stop someone from thinking clearly, ...",
            "to decide not to do something because you are frightened or not confident",
            "to press a key on a computer that makes the previous page of a document appear on the screen",
            "to blame or criticize someone in an unpleasant, unkind way"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide not to do something because you are frightened or not confident"
    },
    {
        "question": "win back",
        "options": [
            "to find and arrest people, ...",
            "to get back something that you have lost",
            "to move about in large numbers in a confused way with no particular purpose",
            "if a situation is looking up, it is getting better, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to get back something that you have lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "win out",
        "options": [
            "to think carefully about something over a period of time",
            "same as build on",
            "same as fiddle, ...",
            "to succeed after great difficulty"
        ],
        "answer": "to succeed after great difficulty"
    },
    {
        "question": "win over",
        "options": [
            "if you are struck on someone or something, you like them, ...",
            "to make an activity or process begin",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you or to be friendly to you",
            "study something quickly, revise"
        ],
        "answer": "to persuade someone to agree with you or to be friendly to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "wind down",
        "options": [
            "to wait or be patient, ...",
            "to separate an area from the rest of a room with a partition",
            "to end, or to finish something gradually, ...",
            "to increase or improve something, or to make it more interesting"
        ],
        "answer": "to end, or to finish something gradually, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wind on",
        "options": [
            "forward a film or tape to a certain point",
            "to look for or try to think of something, especially when you feel pressure to do something quickly",
            "used to tell someone to go away, ...",
            "finally manage to do something"
        ],
        "answer": "forward a film or tape to a certain point"
    },
    {
        "question": "wind up",
        "options": [
            "same as wind, ...",
            "to go away, or to leave",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to ignore someone or something, or to refuse to consider them"
        ],
        "answer": "same as wind, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wink at",
        "options": [
            "stop doing something annoying",
            "grow again",
            "to pretend that you have not noticed something or do not know about it, because you do not approve of it",
            "sign a document joining or agreeing to something"
        ],
        "answer": "to pretend that you have not noticed something or do not know about it, because you do not approve of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "winkle out",
        "options": [
            "to put special thick soft covers on your legs in order to protect them before you start hitting the ball in the game of cricket",
            "approach quietly or secretly",
            "to try to make someone or something leave a place, ...",
            "to spend money on something, especially when you do not want to"
        ],
        "answer": "to try to make someone or something leave a place, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "winnow down",
        "options": [
            "to keep treating someone badly or unfairly, especially by criticizing them, ...",
            "entertain someone in your home",
            "to reduce the size of a group of people or things so that you only keep the best or most useful ones",
            "to connect something to a piece of equipment, especially using a hook, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the size of a group of people or things so that you only keep the best or most useful ones"
    },
    {
        "question": "winnow out",
        "options": [
            "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group",
            "to put someone in a place where they are kept apart from other people",
            "to begin doing something, especially in a determined or enthusiastic way",
            "to make someone feel so guilty or embarrassed that they do what you want"
        ],
        "answer": "to separate the useful or important people or things from the rest of a group"
    },
    {
        "question": "wipe down",
        "options": [
            "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth",
            "to cause difficulties or pain for someone, ...",
            "to be full of a strong emotion, ...",
            "to stop existing or being noticeable, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to clean a surface thoroughly with a cloth"
    },
    {
        "question": "wipe off",
        "options": [
            "same as bring round",
            "to reduce the value of something by a large amount",
            "to continue to talk for a long time",
            "to make two different things equal in amount or value"
        ],
        "answer": "to reduce the value of something by a large amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "wipe out",
        "options": [
            "to invent or to imagine something, especially an excuse",
            "to kill someone, ...",
            "same as lie, ...",
            "clock in, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to kill someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wipe up",
        "options": [
            "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth",
            "to suddenly stop moving or working properly",
            "to cover something completely with frost, or to become completely covered with frost",
            "to continue doing something that takes a lot of effort or is likely to cause you problems"
        ],
        "answer": "to remove a liquid from a surface using a cloth"
    },
    {
        "question": "wire up",
        "options": [
            "to dig ground in order to prepare it for new plants",
            "change tv channels quickly",
            "to ignore or not mention a statement or subject, ...",
            "make electrical connections"
        ],
        "answer": "make electrical connections"
    },
    {
        "question": "wise up",
        "options": [
            "say numbers aloud in a sequence",
            "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something",
            "to put someone in a room and lock the door so they cannot leave, ...",
            "to focus on satisfying the people who are above you in an organization, more than on the people you are responsible for"
        ],
        "answer": "to learn or understand the truth about something, or to tell someone the truth about something"
    },
    {
        "question": "wish away",
        "options": [
            "to do something good that helps someone to feel better after you did something bad to them, ...",
            "to make something stop or disappear just by expressing a wish",
            "be suitable, have the necessary qualities",
            "same as linger, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make something stop or disappear just by expressing a wish"
    },
    {
        "question": "wish for",
        "options": [
            "to enclose an area using ropes, usually because of danger",
            "to return to a place, ...",
            "same as put, ...",
            "to want something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to want something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "witness to",
        "options": [
            "to make someone remember something that happened in the past, ...",
            "to produce a lot of something, ...",
            "a way of encouraging someone",
            "to formally state that something is true, especially in a court of law"
        ],
        "answer": "to formally state that something is true, especially in a court of law"
    },
    {
        "question": "word up",
        "options": [
            "to force someone to leave a place, organization etc",
            "give someone information, advice",
            "to be owned by someone, ...",
            "to start talking about something when it is not necessary, usually something unpleasant that happened in the past and that other people want to forget"
        ],
        "answer": "give someone information, advice"
    },
    {
        "question": "word up!",
        "options": [
            "spoil or ruin something",
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination",
            "a phrase that was used a greeting",
            "to consider or express something in a different way, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "a phrase that was used a greeting"
    },
    {
        "question": "work around",
        "options": [
            "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim",
            "to pay money that you owe, especially when you are unwilling to pay",
            "to form a solid mass, ...",
            "to make arrangements to prevent or deal with something bad that may happen"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal successfully with a person or problem that might prevent you from achieving your aim"
    },
    {
        "question": "work around to",
        "options": [
            "watch or listen to a tv or radio programme",
            "to leave a place quickly and angrily",
            "to gradually start to talk or write about a particular subject in a conversation or piece of writing, especially because it is embarrassing",
            "do something quickly"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually start to talk or write about a particular subject in a conversation or piece of writing, especially because it is embarrassing"
    },
    {
        "question": "work at",
        "options": [
            "same as cough, ...",
            "try to improve something, usually making things worse, ...",
            "to make something more complete, especially by adding another feature",
            "to try hard to develop or improve something"
        ],
        "answer": "to try hard to develop or improve something"
    },
    {
        "question": "work in",
        "options": [
            "if something grosses you out, it is so unpleasant that it makes you feel ill",
            "to suddenly stop working, ...",
            "to mix one substance completely into another one, usually using your hands, ...",
            "to happen, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to mix one substance completely into another one, usually using your hands, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "work off",
        "options": [
            "to discover information by searching for it in a determined way",
            "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ...",
            "move in a dramatic or affected manner",
            "to be busy doing, discussing, or thinking about something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to pay someone what you owe them by doing a job for them instead of giving them money, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "work on",
        "options": [
            "to leave a place, ...",
            "to try to influence someone, ...",
            "to be accepted, wrongly, as being a particular type of person or thing",
            "to murder someone, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to influence someone, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "work out",
        "options": [
            "same as brighten, ...",
            "to leave a group of people, usually because of a disagreement, ...",
            "to decide or agree on something, ...",
            "to quickly produce something and make it available for people to buy"
        ],
        "answer": "to decide or agree on something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "work over",
        "options": [
            "to injure someone severely by hitting them",
            "to behave in a brave way in a very sad or difficult situation",
            "to make someone get used to something when they are young",
            "be absent from a place"
        ],
        "answer": "to injure someone severely by hitting them"
    },
    {
        "question": "work through",
        "options": [
            "to be lively, exciting, and enjoyable, ...",
            "to push or press downwards, ...",
            "to deal with something such as a problem or a strong feeling by thinking and talking about it",
            "to tell someone in authority, especially the police, about something bad that someone else has done"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with something such as a problem or a strong feeling by thinking and talking about it"
    },
    {
        "question": "work towards",
        "options": [
            "to do things that help you to make progress towards something that you want to achieve",
            "same as pick, ...",
            "to begin to be involved with a particular person or group, ...",
            "to count and check all the money that a shop has received in a day"
        ],
        "answer": "to do things that help you to make progress towards something that you want to achieve"
    },
    {
        "question": "work up",
        "options": [
            "to develop something, ...",
            "to move away from someone or something, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away or not get involved in something",
            "to stay in bed in the morning for longer than usual"
        ],
        "answer": "to develop something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "work up to",
        "options": [
            "to tell or show something to someone, especially when you do not expect them to like it, ...",
            "to not go to sleep until someone comes home, ...",
            "to develop or to increase and reach a particular level, ...",
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress"
        ],
        "answer": "to develop or to increase and reach a particular level, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "worm out of",
        "options": [
            "same as build, ...",
            "add a keyword link or bookmark to a blog entry or webpage",
            "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you",
            "let down, snub"
        ],
        "answer": "to gradually get information from someone who does not want to give it to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "worry at",
        "options": [
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort",
            "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ...",
            "something that makes you feel very disappointed or upset, especially when you have been trying hard to achieve something",
            "to reduce a number to the nearest whole number, or the nearest number ending in zero"
        ],
        "answer": "if you worry at a problem, you keep thinking about it and trying to solve it, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wrap around",
        "options": [
            "to put something around something else",
            "to change something so that it is suitable for a particular purpose",
            "be lazy, do nothing",
            "to go away, or to leave"
        ],
        "answer": "to put something around something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "wrap round",
        "options": [
            "return somewhere",
            "leave somewhere safe or comfortable",
            "to put something around something else",
            "same as rain"
        ],
        "answer": "to put something around something else"
    },
    {
        "question": "wrap up",
        "options": [
            "break the surface of soil",
            "to write your name on an official list when you arrive at a place, ...",
            "same as connect, ...",
            "same as wrap, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as wrap, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "wrestle with",
        "options": [
            "to encourage someone to do something stupid or wrong",
            "same as meet, ...",
            "to try to deal with or solve a difficult problem",
            "to agree by a written legal agreement not to be included in something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to try to deal with or solve a difficult problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "wriggle out of",
        "options": [
            "to give someone money or property in a legal and official way, ...",
            "break, damage or hurt by hitting",
            "to remove one part of something",
            "avoid doing something in a way other people don't like"
        ],
        "answer": "avoid doing something in a way other people don't like"
    },
    {
        "question": "write away",
        "options": [
            "same as write off",
            "to write something again exactly as it has been written",
            "to surround someone or something, ...",
            "to keep or save something, especially money, so that you can use it in the future, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "same as write off"
    },
    {
        "question": "write back",
        "options": [
            "to steal something, ...",
            "to start driving in a lower gear",
            "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter",
            "to continue doing something, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to send a reply to someone who has sent you a letter"
    },
    {
        "question": "write down",
        "options": [
            "to speak angrily to someone because they have done something wrong",
            "to write something on a piece of paper",
            "if people grow apart, their relationship gradually changes and they become less close",
            "feel tears starting, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write something on a piece of paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "write in",
        "options": [
            "to think carefully and form an opinion about a person or a situation",
            "to add words or numbers that are missing from something, ...",
            "to make something seem more impressive than it really is, ...",
            "same as spy, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to add words or numbers that are missing from something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "write into",
        "options": [
            "enter an argument or discussion to express a strongly felt idea",
            "to reduce the price of something, ...",
            "break, damage or hurt by hitting",
            "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract"
        ],
        "answer": "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract"
    },
    {
        "question": "write off",
        "options": [
            "to play a tune very loudly, especially on the piano",
            "to write to an organization asking for something, ...",
            "to give your opinion on something, especially in a formal way",
            "marry someone of a different ethnicity, religion, etc"
        ],
        "answer": "to write to an organization asking for something, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "write out",
        "options": [
            "to continue doing something in a determined way despite difficulties",
            "to depend on someone or something for the money or food that you need",
            "to spend time somewhere with no particular purpose, feeling bored or unhappy",
            "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to write something again, usually in a more complete form, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "write up",
        "options": [
            "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ...",
            "to depend on something happening or on someone doing something",
            "to behave in a very friendly or polite way to someone because you want them to like you or to do something for you",
            "to write to a person or organization asking them to send something to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to report officially that someone has done something wrong, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "yack on",
        "options": [
            "if a roof or wall falls in, it falls to the ground, ...",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way",
            "to be a natural result of something",
            "put petrol or other fuel into a vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
    },
    {
        "question": "yammer on",
        "options": [
            "to show that you like or love someone or something in a very obvious way that other people think is silly or embarrassing",
            "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way",
            "to behave in a silly way",
            "to remain in one piece and not break apart, or to make something do this, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "talk continuously, especially if it is an annoying way"
    },
    {
        "question": "yell out",
        "options": [
            "to give someone a particular piece of information using the phone",
            "to remain out of your home for a period of time",
            "to shout something",
            "same as button, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to shout something"
    },
    {
        "question": "yield to",
        "options": [
            "to make a profit, ...",
            "to start to get better after being ill or in a bad situation",
            "to agree with someone or something, ...",
            "same as sign, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to make a profit, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "yield up",
        "options": [
            "to finally allow people to see something that has been hidden",
            "if you lay a ship to, or if it lays to, it stops",
            "to give someone money or property in a legal and official way, ...",
            "to become more relaxed and calm, or to make someone more relaxed and calm"
        ],
        "answer": "to finally allow people to see something that has been hidden"
    },
    {
        "question": "zero in on",
        "options": [
            "to try to hurt someone or damage their reputation, ...",
            "to quickly learn something or check that you know it, for example before an examination",
            "to aim at someone or something with a gun or camera, ...",
            "to persuade someone to agree with you or to be friendly to you"
        ],
        "answer": "to aim at someone or something with a gun or camera, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "zero out",
        "options": [
            "cut off funding for a project, ...",
            "to start a journey, ...",
            "to eat food with enthusiasm because you like it or because you are hungry, ...",
            "to make a short visit somewhere"
        ],
        "answer": "cut off funding for a project, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "zip around",
        "options": [
            "a way of expressing disbelief, or telling someone that they're wrong or have an incorrect opinion",
            "to expect something to happen and plan for it",
            "move quickly",
            "same as chill"
        ],
        "answer": "move quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "zip by",
        "options": [
            "to use all of someone\u2019s money, ...",
            "pass quickly",
            "to continue at around the same level, rising and falling only slightly",
            "same as catch, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "pass quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "zip it",
        "options": [
            "keep quiet, say nothing",
            "to produce something of bad quality in large quantities, ...",
            "used for telling someone rudely to go away",
            "to tell someone about someone or something that they want or need"
        ],
        "answer": "keep quiet, say nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "zip through",
        "options": [
            "to make someone more likely to do what you want by being nice to them",
            "to deal with or complete something very quickly",
            "to be connected with something or to influence it",
            "to behave in a silly way"
        ],
        "answer": "to deal with or complete something very quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "zip up",
        "options": [
            "same as fill, ...",
            "to be closed by means of a zip, ...",
            "used as a polite way of asking someone to be patient while you do or finish something",
            "to leave a place, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "to be closed by means of a zip, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "zone in",
        "options": [
            "pay attention after not doing so",
            "make someone excited or nervous",
            "want something a lot",
            "same as shade"
        ],
        "answer": "pay attention after not doing so"
    },
    {
        "question": "zone in on",
        "options": [
            "to experience a problem that slows down your progress",
            "pay attention after not doing so",
            "to treat someone badly and in an unfair way, especially by giving them orders",
            "to say something in support of someone or something"
        ],
        "answer": "pay attention after not doing so"
    },
    {
        "question": "zone out",
        "options": [
            "to treat someone badly, especially because they have less power or importance than you",
            "if you fling off your clothes, you take them off quickly",
            "to tell someone everything that you are feeling, ...",
            "not pay attention, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "not pay attention, ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "zonk out",
        "options": [
            "to keep a mother and baby together after the birth",
            "same as fold, ...",
            "to support an idea, project etc, or help someone in what they are trying to do, ...",
            "fall asleep"
        ],
        "answer": "fall asleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "zoom in",
        "options": [
            "focus more closely",
            "to say or do something with someone else",
            "to make someone go somewhere, especially in order to get rid of them",
            "to succeed in getting enough of something, especially money, by making a lot of effort"
        ],
        "answer": "focus more closely"
    },
    {
        "question": "zoom in on",
        "options": [
            "to touch someone\u2019s clothes in order to check whether they are carrying something such as a weapon or illegal drugs, for example at an airport",
            "focus more closely",
            "to be in a particular place or state after doing something or because of doing it",
            "to manage to do something without any bad results, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "focus more closely"
    },
    {
        "question": "zoom off",
        "options": [
            "to include a particular feature in an official document such as a contract",
            "to be a sign of something bad",
            "go somewhere quickly",
            "to waste time doing stupid things, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "go somewhere quickly"
    },
    {
        "question": "zoom out",
        "options": [
            "focus less closely",
            "to tie your hair tightly so that it does not touch your face",
            "to wash the inside of something quickly, especially in water, ...",
            "if a vehicle or driver drives off, the vehicle starts moving and leaves, ..."
        ],
        "answer": "focus less closely"
    }
]